永无止境的黑暗
我们都很笨拙的人
但我很勇敢，我很坚强
不管谁来，只是闭上我的眼睛
我不想听。不要说话。
不要告诉我应该做什么
Even though I'm brave
I'm always alone, I know it already
I'm already bruised
Life's a jungle with no answers
I'm lonely, sad and lost
I'm trapped in here
This tiny grey building
We're all trapped, floating in air
Hear the car horn beep, beep
We have nowhere to turn
Can you help us?
Who will trust us? We're trapped
19 years old right now
Nineteen
Jeong-hun
Min-seo
Min-seo, what are you doing?
What are you doing down there?
Always singing strange songs
Aren't you going to school?
School? No, I go to work today
Skipping class for a measly casual job
This is my seat
Hey! I marked that page
Don't study at the table
It ruins everyone's appetite
I'm not the same as you
How are we different?
I go to a good university,
I'm going to be an accountant
You go to a poor university
which you hardly ever attend
- Not again!
- She's right
Father...
You need to think about the future
I am thinking about the future
- Not hard enough
- Watch it
You won't get a job with your degree
You're already on your way
to becoming a failure
You should study to acquire a license
Hurry up and eat
Yes, eat up so you can go
earn lots of money today
Close your book
- Hey!
- Watch your manners!
I'm going
Jeong-hun! Have breakfast!
What's wrong with him...?
Eun-a!
Oh... hi
You weren't answering my calls
- Have you been ill?
- I'm fine
You don't look good
You should see a doctor
No, I'm fine
Let's make sure, see a doctor
I am seeing a doctor
- Who's he?
- My boyfriend
Boyfriend?
I'm your boyfriend
This is Su-bin, he's a med student
- How are you feeling?
- I told you not to come
- I finished early today
- They're so pretty, thanks
I picked them from the garden
- How's work going?
- Not bad
I want to see
The manager says I'm good
She lets me help style customers too
Did you design these hairstyles?
- It's nothing
- They're good
I don't need to worry about
you when I'm gone
Don't say that.
You're going to get better
- Hello?
- Where are you?
Get down here now! We're busy!
Sorry, but my mom's ill
I'm at the hospital
Don't give me that excuse.
You're old enough to look after yourself
You're 19, an adult
I pay you wages,
you should take responsibility
Should I stay at work even
though my mother's dying?
Are you shouting at me?
I'm sorry, what I meant was...
You're just an assistant
Don't talk back to me like that
I don't need you, you're fired!
Hello? Hello?
- Hello? I'm sorry about...
- Eun-yeong?
- Yes, speaking...
- It's me...
Are you feeling ill, Min-seo?
I'm fine
Should we go to dad's hospital?
No, I'm fine
Have some cake then, I made it
I ordered the butter from Switzerland
You eat it, then
I made it for you, it's good for you
You need to be strong to study
Study hard, go to university next year
- I'm going out
- Where are you going?
The library
I'm starting another day
Turning on the lights
Who put that cup there?
If I catch them, there'll be trouble
You scared me!
- Boss!
- You're here
Could you help Yeong-ae clean up?
Yeong-ae, take this with you
- What's wrong with her?
- She said she's going to quit
Why?
She got a part in a film
wants to concentrate on her career
I heard she went to acting school
I paid her a high wage too
I guess she's not desperate
You have me here
I'll stand by your side
Thanks a lot
Should I just give up school
and come here everyday?
You're just being kind
You're the kind one for
hiring a fool like me!
I'm going to my son's school
I won't be back until lunch
You're the man in charge
Don't worry
See you later
You scared me
- You're good
- At what? Sucking up?
You sound like a real rapper
You're good
It's nothing
You should try out
for auditions
You know, rap battles
That's too difficult
You have to make up
lyrics freestyle
Just say what comes
to mind naturally
The lyrics will be depressing then
Why? Are you depressed?
That's the story of my life
Tell me about your life,
I'll listen
I don't have anything to say
You're so slow
I'm asking you out on a date
You're what?
Do I have to do all the work?
I liked you from the beginning
- No way Really?
- Why? I'm not your type?
No, that's not it
Girls like you always have boyfriends
I don't date girls like that...
I don't even try
I never imagined that a girl
like that would ask me out
I don't talk to them because...
What I mean is... I'm trying to say...
I'm free... whenever you are
Hang out with me after work?
With you?
I'm coming
I'll get it
Hello.
- It's $1 an hour, you can sit...
- I'm a member
Pick any seat
Hello. Are you a member?
- I'm looking for someone
- Who?
Is Yeong-ae here? I'm her friend
Yeong-ae, your friend's here
I don't care about your dreams
Eun-yeong, please
I came here to
make things clear
I can't do it, I refuse to
What gives you the right to ask me?
I asked because you're my friend
My answer's still no
Don't call me again
Eun-yeong...
- Hey... will you protect me?
- Of course I will I'll protect you
- You will?
- I give you my word
You have to watch over me. Promise me
Follow me
Who did it? Tell them to all come out
I'll get them all!
- Are we...
- What is it? Tell me
Are we going to meet again?
Are we going out?
I don't know
Why not?
How about if we
just live together?
Live together?
We're both 19... wouldn't it be fun?
People don't think fondly of unmarried
couples living together
My parents are really conservative
I'm just kidding
You're going to protect me, right?
See you tomorrow!
An adult, yet still a child
Yearning for independence
Endless opportunities
An age of transition...
We were at that age, 19
- Look!
- What?
Her wallet's here...
she didn't get mugged
You're right...what's this?
She must have gone to a club
A club??
A nightclub that kids go to
Where's her cell phone?
I don't see it. Maybe she dropped it
Or someone threw it in the river
We've got a smart one on our hands
Mom! I don't have school today
Where were you last night?
Why do you care? Let me sleep
- The police are here
- What?
- Are you Seo Jeong-hun?
- Yes, why do you ask?
- Do you know Oh Yeong-ae?
- Oh Yeong-ae?
What's happened?
Her body was found along the river
What?
You must be joking
What does my son have to do with it?
You'll need to come to the station
Around 1:30 last night at the southern
end of the Han River
A witness says they saw someone
push a young girl into the water
I don't believe it
Who would do that to Yeong-ae?
You worked together?
Yes, it's been about 6 months
- Were you close?
- Excuse me?
I'm just asking if you were friends
Were you?
We chatted while working sometimes
That's all
Are you a student?
I'm a freshman at Samhwa University
What's your major?
Humanities and cultural studies
What's that?
The stylist attends to the customer
I help out and learn the ropes
You're just a junior then
We're referred to as staff
Have you learnt a lot?
- It doesn't matter now
- Why not?
- I got fired
- When was that?
- Yesterday
- Why did you get fired?
I talked back to the boss
She fired me
I would have done the same
So you were mad
Your friend was murdered
yesterday too
It's got nothing to do with me
It's got nothing to do with you?
Isn't this camera yours?
Is it yours?
We went to a club, then...
Where did you go afterwards?
- Home
- Did you head straight home?
You don't remember?
You can't think?
No! I mean yes, no!
We went to the river for some air
You got some fresh air and...
We just talked and went home early
I mean it, we went home early
You mean early in the morning...
You don't know anything?
Your friend died
but you know nothing
- You're not even sad?
- It's unfortunate what happened
She's a school mate
but we were never close
She's not really my friend
Is that why she called
you every day?
Tell me who took
these photos then
Your father's
a famous businessman
You shouldn't get messed up like this
Did you tell my parents?
What?
We looked at Yeong-ae's call records
She called you last week 6 times in fact
That's because...
You're a precious son at home
I've met mama boys
like you before
You can't even go chat up a girl
You follow them around in hiding
Take photos of them like a pervert
She probably accused you of stalking her
You were embarrassed, got angry...
Fine then! She called me for money
Money?
She kept asking to borrow money
I work so she thinks
I have money
I'm a staff, I hardly earn anything
So?
I can't even pay my mom's hospital fees
I told her I didn't have any money
I didn't kill her. Why would I do that?
- Then why did you lie?
- I didn't lie
You lied from the beginning
You weren't close to her
You went home after the club
You must have something to hide
- Detective Ha
- Yes?
I'll get an arrest warrant,
write up a report
Yes, sir
You hopeless fool
I feel sorry for your parents
They pay to send you to university
All you do is hook up
with girls and go to clubs
Stop putting words in my mouth
- Am I making you angry?
- Stop it!
How old are you anyway?
How old are you?
Sit back down. We're not done yet
I have to pee!
- Mama boys like you...
- Don't call me that!
The mama boy knows how to talk
She's pretty so I took some photos
Why don't you trust me?
Because you're a pervert, a stalker
Don't trust me then
I did it I killed Yeong-ae
I killed her.
Is that what you want to hear?
You're just a kid... already...
Looking for women...
- Think of... your future
- Stop it!
What do you think you're doing!
Don't!
- Hurry up!
- Get them!
Boys shouldn't come in here
I'm not a boy!
You stay right there
Detective Ha, what happened?
Sorry, he knocked me out
- Hurry and find them
- Yes, sir
That way!
There they are!
You're a genius!
What? You lost them?
- Sorry
- How embarrassing
We didn't expect the kids to...
I should've chosen athletes
At least they can run fast
Congratulations on a job well done
You lost all 3 of them?
Fooled by a bunch of 19 year olds
I'm sorry
Did you forcefully accuse
them of being criminals?
Kids these days aren't scared of us
They know juvenile sentences are short
- Kids like that deserve...
- Detective Kim
Stop it, please!
If you're on my side, you could
end up getting fired too
I'm not taking sides
I just want to catch our criminal
What's wrong?
Tell us the truth
The police said you confessed
- I didn't do it
- Then who?
The police said he killed Yeong-ae
- I didn't do it, it's not me
- Then why did you confess?
- It's not me
- He didn't kill her
How do you know that?
- Did you kill her?
- No!
Look how pathetic he is
Do you think he could kill someone?
No.
What do we do now?
We escaped, but what do we do now?
They'll think we ran
because we're guilty
We didn't just run.
We attacked the officers too
It's all a big mess, I'm going home
Have you lost your mind?
The police will be there by now
I'm more scared of my parents
than going to jail
What?
That's stupid You're weird
You don't know my parents
Staring at the door
isn't going to open it
Let's just go
What did they say?
They refuse to meet us unless
we come with their lawyer
Did you tell them their son
confessed and ran away?
They already knew
The chief called them himself
You're lucky your parents are rich
Your dad's a millionaire?
You're going to inherit everything?
No...right now I'm repeating
to go to university
There's nothing wrong with that
You need money to study like that
Better than going to
a bad school like me
My parents are always
telling me to repeat
My son? Jeong-hun?
Calm down
My son murdered someone?
We need to investigate further
Do you know where he might have gone?
I'm not sure what you mean...
A friend's place or somewhere
he often visited
I'm always busy at work...
Can you think of somewhere?
I'm not sure... Hyangja, do you know?
You all have no idea?
She just took her medicine
Cervical Cancer
Is it serious?
How long does she have left?
She doesn't have much time left
- How long has she been here?
- A little over 6 months
Her daughter quit school and works
at a hairdresser's to pay for her mom
Her ex-husband has never visited
Her daughter's a little rude,
but she seems all right
You're my hero
- You're such a good daughter
- Forget it
You should've seen the detective
make fun of me for being a staff
- I'm still so mad!
- Same here
He doesn't even know what humanities
and cultural studies is...
Said I'm wasting my parents' money
Same here He kept calling me a mama boy
I was so angry
Right! Going back to
the police is a stupid idea
- I agree
- I think so too
I'm going to ask one last time
You really didn't kill Yeong-ae?
Of course I didn't!
I was just a customer there
She's got nothing to do with me
I don't even remember her face
- You?
- I didn't kill her
She just called me to borrow money
What about you then?
We worked at the internet cafe
We had dinner once, last night
That's it!
Nothing happened between us
I swear it
All right
I trust you both
I trust you too
Same here
Turn your phones off
Before they track us down
Then it's time for us...
To escape
Hey
We're all the same age, 19
Yes, so we are
Why do you keep speaking politely?
I'm...
Is it because you're rich?
- Think you're a prince?
- Don't be mean
It's... just a habit
Just speak to us like we're friends
Let's introduce ourselves properly
- What are your names? I'm...
- Wait a minute
We don't need to know your name
Name, age, school, where you live...
People always ask but it's meaningless
Won't it be more fun if we don't know?
- Fine I'm age 19, number 1
- Then I'm number 2
- Then I will be number 13
- Why skip to number 13?
I just feel like it
- I told you to go home
- I know, but...
Study for your administration exam
You're wasting time here
You'll just get beaten up by hooligans
Orjust a bunch of 19 year olds
- Watch it!
- It's all right, go home
Seonmin, go buy me some socks
What color socks should I buy?
Black, it's always black
Yes
I'll see you later
Hey! That hurt!
They seem like good kids
Detectives don't need warm hearts
No, I mean those kids
we brought in
I feel sorry for the girl
- So what?
- Excuse me?
Her mom's sick so it's all right
for her to kill someone?
Their families don't care about
them so it's okay to kill?
That's not what I meant
You don't need to feel sorry for them
Yes, sir
Can I ask you something?
Why do you hate teenagers so much?
You're strict on juveniles,
- even today
- I don't like them
I don't like kids like them
Hey! Leave her alone!
Stop it! Don't! Leave her alone!
Sin!
This stop is Mokpo, Mokpo station
Where are we? The air's so fresh
I wanted to come to a place like this
after I become a freshman
I wanted to come with my boyfriend
In your dreams!
One person should look after the money
You do it, you're rich
No, you do it
Your father works at a bank
I'm not good handling money
I get sick looking at numbers
- Your order's ready
- Great! Ddeokbokki!
You're lucky to be rich.
You can buy whatever you want
Yes...but I don't really need anything
You don't need anything?
She gave us a lot
- Hey! Slow down
- Have some water
I didn't know Ddeokbokki
was so delicious!
You've never tried it?
My mom said it's junk food...
She told me not to eat it
You're joking
You do everything
your mom says?
Because I'm repeating...
Right now, you're a fugitive...
You're on the run Do whatever you want
What else haven't you done before?
You play, I don't want to...
Did you see that?
What?
We spent it... we went around a lot
I don't believe this.
You're supposed to be our Treasurer
Stop it
We don't know how long we'll run
You should've been more careful
with our spendings
- We all spent it together
- You should've stopped him
Don't blame me!
You bought those sunglasses
I'm sorry, it's my fault
But I have a credit card
We can't use a credit card!
Don't shout. This is your fault too
Stay out of this
Let the men handle it
- Stop it, you ugly...
- Ugly what?
What do I look like?
Come back here! Move!
What did you say to me?
- You tiny little dwarf
- What? Dwarf?
I'm sorry, I was the Treasurer
This is all my fault
It's not
It's not your fault, don't worry
Do we have to have money?
Of course we need somewhere
to sleep at night
Can't we just go to a hotel
and send them the money later?
This is the internet cafe...
Hi! Jeong-hun!
Are you all right?
Yes, that's right... In Gangwon province
My parents don't know yet
You will?
Thanks, boss
See you
Are you sure we can trust him?
We can trust him, he knows Yeong-ae too
That's good... but do you think...
It's fine, don't worry
What I mean is...
Mr. Park, I need to ask about your son
You took him to the station...
Did you have an arrest warrant?
Taking someone without a warrant
Questioning by force.
Isn't that illegal?
That's right
Conducting an investigation
without court consent...
This is your son's camera
He visited the internet cafe everyday
He took photos of her in hiding
Take a look for yourself
- Your point being...?
- He was stalking her
And that makes him a criminal?
He ran while being investigated
Of course we're suspicious of him
Those photos...
Do you have any proof
that my son took them?
Jeong-hun!
- Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm okay
I heard you ran from the police
They came to see me
It just sort of happened...
but we're innocent
We're going to stay on the run
until they find the real murderer
Are they your friends?
Boss
- You believe me, right?
- Of course I believe you
Yeong-ae and I weren't even close
Why would I kill her?
Yes... I know that. This is unfortunate
It's not fair...
The police won't even listen
It's just a case of bad luck
The truth will be revealed
- Don't worry about it
- Thank you
It's not much
How can I thank you?
There's no need for that
I should get back to Seoul
before the police visit again
Take care of yourselves
Stay here tonight
Thanks, boss
Cheers!
I needed a good drink
You eat a lot for your size
Now that we're full... what's next?
We have no plans. Just go with the flow
Let's stay here tonight, and tomorrow...
What do we do tomorrow?
It's not good to stay
in one place too long
That's the first rule for runaways
Keep moving
- Where should we go?
- How about the beach?
Good idea! I haven't been in ages
- I've never been
- You're joking!
- I'm not
- Are you Mongolian?
All Koreans have been to
the beach at least once
You both think everyone's like you
Never been to the beach
Never owned an MP3 player
Can't even eat 3 meals a day
There are a lot of kids like that
You can't even imagine it, right?
Let's go to the beach then
What else? What do you want to do?
Go to sea, get on a boat...
Pose like the scene in 'Titanic'
I have no thoughts about my life
You must have plans for the future
I have no plans at all
You're only 19. You have no dreams?
Dreams...? I don't know
Number 13, do you?
I have so many plans
English at 10am, math at 12:30pm
then TOEFL in the evening
University,
study abroad then get my MBA and...
You're giving me a headache
Tell us what your dreams are
Well... I want to go to sea
You haven't been to sea as well?
You haven't been on a boat?
I've been on a cruise, on a big ship
Then why do you want to go to sea?
To go fishing?
No I want to...
Do this too
Hey! Number 13! You're naughty!
What about it? I don't get it
What is it?
- It's a rap battle!
- They're all pretty good
Okay, stop there How was it?
Did you enjoy it?
Yes!
- Are you all having fun?
- Yes!
Who will be our winner?
If you liked this person, clap now!
Should I call for back-up?
Why don't we just bring in a SWAT
team to take out 3 kids?
$1,000 is up for grabs!
You rapped before, you're good
I'm not good
Here! My friend's going!
We have a challenger,
- give him a clap
- Hurry up, go
Come on out!
Go back study, get out of here
Go to your parents, ask for money
Get out, get out yeah
come on~ come on~
Close your mouth, watch your words
You stand here but you're nothing
Listen up, listen carefully
You rap just like a broken car
Listen up, listen to my rap
I don't know you, your broken dreams
I don't know where I'm headed
Don't think you know me, you don't
Look at your expressions now
Big Bang, I've got what it takes
This mic, this stage is all mine
Don't make fun of me, it's not new
Try to make me cry if you can
Come on, is this the best you can do?
You'll regret having challenged me
Everybody tries to imitate me
I'm upset, I'm unhappy, bang bang
Worship my brother, my parents...
Why did he stop?
It's them!
- Isn't that them?
- I think you're right
- Let's go!
- Hurry up, go
How long will you keep running?
If you're innocent, come out!
Come out and tell us
What happened the day Yeong-ae died
Tell me why you took photos of her
Why did you stalk her?
Listen up
I'm going to get you kids
I don't care what it takes
Tell us the truth
About Yeong-ae's photos, stalking her
He was talking to you
Tell us
Don't talk like that... you're not a cop
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry about?
The truth is... I watched her secretly
- Why would you do that?
- She was so pretty...
but I couldn't talk to her
I didn't mean any harm
What you did is harmful
That's what stalkers and perverts do
Don't be so harsh on him
Aren't you angry?
He's been lying all this time
She's got nothing to do with me
I don't even remember her face
You don't remember her face?
I actually believed you
- I'm sorry
- Stop pretending
Acting helpless, as though
you know nothing
- What I mean is...
- Don't say anything
I can't trust you. Did you kill her?
- What?
- Stop it, that's enough
Are you all right? Where are you now?
We're fine, heading towards Sokcho
Am I doing the right thing?
You should cooperate with the police
Please promise me one thing
What is it?
They may be criminals,
but they're good kids
Please don't harm them
Don't worry about that
Let's go
Good bye
I've divided the money up evenly
Let's split up now
- Do we have to?
- Yes, I've had enough
You wanted to run away together
I changed my mind, I'll travel alone
We're not going on a boat?
Why don't the 2 of you go?
You look good together anyway
What are you going on about?
I don't know your names,
I'll probably never see you again
Have a good life then
He's so stupid
I'm sorry
Stop saying you're sorry
I should have told the truth
I didn't think you would believe me
- I'm really sorry
- Stop saying that!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
How many times have you said that?
Sorry Oh, sorry... oops
I'm going too
A girl I know died
I've been mucking around like this
I wasn't thinking straight
I'm going
I am thinking about the future
Not hard enough
You've started on the path to failure
Find a way to make up for it
They pay to send you to
school and you skip classes
You go to clubs, hook up with girls
How old are you?
Is something wrong? Tell me!
I'm asking you out on a date
I liked you from the beginning
You have to protect me...
promise
You promised to protect me
You didn't come with your parents?
No.
Please don't tell them I came
As you wish
Hello? Hello?
It's you! Min-seo! Are you all right?
Where are you now?
- Are you hurt?
- I'm fine, Mom
Is father angry with me?
He's worried sick about you...
Are you sure you're not hurt?
Listen to me carefully
You can't come home,
don't even come near here
If the press finds out,
it will be a huge mess
Our lawyer will handle things
You just do as you're told
Let me speak to him
He'll call you soon, hang up now
Don't hang up, let me speak...
Do you understand me?
- Give me the phone
- Stay out of this
Hello...?
You're busy, don't worry about me
Working on the weekends,
I hope they're paying you well
Everyone wants me to do their hair
Your daughter?
It's all right... I'm eating well
I even ate a whole banana yesterday
Don't worry about me, work hard
Thanks mom
I'll visit soon and bring you treats
Sorry, I have to go now
- Hello...mom? Hello?
- Come in number 13, over
Number 1 ! where are you?
What are you doing?
I came out to the beach for a walk
In my pocket... I found your MP3 player
I don't want you to report me as a thief
Come get your stuff
Here? The beach...
I don't really know where
Tell me where you are
Hurry up!
We're fugitives now
It's dangerous sitting out like that
I'm sorry
- Here, it's yours
- Thank you
It's all right
Where's number 2? In her room?
Were you... in the same room?
We split up just after you left
Why? You like her
What..? I don't like her
I left you alone on purpose
I mean it
You're the one who likes her
Me?
Me? Like her?
Don't say that!
She's not even a girl
She's not my type, you can have her
She's not my type either
I think she hurt her ankle
She sprained it last night
It was swollen this morning
She was limping around before
Do you know where she is?
I think she'll still be around
Probably, her ankle's sore...
Let me go!
Don't touch me!
It's her!
Let me go!
How about a glass of soju?
We're on duty
Your necklace... isn't it for women?
You must have strange taste
It belonged to my wife
I proposed to her with this
I never bought her a proper gift
Your wife was beaten by teenagers...
Do you think it's silly that I'm
chasing after those kids?
Of course not
You probably think I'm trying
to get my revenge
I don't think that
- Don't lie to me
- I'm not
- Have you finished?
- Yes
It's a small town.
We'll find them in internet cafes,
saunas in no time
We're going to search
for them all night?
We're not here to relax at the beach
The stars look like they'll fall down
They feel so much closer than in Seoul
I wanted to be an astronomer
when I was young
I wanted to be an astronaut
We had a lot of dreams
when we were young, right?
I used to look at the stars more often
Sky, universe, stars
Sea, wind, trees, grass
What are you doing? What's he up to?
Leave him, he's listening to music...
Look! Did you see it?
Sure... a shooting star
Number 13, did you see?
What are you doing?
- What are you listening to?
- Why? what happened?
A shooting star. You didn't see it?
What are you listening to?
- It's a song I made
- You wrote it?
You write songs? Let me listen
You're such a mystery
I can't hear... what is it?
It's just the instrumental track
- Sing it for us
- Let's listen to it live
- It's not very good
- Come on, let us hear it
- It's not finished yet
- Sing it! Please?
Are you all right, is everything okay
You left without a trace...
to another world
After time passes and I'm born again
I'll tell you that I love you first
All the things I wanted to say
I'll confess my love to you
The one person that I've loved
If we're able to meet tomorrow
Greet me with a smile
Tell me you've been well
You're the only one for me
I miss you so much
I'm brave enough to tell you now
I've always wanted to say this
I love you
We had a bad run
Nothing serious, but she's hurt
It's not broken, but it hurts
Sure. An X-ray would help
I don't think I can go there...
I'll send someone else
Can you tell me where you are?
Let me get a pen
You're at a temple
I know where it is
Sorry to interrupt you both
Don't overreact.
He was tying his handkerchief
around my ankle
You carry a handkerchief?
You're so weird
Here, for your ankle
I could do it myself
Just say thanks, be cute
Guys like cute girls
I know I'm not cute
- No, you're really cute
- Don't say that out of pity
I mean it
Look at you throwing
pick-up lines at her
Give me your handkerchief again
I put a patch on it for you
The yellow looks ugly,
plus it won't fall off with
the handkerchief over it
You're going to cover my ugly
patch with his handkerchief?
Stop it Give it to me then
What's this?
- The work of a stalker?
- Give it to me
Don't look at them
- It's Yeong-ae
- Let me see...it is her
I'm not a pervert
The photos turned out nice
I was going to give them to her later
I feel sorry for her
Actually... I've been hiding something
I said I didn't know
why she needed money
She told me when we met
I need money to attend acting school
I told him I wanted to break up
after I got the part
He told me to pay back every cent
Or he'll tell everyone about us
Don't ask me for money
It's your problem, you handle it
I wouldn't ask unless I was desperate
Please help me This is
going to be my big break
It's my dream! I want to achieve it
They're your dreams, not mine
Eun-yeong, please
I shouldn't have been so cold
It's not your fault
Don't blame yourself
Wait... look at this
I think it's him
Isn't this your boss?
What did you say?
- Look at this photo
- Show me... it is him!
I didn't notice before
but he's behind her in
all of these photos
That is his car
Why would she get in his car?
Hang on...
He's married
Then the man you
said Yeong-ae...
The married guy!
It can't be...
I just talked to him
on the phone
After he came to the resort...
Right! The detectives came then!
How would they have known unless...
My boss isn't like that!
They were here until just now
They can't be far then. Give me the keys
Actually...
I have something to confess
What is it?
I told you there was nothing
between Yeong-ae and me
- We kissed
- What?
But nothing else happened
Don't you think it's strange?
Why would she go out with you?
I'm telling the truth
She kissed me first
What's wrong?
You don't believe me?
It's not that...
I think she wanted money from you
I think so too
She kissed me to ask me for money?
And she asked you to protect her
She just wanted money,
but guys could get the wrong idea
She didn't say anything about money
You didn't give her the chance,
or she missed the right timing
Timing?
See you tomorrow!
Forget it, I got tricked
She wasn't all that
great anyway
She wasn't? She was great
when you kissed her
But now she's not all that
- That's not what I said
- Do you regret it now?
I don't regret it. I've got
nothing to do with her
What about you?
Your friend begged you for money
but you refused... do you regret that?
No, I could've been nicer
but it was the right thing
to do in my situation
I regret it
I took photos secretly and
never spoke to her
I don't know what she was like,
what problems she faced
If I'd been brave enough to tell
her how pretty she was...
Or tell her how much I liked her
It's not really that difficult
Of course...
It's unfortunate that she
met men for their money
But she did that to
chase her dream
At least she had
a dream for herself
Me...?
I just did as I was told,
I didn't know what I really wanted
I never thought about it
I regret that
I only thought about money...
not about my dreams
I'm the worst here
I never thought about anything...
I just wasted time
It's sad
We didn't kill her but we didn't
help save her either
We should do something
Let's meet that man
He's the one responsible
He's not like that
He wouldn't kill someone
He told the police where we were
You don't know that.
They could have tracked our cell phones
It happened twice You called
him this morning too
It's just co-incidence
It isn't a co-incidence
Don't you get it?
- Don't get so worked up
- Aren't you mad?
He's a dirty man playing
around with a young girl
- You can't prove that
- Didn't you see the photos?
We know he threatened Yeong-ae
He's capable of killing her
My boss wouldn't kill anyone
He's never acted strange
around her Not even once
You're here.
Could you help
Yeong-ae clean up?
Yeong-ae...
Take this with you
Yeong-ae was
usually so bright
But...she looked
so sad that day
It must be him
The police might be waiting there
If we get caught again
We have to tell them the truth
They didn't believe us when
we tried to tell them before
Stop right there
There's nowhere for you to run
Stop!
Don't come any closer, we'll jump
We mean it, we'll jump
You don't want us to die, do you?
Come over here, don't be silly
Jump if you're game enough
Don't say that
Did you hear what he said?
He was rude from the moment we met
- Don't think we won't jump!
- Fine, we'll wait
Don't take too long to decide
What if they really jump...
Trust me, they won't
- I think I can jump
- What?
- You mean it?
- Why not? we're 19
I'm game enough
I don't think they're joking
Don't fall for their tricks
Are you going to take responsibility?
Sure, I'll take the blame
We'll be together, even in heaven
I don't want to get fired
Go on, jump. Do it.
Wait, don't!
We'll let you go. We'll let you go
We're not letting them go
- They left the keys in the car
- Do you have a license?
You can acquire a license
when you're 18 but...
You still need parent
permission to buy a car
We can vote for a member of parliament
but we can't vote against policies
We're adults but still children
What do people want from us?
This is all for your own good
You know I'm on your side, right?
Welcome
- Is the boss in?
- He's gone out
Follow me
Hello
What are you doing here?
I thought you were
in Gangwon province
Did you come on your own?
Yeong-ae...
What?
Did you really go out with her?
What are you talking about?
Yeong-ae told me
she was seeing a man
I don't believe this
Why do you think it's me?
She said he was married
Am I the only married man?
There are thousands of them!
What's this?
What is all this? So what?
It's nothing! This is nothing.
What is this!
We can print those photos again
I helped you run from the police
This is how you repay me?
- Why did you do that to her?
- What did I do?
I don't believe this, Jeong-hun
How could you accuse me?
You pay me back every last cent
of the money I gave you
You got that?
Yeong-ae told me
That man...
That married man told her
To pay back every last cent
Exactly what you just said
I really looked up to you
No-one favored me at home or at school
But I worked hard for you
You trusted me... I was grateful
Why did you do it?
Tell me
Tell me the truth
I never forced her to see me
I was just joking around
I asked her on a date
She said she would
go out with me
if I paid for her acting classes
I have a family
It started off as a fling
But the more I met her...
I ended up falling for her
- Then why did you kill her?
- I didn't kill her!
It's late, you didn't answer my calls
Is something wrong?
Tell me what's wrong
I don't want to see you anymore
- This isn't right, I'm sorry
- We've been through this
Thank you for helping me out
- What?
- I'm sorry
Fine, pay me back my money then
Every last cent of my money
I'll pay once I start earning money
- Pay me right now!
- I don't have it
I'll pay you when I can
You're so stingy
Yeong-ae, don't leave me, I like you
Get off me, let me go
Wait! Yeong-ae!
What are you doing?
Be careful!
- Let go
- Listen to me, please
- Let go!
- Yeong-ae!
Get off me! Let me go!
Yeong-ae!
It was an accident
You killed her
No! I didn't mean to kill her
Stop making excuses!
You destroyed her dreams
- You ruined her
- It's not my fault
- You took her life
- I didn't
Stop
Stop it
That's enough
You need to come to the station too
Why? You've got your criminal
We haven't done anything wrong
Running off during investigation
is intrusion of public duty
Jumping off the roof
was intrusion of public
order and blackmail
You stole my car
Do you even have a license?
Driving without a license too
And so ourjourney ended
The dead were silent
and so were we
The heartless city...
only the city lights quivered
silently in the darkness
I met Yeong-ae in my dreams that night
I'm sorry
For what?
For kissing you even though
I didn't really like you
You're nice and good to girls
I thought you would help me
I'm sorry I couldn't help you
It's not your fault
I shouldn't have approached you
Were you mad at me?
It's all right...
I actually enjoyed the kiss
Did you?
Goodbye
Please forgive me
Are you going
to forgive me?
I said I was sorry, forgive me...
Go buy me a pair of socks
Sure thing
White ones? Black ones?
- Here
- I'll get the black ones
I've lived a hard life, you know that
That's why I hated kids
who think life is easy
Can I take a shower?
Me too. I need to wash my hair
When's our trial?
Trial? why would you go to trial?
- Get out of here
- What?
Breathe in the fresh air!
It feels like we got back
from a long trip
I don't want to go home but
Are you scared? Mama boy
- Don't call me that
- Are you a big boy now?
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes, hello
Don't look so happy
we let you go
What you did was wrong
We're so busy that we don't
have time to waste on you
- Excuse me?
- Anyway, thank you
You tried to find out the truth...
It was quite brave of you
Thank you
What happened was unfortunate
But think of it as good experience
It will end up being...
what's the word...?
Beneficial?
An ironic fate? That's not it either
- Take care of yourselves
- Goodbye
I almost forgot to tell you this
I was 19 once too
Nineteen
Like the warm summer sunlight...
The age of nineteen won't last
There's nothing. We can do to stop time
Let's go
We need to find new direction
and follow the light to our futures
I didn't tell you before
My name's Cha Eun-yeong
I'm Seo Jeong-hun
I'm Park Min-seo... I'm 19 years old
Subrip: easytobeaman
I had a crazy dream one of a kind
It rained in my dream
The sun's so hot out here,
but it's hotter on the other side
Will tomorrow come? Ready or not
My dream's to be born to a writer
Whoever is weak can be
strong by working out
Beef up your soul with visuals
Drive, keep watching the side mirror
I'm always wandering around
with my big eyes, I'm an animal
Sometimes I've wasted my youth
I've leant on you, I'm sorry
Sometimes things come back to me
The streets are empty,
I want to be like those
couples walking around
I don't want to be alone
The nights are lonely
Today, tomorrow I'm all alone
I'm wiping my tears
Shine the light on my childhood dream
Back then, I sat splashing
along the water
I don't know how I'll end up
I have nowhere to wish
Nowhere to turn to
I'll regret this someday
I don't know how I'll end up
I have nowhere to wish
Nowhere to turn to
I'll regret this someday
Let's go higher than TOP
Standing in this endless tunnel
This is enough for me
Holding my gaze, family
I have my family, friends
I've got everything I need
If they don't understand
I close my mouth and walk on
I'm a burden on myself
I don't know the solution
People always asking, it hurts
Makes me lose confidence
and hurts my heart
Sometimes things come back to me
The streets are empty,
I want to be like those
couples walking around
I don't want to be alone
The nights are lonely
Today, tomorrow I'm all alone
I'm wiping my tears
Shine the light on my childhood dream
Back then, I sat splashing
along the water
Why, I don't know why but I feel lost
I'm still wandering Today and tomorrow
Because of me
I still have time left
I'm grateful for time
I'll work things out for me
I don't want to be alone
The nights are lonely
Today, tomorrow I'm all alone
I'm wiping my tears
Shine the light on my childhood dream
Back then, I sat splashing
along the water
I don't know how I'll end up
I have nowhere to wish
Nowhere to turn to
I'll regret this someday
I don't know how I'll end up
I have nowhere to wish
Nowhere to turn to
I'll regret this someday