Subtitles by EroJapanese.com
Copyright 2016
At one luxury sex shop in Tokyo
Today, Natsume Iroha will perform various services
catering to to the special tastes of her clients.
Various cosplays and role-playing scenes
will be documented as they occur.
The famous Natsume Iroha will face un-rehearsed situations...
What will happen from this point on...?
Well, we won't keep you waiting...
Let the show begin!
Hello everyone!
I'm Natsume Iroha.
Today,
I'll be doing an
"erotic cosplay massage"
together with
all of you.
Well,
I don't have much experience in this but,
um, well...
when you say "erotic"
it really depends on what a person considers so,
and what's in that person's "list"
we want to, at least, realize those fantasies.
Let's start with the first one.
"Suddenly doing it with a stranger..."
This is really erotic somehow...
I haven't really done it so I'm a little uneasy but,
well, we use stuff like this as well, huh.
I wonder if I can do it...
I think it'll be a little embarrassing but
it's interesting...
to at least try... That's what I think.
So, I'll do my best.
What kind of massage do you like?
Me, well...
Um...
I don't really know what kind is considered "good" and...
well, I'll be doing
the "erotic massage" this time so,
I thought I should see how this "new" me would turn out.
I'll do my best!
Course 1
Pussy Rub and Hand Job
First, Iroha will be giving her partner a normal massage.
Today,
our first client is
a typical male.
Our services will include
a hand job, pussy rub and massage.
Um...
I'm feeling a little nervous all of a sudden...
about our male client...
But I'll do my best!
I'm in your hands.
Today, I'll be the one in charge of you. My name's Natsume.
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
Yes, nice to meet you too.
Excuse me.
That part...
- Here?
- Yes, that feels good.
- Is this ok?
Feels good... you're good at this...
Ah, thank you very much.
Um, it's a bit...
Is this really ok?
Ah... amazing...
Yeah, you really are good. It feels good.
That's good to hear.
Somehow...
I...
- It's actually my first time...
- Ah, is that so?
- I see.
- This kind of massage is...
- ...not really my specialty.
- Ah, really?
But you're good for a beginner.
- Yes.
Thank you very much.
This part's really tight.
True. Well, I do use it a lot.
So you use a lot of physical strength.
Ah, yes, probably.
Your muscles are amazing.
Ah, really?
Well, um...
- I'm not really good at this part...
- I see.
- So, can you face up?
- Ah, yeah, sure.
- Ok, will do.
- Ah, sorry.
Huh?!
Ms. Natsume...? That's...
Huh? Are you "that" Natsume...?
- Huh? Ah, you're Natsume Iroha, right?
Your screen name? - Y-Yes.
Huh? Huh?! Um...
Is it really ok to be doing this?
Ah, it's totally fine.
- Then... - Yes...
- Please continue...
- On my back right?
- Yes, on your back please.
- Here I go...
- Ok...
I'm ready.
- I'm in your hands.
- Well, now...
- I'm gonna do this part...
- Yes...
This part is my specialty so...
- This part...?
- Yes.
Huh? Eh, ah, is it ok to be doing this?
If yes, then by all means!
- Yes, I''m also in your hands.
- Ok, let's do this.
Is this ok?
Your fingers...
They're amazing...
Ah... shit... ah, that part...
Amazing...
I can see
how pretty your fingers look even with gloves...
Really?
Really.
That makes me happy.
Your fingers are really slender...
You have really beautiful fingers...
Thank you very much.
So good...
Is it ok getting hard like this?
If it makes you feel good, then please do so...
I'll happily comply.
It feels really good.
That feels...
- This part?
- Ah... that feels good...
What nice looking fingers...
Nice fingers...
Seriously... the way you do it is so... amazing...
Shit...
I hope this makes you feel really good...
Thanks a lot...
- Whoa... that feels really good...
- Ah, really...?
Feels good...
Can you do this kind of thing as well...?
Then, by all means...
Yes.
- Is this fine?
- Yes.
Feels good...
I can feel it hitting the spot...
Well...
Sir...
The harder it is...
The better it feels...
Right?
Ah... feels good...
Feels good...
Ah... it's piling up...
Amazing...
Can I move faster...?
Yes, you can...
Feels good...
Feels better when it's harder...
I'm so sorry...
I felt really good just now...
Me too...
Please feel really good...
Looks like
something came out...
Does this feel good?
It does...
Something came out, huh?
Yes, you did.
- You did release quite a bit of this...
- What came out?
Huh? What do you think it is?
I don't know...
Please tell me.
The "really-felt-good" juice came out.
So the  "really-felt-good" juice came out, huh...
Yes, it did.
That's a good thing.
Because it really felt good.
A lot came out actually...
Feels good...
- Does it feel good?
- It feels really good.
Until I cum...
Yes, please feel really, really good.
A lot's coming out...
It's throbbing hard...
Does it feel good?
Feels really good.
Ah, feels so good...
It feels good to the point where
a lot of juice is coming out...
Please... don't say that or else I'll... ah...
Amazing...
Ah, oh, no, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming... cumming...
Ah cumming! Ah cumming... ah!
Cumming...!
Ah...
Cumming...
Looks like you came a lot...
A lot...
Looks like...
Huh?
You're gonna cum again...
- Huh?! No way...
- But you look like you're about to...
But it's fine... ah... cumming again...
It feels good... amazing...
Cumming again... please stop...
Ah, that feels too good...
- Are you about to cum again?
- I'm about to cum again!
Course 2
Lotion, Mat and Soap Role-play
Challenge to play using a slippery lotion!
Our next client is
um, he's a bit of a masochist.
Services will include...
a full body lotion massage...
and...
another option is...
doing it raw.
Um...
I'll do my best with this "lotion role-play!"
Yes.
Welcome!
Ah, hello.
- Today, I'm in your hands.
- Ah, same here.
- Um...
- You're... Ms. Natsume, right?
Yes, I'm Natsume Iroha.
Ah, um...
Are you good at this?
Well, a bit I guess...
- Ah...
- Yes, today...
Please take it easy and don't hold back...
If you do that, I'll be very pleased.
I feel nervous all of a sudden.
- I'm in your hands.
- I'm in your hands too.
- Then, please come this way.
- Ah, yes.
- Please stand right here...
- Yes...
- And we'll have you in that position for a bit...
- Yes.
Is this really your specialty?
- I never thought you'd be the one doing this.
- Ah, really?
- Yes... ah, sorry.
- Can you take it off? - Yes.
- I'll be glad to.
- Ah, that makes me happy.
Thank you very much.
Whoa...
I-Is this for real?
Yes, probably.
- Probably...?
- It's probably the real thing.
Ok...
Then...
Can we take this off too...?
Ah, yes...
Ah, it's a bit...
- Is it fine?
- Yes.
- Excuse me...
- Yes...
- Ah... it's...
Kinda embarrassing...
- You're really hiding it.
- Yes...
Let's fold this nicely...
Ok...
Ah...
- Now we'll start.
- Please go ahead.
- I'll start.
- Yes.
I'm putting some of this...
- Ah, it's my first time with this type of thing...
- Ah, it's your first time? - Yes.
Somehow it feels...
...really good when you do it.
That...
- Saying it like that makes me feel embarrassed...
- No, really...
I mean, I never thought this would happen...
Well, neither did I actually...
- Does it feel good?
- Yes...
Mmm...
Can I put some on your hand?
Whoa...
I can feel it...
Ah...
More...
Hm?
I'm putting it in.
Ah, is that ok?
- Can you feel it getting harder?
- Yes.
- Can I put some more?
Excuse me...
Are you ok?
- Yes.
- Ok...
- Thank you very much...
- Yes...
I feel like just by you doing that
I'm about to cum already.
I'm gonna move now.
Is this fine? This pace.
- You can feel it in your hand, huh?
- Yes.
Here...
Ah, it's starting to feel really good.
Yes.
Then...
Yes...
Ok, now...
Ok...
Is this ok...?
Ah, yes.
Ah, amazing...
- Is this ok?
- Ah... it's amazing...
- Does it feel good?
- Yes.
It feels so good...
Does it hurt anywhere?
Um... ah...
I'm totally fine.
- Are you ok?
- Yes.
You sure?
I think there's one spot that's in pain...
- Eh?
- Eh?!
- You got bigger again...
- Ah, yes...
I-It just got harder...
Ah, what am I gonna do...
I got really hard.
- Did that feel good just now?
- Yes.
It's gotten bigger.
- It got bigger, huh?
- Yes...
Ah... that feels really good.
Feels good...
Ah... that's dangerously good...
Is it dangerously good?
It's throbbing hard.
- Really tight, huh?
- Yes.
That's a bit...
Here you go...
Did it pile up?
Yes...
Ah... feels good...
Good...
Is it too much?
Ah... so good...
Tell me if there's anything you don't like, ok?
Ah, yes...
Just by doing that is enough to make me cum...
- Does it feel good?
- Yes.
It's throbbing hard.
It's because you're really good at this.
Please relax and feel really, really good, ok?
Ah, yes...
Then...
- Yes...
- Now, let's do it from here...
W-What are you doing...?
- Is this ok?
- Ah, it's f-fine...
Ah, my dick just got harder.
- Are you ok?
- Yes.
C-Can I lick your ass?
- Do you want to?
- I want to lick your ass, please.
Can you make me feel good as well...?
Can you make feel good too...?
Is this part ok?
- Is that fine?
- Whoa...
What a beautiful pussy...
Can I lick it...?
Ah... please make me feel even more good...
Yes...
- Does it feel good?
- Yes.
It's good...
You’re very good at this.
Ah... that's good...
A-Are you ok?
I just feel really good...
Ah...
Let's change position...
Now...
Yes...
- Then...
- Yes...?
We'll do it raw...
Ah, is it really ok, doing it raw?
- Well, I'll have you show me that.
- Ah, how...?
Yes... ah, what am I gonna do...
- Is this ok?
- Ah, yes.
Does it feel good?
I'm sure this will feel real good.
Ok, here I go.
Ah, it's in.
Ok.
Awesome... your pussy's so warm...
- It's so warm and feels good, right?
- Yes.
Ok...
- It's in...
- Yes, it feels good...
Awesome...
Ah... it's so warm, huh...
It's really going in...
It's going all the way in...
Whoa... what a lewd position...
Can you see it?
Ms. Natsume...
Ah...
I wanna see your ass too...
My ass...?
Amazing...
Feels good...
I can't take it anymore...
It can't be helped... can't be helped...
Ah... from behind...
Ah... amazing...
Ah... no...
Feels really good...
Is this ok...?
Are you feeling good?
Yes...
Good... please feel even more better...
Ah, shit...
It's going in...
Then next...
- Please go on top...
- Yes...
Ah... amazing...
Ah... oh, no...
Ah... gonna cum...
Ah... no...
Ah... wait...
I came...
Inside...?
Sir...
It felt so good...
- You came... you said you came...
- It was...
You did came...
Sir...
I-I'm really sorry...
Cumming inside me
- was definitely not an option.
- Ah, I'm so sorry.
It felt really good and I couldn't help it...
Um...
Are you ok?
Yes...
I didn't think your pussy would feel this good...
Really...?
It was an excellent experience.
Thank you very much.
Until next time.
I'm sorry.
Sorry...
I'm looking forward to
the next part.
Course 3
Masochistic Role-play
It's about time to get more serious,
so this next "service" will be more challenging!
The next client will be getting
an M service,
M (masochistic),
feet job,
blow job,
Verbal abuse.
I haven't done much of that but...
I'll do my best!
You again...?
I came again.
So the last time wasn't enough?
No, no, I just wanted more.
- You wanted more?
- Yes.
- But today, - Yes...
- I won't give you any of that so do it yourself.
- Ah, please do it...
- No.
Please.
- You can't ask me that.
- Huh?
- Please.
- Do it yourself.
- Eh...?
- Then, can you lay down there?
Ah, ok.
H-Here?
- You like this, right?
- Yes...
Doesn't this make you horny?
Ah...
Let's see...
Ah... feels good...
- You're getting harder, huh...
- Yes...
What a shameful cock you have...
Yes it is...
Can I take this off?
- You wanna take that off?
- Yes.
- Can I?
- You want direct contact? - Yes.
Please touch me directly.
Ok.
Getting horny like this... embarrassing...
Ah, yes...
I'm sorry about that.
Ah, that's... ah...
That's good... that's... please keep doing that.
Come here.
Yes.
That's so erotic.
You'll be licking me down there.
Ah... yes... of course.
Make me feel good...
Ah, yes.
Your pussy tastes good.
More.
Lick me a lot.
Yes.
Now...
Yes...
- As a reward,
- Yes.
what do you want me to do?
I want you to give me a blow job...
- Blow job?
- Yes.
- Like this?
Thank you very much.
Please lick it all the way.
Ah...
Ah, I think my mind's gonna explode...
I'm about to cum...
Ah, wait...
Ah, wait, ah... I'm about to...
Ah... ah... wait...
You can't just cum when you want to.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry Teacher.
Next time, you can't.
Ah.
Just make sure...
- Yes.
- that you don't cum easily.
Yes.
- I'll be careful.
- Ok then.
It's throbbing hard.
Hm?
What do you want me to do?
Just a bit...
Please lick my balls too.
- Your balls?
- Yes.
Ah... amazing...
God...
Ah, that feels good.
I'm hitting the spot.
Yes...
Even my hips are moving...
It feels that good...
Please...
Please make me feel real good...
That's it...
Ah... that's it...
Ah... I'm gonna cum...
I came...
Again you...
...came without warning.
I-I'm sorry.
And a lot too.
Did I cum a lot?
H-How is it... my cum?
Hm?
How?
Yes.
It's... it's...
Disgusting.
I'm sorry for that.
Course 4
Blindfold-imagination Role-play
Featuring a blindfolded AV actor
Um, our next...
client is...
a typical male.
Um...
The service will include
Image...
Imagination and...
blindfold role-play.
Um...
While blindfolded, I'll be waiting for the client,
and until he's satisfied, I'll do my very best.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
It can't be...
I mean, you're blindfolded but...
You're Natsume... Iroha, right?
Yes.
That's right.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Is it really...
...fine to do anything...?
Role-playing, I mean.
Yes.
Anything.
Really? Then...
Ok...
Pleasure my dick.
Huh?
Eat...?
Please.
- But.
- Can you do it?
Um...
First, let's...
Um, this is role-playing, right?
- Um...
- This is actually pretty basic.
- Basic?
- Yes.
Basic...
Huh?
It touched me.
You can touch it if you want to.
Huh?
Is this really... huh?
Like this?
Servicing
cocks is...
...basic.
Is that so?
I can't see it so...
- Can you... - Yes?
- lift your lips so I can see it?
Up?
My lips...
Even if you're blindfolded,
I want to see clearly...
how beautiful you are.
I'm embarrassed.
Thank you very much.
Ah... that feels good.
Please let me see your face.
- My face...?
- Yes.
Faster...
You're servicing dicks you know.
S-Servicing?
Yes.
Eh?
Hm.
What did you say?
Yes, it's not going in.
Where do you like it?
Ah, that's it.
Hm? Ah...
That feels really good.
There...
Your nipples are hard...
They are...
- Can you... - Hm?
- ...suck it all the way in?
That's it.
That's so lewd...
That feels really good...
Is it your first time servicing dicks?
Yes.
Feels good...
I can't take it anymore...
Getting all wet like that...
You're actually a pervert, right?
Your nipples are getting bigger...
Next...
Can I lick your beautiful legs?
That tickles...
The part I want to lick most...
is this part...
I'll lick it a lot ok?
I'll make sure
to lick you a lot too...
No...
Wait...
Huh? What's the matter?
Amazing...
- Embarrassing...
- I'll spread it even wider...
- I got to see it...
- No...
It's very beautiful.
Ms. Natsume, everything about you is beautiful.
That's embarrassing...
Huh?
It really is beautiful.
Look...
Thank you very much... ah...
Ah... tickles...
It tickles a bit...
Ah, then, I'm not doing it right after all.
Ah...
It's really delicious.
Please let me see it.
Huh?
All of this...
These beautiful legs...
Keep them spread open...
That's it...
Like this...
I can lick you for hours...
Your clit's getting bigger too.
Ah... don't look at it too much...
Huh?
Is it bad?
How about this?
How does this feel?
Ms. Natsume... this sound...
What is this?
I don't know...
You don't know?
It's the sound of...
Ms. Natsume's pussy.
Here.
This part.
Amazing...
Going in this deep...
It's really warm inside.
Amazing.
This part...
is so messy...
So wet...
Amazing...
My finger goes right in...
This part...
- This part...
- Huh?
Ah...
Huh?
That's it... more...
Please lick it.
That's it.
That's it...
What long legs you have...
This is good.
Suck on it like a lollipop...
I'm hitting your spot...
You're really good at this...
Ah... you're all wet and messy.
More...
I'll finger you more...
Right here...
What are you doing?
Hm?
Ah... ah... stop...
How was it?
So you don't want me...
to use my finger?
Am I wrong?
Would you let me do this?
What?
I'm putting it in...
Here...
This is not a finger.
I want to put it in.
Here...
It's in...
Ah... wait...
Your smile...
Even if you're blindfolded,
I can feel you smiling.
It’s throbbing.
Feels good...
I'm close...
Before that...
I want to see your face...
Is it ok?
Ah, I'm taking this off...?
This...
Amazing...
You're so beautiful.
Huh? After being blindfolded,
now you're hiding your face?
Amazing...
Can you... show me your face?
Please.
I want to see it.
Your beautiful face.
You really are beautiful.
Which is better, my finger or my dick?
Di...
Please tell me...
Um... this one...
This...?
Saying, "This" isn't enough...
"This" you say...
Dick...
What's making you...
look that way...?
Your cock.
You mean this?
Harder...
I'm gonna fuck you harder...
Next... can I do you from behind?
Behind...
Ah... no matter how you look at it...
It really is beautiful.
- No...
- Ah... this part...
Embarrassing...
Can I stick my tongue in?
Ok...
Amazing...
Do you like it?
Ah... amazing...
I want to ask you to come over here...
Can I... see your face from here too?
My face...
That's it... that's such a turn on...
Ah, no, no...
Amazing...
Open your eyes.
Can you face this way? Ah...
Amazing... I'm hitting the spot...
I’m fucking you so deeply.
This is in the way...
Let's get this off...
Everything...
I want to see everything.
Can you take this off too?
That's it.
Amazing...
Your face...
You're so beautiful...
I wanna lick you...
I can see everything.
I wanna see everything.
No...
You said you prefer my dick over my finger right?
Huh?
Which one?
Huh? Cock?
Cock?
Cock.
Can I fuck you harder?
You're so beautiful...
I'm savoring every bit of you.
From head...
up to your feet.
I wanna see you go crazy with my cock
that you like so much.
Cock...
Please look at my cock.
That's it.
Look at how it goes in and out.
My cock.
In and out...
That feels so good...
Ms. Natsume...
this feels really good...
Let's get crazier...
Is it ok? Let's go crazier.
Ah, no.
I'm about to...
I'm at my limit...
Your extremely...
beautiful...
face...
I want to shoot my cum all over it.
Ah... cumming!
Somehow...
That person...
...wasn't the least bit gentle.
He was really rough.
By any chance,
have you cleaned up yet?
Ah, no...
- Then, let me...
- Ah, no, no...
I didn’t mean to pour my semen...
You poured a lot.
No...
Since it's Ms. Natsume,
even a guy like me would go this far.
You're just talking...
That kind of lines...
- Did you think that was just a line?
- No, no...
But you did cum a lot.
Huh?
I think you're all clean now.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Ah...
I've been tricked.
Course 5
Prostate Massage?!
The last one is a little more difficult!
Will she be able to do it?
Yes. The next client is
Mr. A.
The service includes
the challenging prostate massage.
We'll be doing...
...a prostate massage...?
Wait...
I don't think I can do it...
I've never done this before.
We'll leave it to you!
Wait...
No way...
I'm being forced into this...
I'm your hands.
You were the last client, right?
I'm in your hands.
Ah, wait...
Seriously...
I don't know what to do...
Huh?
You can use this if you want.
No, I can do it on my own... This is a bit...
This looks really intimidating...
It's fine.
Really? You're fine with it?
Please put it in gently.
Yes... but I'm feeling really nervous...
What do I do...
It's vibrating... this is fine right?
Um...
Whoa...
I'll start...
Around or in right away...?
You should do it dirty.
Ah, so that's it... ah, directly...?
I'm putting it in...
Ah, what's wrong?
Is this... fine?
- Well...
- Somehow...
I have no clue...
Ah, I'm scared...
Hm?
Like this?
Like this right?
Ah, you can't do it?
Ah, wait...
Huh?
- It's scary... because it's scary, I...
- Scary?
But... this is really big.
Um, it's normal I think.
Ah, that's...
Well, I think...
even if it goes in...
Um...
- Ah, wait...
- Makes me wanna lick it just to be sure...
- You're not gonna do it?
- Well, it's...
Come, come, come here...
Come here for a bit...
Come on...
- Please sit here for a bit.
- Ah, I can sit...?
Sit here,
- Then...
- Wait a minute!
What's wrong? What's the matter?
Wait...
Like this...
- And this...
- No, I...
- Like this...
- Am I gonna...
Can you show it to us?
This is amazing...
Wait...
Now it's clearly visible.
Wait... How did it come to this...?
No, but we can't...
see it all.
- This goes here...
- No, no, no...
Even you'd say challenging...
This goes here... that's it...
You said you don't know so...
But...
- I did say that but...
- Just a bit more...
Just keep it like this...
Keep it still...
Still...
I can do that.
Huh?
Nice scent...
No, no, I...
It's really beautiful.
Is it hot?
It is.
Wait...
Huh?
Wait a minute...
Huh? What's wrong?
You said you didn't know so...
I did say I didn't know but...
- But...
- I haven't done anything yet.
Somehow...
Yes?
I wanna...
- Wait! Wait a minute...
- Huh? What's wrong?
Ah, you want turn around first?
Ah, sorry, I guess it's better if we do it from behind.
Sorry, I didn't know. Here we go...
- I didn't know that too...
- Huh?
Your ass...
Huh? Ah, wait...
This is it...
Look at that.
This beauty...
Yes, I'll follow you.
Yes...
Ah, should I do it?
Spread your legs... that's it.
Then do this, like earlier...
That position we took earlier...
No, no, I can't...
Wait.
How about this?
I don’t know what would you like so I want to try.
Ok.
Good.
I... fucked you more than this earlier, right?
Yes, you did...
I totally  hammered you from behind.
Can I do something similar again?
Well...
That's...
fine I guess...
Then, let me taste your nether regions...
This is it...
This part...
- You're touching...
- I saw it from the front, so now I want this way.
- Ok.
- So now it’s from the back.
- Ah, not that...
- Ah, this...
This part right here...
No...
What will you think of me?
This...
This part...
Ah, that's...
Is it cold?
Let's confirm it.
Ok, please come closer.
- It's fine, since we'll just test it.
- Test it...
Just gonna run some tests...
That's it...
Can I stick it in?
Huh?
- It's fine... it's really fine.
- Um, that's...
It's fine.
- Ah, but...
- It's fine.
Ah... this is bad...
It's fine.
My ass...
Your hips are moving.
No way.
It's fine.
This right here...
That's a bit...
Let me know if it doesn't feel good...
No...
It’s lewd.
It's only halfway in.
Eh, really?
It popped...
Then... I'll go all the way.
Like this.
Let me stick it in.
If it's like this,
it feels better, right?
Come closer.
That's it.
Like this...
Actually, you want me to go deeper, right?
Eh...
Then, I'll stick it in even further...
Like how I did you earlier...
Ah, that's...
Like this...
Is this pleasurable?
Huh?
Amazing...
Your pussy's burning hot.
It's twitching all over.
Don't tell me...
- I didn't.
- Did you just cum?
Somehow...
I came unexpectedly.
- Unexpectedly...?
- I came unexpectedly.
You came unexpectedly, huh.
- Move this way.
- Ok.
That's it.
Amazing.
Just keep it like that.
Just like that.
Let's do it this way...
This way it won't miss.
Wait, it's...
That's it.
Are you confused?
Here we go...
You came even before I touched you.
You can't cum yet.
Your pussy.
Here we go...
You're glowing.
Glowing...
That's...
You want me to do more?
Then...
For the special part...
No way...
What the...
Wait... I'm gonna break...
Hm?
You're gonna break?
You know, we're not gonna be putting this in...
Is bigger a lot better?
You prefer clit orgasm, huh?
Which of these do you want?
Wait...
I can't...
Ah, what's the matter?
It's going in...
Here we go...
Ah... no... I'm gonna...
Ah... cumming...
So you prefer both after all.
Yes.
Can I see when you come?
Well...
I'll check it.
- Let's open this wider.
- Ah, I'm so embarrassed...
Can you get up for a bit?
That's it...
- Here...
- Yes...
That's it...
Nice shape...
You're all wet and messy down here...
Right?
Look at that.
Ah... a bit...
Huh?
You came, huh?
I came...
No...
Then...
we didn't get to do the prostate at all.
Actually, I wanted to feel good too...
I...
on the other hand, felt really good.
I'm sorry.
But that's good too.
Natsume, you worked hard.
We're looking forward to the next episode.
Subtitles by EroJapanese.com
Copyright 2016