[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: Default Aegisub file
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.45,0:00:39.75,Default,,0,0,0,,武史？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.22,0:00:43.46,Default,,0,0,0,,武史？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.46,0:00:44.06,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.06,0:00:45.96,Default,,0,0,0,,我进来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.03,0:00:50.33,Default,,0,0,0,,啊 好臭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.93,0:00:54.13,Default,,0,0,0,,你偶尔也要打扫下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.43,0:00:55.43,Default,,0,0,0,,再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.74,0:01:01.37,Default,,0,0,0,,惠理子好像不认识我们家迷路了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.74,0:01:03.94,Default,,0,0,0,,你去找找去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.38,0:01:06.95,Default,,0,0,0,,哎？为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.95,0:01:08.81,Default,,0,0,0,,我正学习呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.21,0:01:11.98,Default,,0,0,0,,反正你在家也是一直玩游戏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.98,0:01:15.72,Default,,0,0,0,,看啊 天气这么好 就当散步了 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.99,0:01:18.09,Default,,0,0,0,,妈妈要晒被子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.09,0:01:19.59,Default,,0,0,0,,知道了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.03,0:01:21.59,Default,,0,0,0,,惠理子是哪个惠理子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.79,0:01:24.16,Default,,0,0,0,,认识叫惠理子的不就只有一个人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.16,0:01:26.70,Default,,0,0,0,,妈妈高中时代的好朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.70,0:01:29.23,Default,,0,0,0,,跟妈妈一样 是个大美人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.28,0:01:48.82,Default,,0,0,0,,什么啊 那人我都没印象啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.13,0:01:55.86,Default,,0,0,0,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.13,0:01:56.86,Default,,0,0,0,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.91,0:02:14.85,Default,,0,0,0,,难道说你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.71,0:02:17.28,Default,,0,0,0,,武史君？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.35,0:02:21.29,Default,,0,0,0,,是我没错
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.55,0:02:23.82,Default,,0,0,0,,真的是小武啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.82,0:02:27.06,Default,,0,0,0,,长这么大了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.33,0:02:30.26,Default,,0,0,0,,喂 还记得阿姨吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.20,0:02:34.00,Default,,0,0,0,,不太记得了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.73,0:02:38.40,Default,,0,0,0,,也是啊 那时候你还很小呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.11,0:02:42.81,Default,,0,0,0,,啊 惠理子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.61,0:02:46.98,Default,,0,0,0,,你可来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.05,0:02:48.88,Default,,0,0,0,,芳恵 好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.11,0:02:52.28,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉了 我还是那么路痴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.28,0:02:55.19,Default,,0,0,0,,快进来 快进来 武史你还愣着干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.32,0:02:56.82,Default,,0,0,0,,啊 我来帮你拿行李
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.82,0:02:59.19,Default,,0,0,0,,没关系啦 小武
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.19,0:02:59.96,Default,,0,0,0,,请进 请进
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.46,0:03:02.29,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢你 小武
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.86,0:03:05.40,Default,,0,0,0,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.53,0:03:08.43,Default,,0,0,0,,哇 好漂亮的家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.43,0:03:10.43,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.43,0:03:10.43,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.70,0:03:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.04,0:03:25.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.91,0:03:30.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在正是要考试的重要时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.38,0:03:34.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暂时要麻烦你们照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.45,0:03:36.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.32,0:03:40.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正他很自我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.59,0:03:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在损我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.06,0:03:49.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要我帮你读书
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.07,0:03:52.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.20,0:03:54.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.94,0:03:57.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我受到你们照顾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.81,0:04:02.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我帮得上忙的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.41,0:04:03.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.15,0:04:06.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她以前很会读书喔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.22,0:04:10.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.69,0:04:11.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.62,0:04:15.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托老师了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.24,0:04:28.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仔细看这边数字
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.31,0:04:31.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.31,0:04:33.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.91,0:04:39.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仔细看的话\N难的问题也可以解决
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.52,0:04:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从这边到这边\N用15分钟解题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.58,0:05:40.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.45,0:05:45.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也会用这个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.72,0:05:53.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用在意喔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.12,0:05:55.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,男生都是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.40,0:06:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没做完吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.00,0:06:02.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,继续吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.04,0:06:40.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.51,0:06:44.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.25,0:10:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要考上喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.13,0:21:35.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被你这样舔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.93,0:21:40.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好兴奋喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.94,0:21:45.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真会舔喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.94,0:21:50.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨的小穴好湿喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.68,0:21:54.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.95,0:21:55.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.35,0:21:55.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.78,0:22:27.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来玩弄一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.59,0:22:33.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小穴 阴毛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.12,0:22:33.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小穴 阴毛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.26,0:22:34.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小穴 阴毛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.33,0:22:39.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不够喔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.20,0:22:44.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨最喜欢年轻肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.54,0:22:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来教你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.61,0:22:55.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我舔肉棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.82,0:23:01.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会的话\N要处罚喔
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.02,0:23:03.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.02,0:23:09.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我肉棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.56,0:23:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我肉棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.30,0:23:14.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.96,0:23:17.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨好想要舔
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.67,0:23:55.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.94,0:23:59.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.48,0:24:02.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.55,0:24:14.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.13,0:24:59.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了\N不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.89,0:25:17.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.22,0:25:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.69,0:25:26.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎样了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.36,0:25:29.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.04,0:25:39.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不错哦，都答对了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.24,0:25:41.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲真厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.98,0:25:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快考试了\N要好好睡觉
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.12,0:25:51.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天再加油喔
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.99,0:25:54.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨会帮你的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.53,0:26:03.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,答对了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.80,0:26:05.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.64,0:26:40.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.90,0:26:43.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,努力读书喔
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.65,0:26:58.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这边解看看
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.86,0:27:06.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像无法集中精神
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.00,0:27:10.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.33,0:27:13.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.95,0:27:28.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.09,0:27:31.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有女朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.75,0:27:33.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.56,0:27:39.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为是考生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.23,0:27:46.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然没有
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.37,0:27:51.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样很辛苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.31,0:27:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.85,0:28:05.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.52,0:28:08.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是什么害羞的事
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.99,0:28:13.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,处理性欲的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.26,0:28:17.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新东宝翻译制作\N色花堂 Yamete 商业提取
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.21,0:28:24.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.08,0:28:32.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以喔
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.22,0:28:34.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.89,0:28:46.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.70,0:28:57.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样才是健康的男生
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.11,0:29:07.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.92,0:29:13.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是阿姨的话，还是不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.19,0:29:14.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪有
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.19,0:29:17.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.80,0:29:24.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.61,0:29:39.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果考上的话，我就亲你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.22,0:29:43.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.15,0:29:46.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.09,0:29:51.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.56,0:29:52.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会加油
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.72,0:30:14.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.05,0:30:23.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也很辛苦\N每天在超市打工
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.86,0:30:29.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一个人养大小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.53,0:30:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.74,0:30:36.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老公只留下这房子
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.61,0:30:46.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N自由一点的好
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.55,0:30:51.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你老公很棒，找不到第二个了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.82,0:31:00.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了，小哲今年考得上吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.90,0:31:04.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像状况不错喔
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.23,0:31:06.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.37,0:31:10.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只需要注意 集中精神就好
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.31,0:31:16.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲很容易分心
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.98,0:31:18.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.85,0:31:21.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,整天漫不经心
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.92,0:31:27.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.99,0:31:31.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他也很认真
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.19,0:31:33.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.13,0:31:38.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天多喝一点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.07,0:31:41.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.68,0:32:55.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被看见了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.35,0:33:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一喝酒
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.75,0:33:03.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就受不了噜
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.15,0:33:09.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也会自慰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.36,0:33:13.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女人都会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.90,0:33:18.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是学生的时候也常做
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.25,0:33:34.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.98,0:33:36.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是说要考上再说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.39,0:33:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.20,0:33:51.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经结婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.34,0:33:58.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了和老公做爱之外，只能自慰
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.21,0:34:07.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,继续自慰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.89,0:34:19.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.04,0:34:27.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.58,0:34:43.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要努力读书喔
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.32,0:34:46.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说好了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.46,0:34:50.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会加油
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.73,0:34:54.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.74,0:35:07.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下下喔
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.75,0:35:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以摸喔
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.57,0:35:38.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要再靠近了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.04,0:35:41.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只能用看的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.58,0:35:46.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用看的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.46,0:35:59.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.07,0:36:15.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,专心看喔
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.94,0:36:20.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重要的东西，要仔细看喔
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.84,0:36:51.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以靠近吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.98,0:36:53.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.85,0:36:56.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新东宝翻译制作\N色花堂 Yamete 翻新
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.67,0:37:15.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要太靠近
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.95,0:37:34.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.30,0:37:41.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.64,0:37:55.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要自慰了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.26,0:38:12.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,受不了噜\N小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.60,0:38:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.14,0:38:31.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.15,0:38:36.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.32,0:39:11.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让阿姨看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.50,0:39:58.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好湿喔
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.38,0:40:10.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,摩擦肉棒喔
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.46,0:40:30.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样摩擦着
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.21,0:40:47.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎样了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.30,0:41:03.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以喔
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.43,0:41:06.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以喔\N说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.70,0:41:08.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.84,0:41:11.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想舔
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.71,0:41:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨也忍着的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.65,0:41:20.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.18,0:41:22.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.45,0:41:28.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也很想要舔肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.79,0:41:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好湿
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.87,0:41:41.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.14,0:41:43.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好想舔
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.14,0:41:47.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.01,0:41:51.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.35,0:41:56.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.43,0:42:06.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舔一下
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.10,0:42:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下就好
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.51,0:42:24.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让阿姨舔一下
Dialogue: 0,0:42:26.98,0:42:31.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲一下就好
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.33,0:42:42.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨舔一下喔
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.07,0:42:47.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.14,0:42:50.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.09,0:43:07.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:43:16.90,0:43:17.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.65,0:43:31.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:44:06.28,0:44:07.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.56,0:44:20.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.10,0:44:21.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:44:31.77,0:44:32.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下下喔
Dialogue: 0,0:44:38.71,0:44:40.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舔一下
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.92,0:44:44.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会加油
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.52,0:44:50.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舔一下就好\N还要去读书
Dialogue: 0,0:44:51.93,0:44:53.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:45:02.47,0:45:03.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.24,0:45:43.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.12,0:45:57.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想要舔肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:46:01.60,0:46:02.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:46:15.61,0:46:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.21,0:46:21.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要等到考上
Dialogue: 0,0:46:29.62,0:46:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要等到考上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.63,0:46:36.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:47:03.92,0:47:04.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:47:11.93,0:47:12.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.81,0:47:25.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨只是想要你认真读书
Dialogue: 0,0:47:27.68,0:47:29.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要努力读书
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.19,0:48:15.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.27,0:48:28.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲的肉棒\N好想要
Dialogue: 0,0:49:01.38,0:49:02.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:49:08.58,0:49:10.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:49:13.79,0:49:15.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要忍着喔
Dialogue: 0,0:49:15.92,0:49:17.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍着
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.53,0:49:22.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:49:28.47,0:49:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要等到考上
Dialogue: 0,0:49:33.01,0:49:35.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.68,0:49:40.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨湿了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:21.19,0:50:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:50:35.74,0:50:38.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉我今天喝多了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.41,0:50:43.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.42,0:50:51.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:51:01.90,0:51:03.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:51:04.16,0:51:08.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N不可以插入
Dialogue: 0,0:51:39.13,0:51:39.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:51:39.67,0:51:40.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:51:42.87,0:51:44.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好兴奋
Dialogue: 0,0:51:47.41,0:51:48.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:52:09.43,0:52:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:52:09.83,0:52:09.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:52:09.96,0:52:10.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:52:19.04,0:52:20.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,0:55:36.70,0:55:37.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:55:40.17,0:55:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要考上喔
Dialogue: 0,0:55:47.51,0:55:49.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要考上喔
Dialogue: 0,0:56:36.90,0:56:40.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲我很在意你
Dialogue: 0,0:57:24.54,0:57:25.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:33.35,0:57:35.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:54.31,0:57:57.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:57:59.51,0:58:02.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:06.99,0:58:07.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说好了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:58:10.72,0:58:12.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会考上的\N说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:13.39,0:58:15.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:25.94,0:58:27.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:51.83,0:58:52.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,0:58:59.31,0:59:00.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,0:59:42.82,0:59:43.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:00:06.71,1:00:08.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:02.23,1:01:03.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:01:05.17,1:01:06.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:02:25.65,1:02:26.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,1:04:37.11,1:04:38.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:46.45,1:04:47.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:05:19.42,1:05:20.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,1:05:22.89,1:05:23.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:05:29.03,1:05:30.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:05:35.44,1:05:37.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗？\N好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:06:10.67,1:06:12.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:16.41,1:06:17.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:05.79,1:07:08.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨下次再来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:07:09.40,1:07:11.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不要一个人
Dialogue: 0,1:07:13.53,1:07:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以这样\N说好了要等到考上
Dialogue: 0,1:07:25.68,1:07:29.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,考上了\N再来做爱吧
Dialogue: 0,1:07:33.15,1:07:36.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等你考上
Dialogue: 0,1:07:38.49,1:07:39.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来做爱
Dialogue: 0,1:07:42.90,1:07:51.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也很想要小哲肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:07:55.98,1:07:57.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,1:07:59.18,1:08:00.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,1:08:01.85,1:08:04.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨也要忍着
Dialogue: 0,1:08:06.79,1:08:11.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也要忍着喔
Dialogue: 0,1:08:17.60,1:08:18.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要考上喔
Dialogue: 0,1:08:30.01,1:08:31.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很会亲吻喔
Dialogue: 0,1:08:39.22,1:08:40.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:10:05.17,1:10:08.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠里子的老公来了
Dialogue: 0,1:10:08.77,1:10:10.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暂时不可以下来喔
Dialogue: 0,1:10:11.58,1:10:12.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,1:10:13.31,1:10:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来接她的吗
Dialogue: 0,1:10:15.18,1:10:16.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:10:17.45,1:10:20.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老公正在道歉中
Dialogue: 0,1:10:21.05,1:10:22.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也算是个男人
Dialogue: 0,1:10:26.26,1:10:27.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那她要回家了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:10:28.93,1:10:29.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该吧
Dialogue: 0,1:10:31.73,1:10:33.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好读书吧
Dialogue: 0,1:11:33.53,1:11:34.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,1:11:35.13,1:11:38.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了你，他考上了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:38.46,1:11:40.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是你的功劳
Dialogue: 0,1:11:40.87,1:11:41.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎样了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:42.20,1:11:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还顺利吗
Dialogue: 0,1:11:44.47,1:11:45.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是喔
Dialogue: 0,1:11:46.07,1:11:47.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夫妇感情好 是最棒的
Dialogue: 0,1:11:49.54,1:11:52.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲说要跟你说谢\N换人了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:57.02,1:11:59.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我考上了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:02.22,1:12:03.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们约定好了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:05.56,1:12:06.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是惠里子的功劳
Dialogue: 0,1:12:13.03,1:12:14.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干杯
Dialogue: 0,1:12:20.24,1:12:21.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好喝
Dialogue: 0,1:12:21.84,1:12:23.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恵里子的功劳
Dialogue: 0,1:12:24.91,1:12:26.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为小哲很努力啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:27.98,1:12:30.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的很认真喔
Dialogue: 0,1:12:31.85,1:12:33.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:34.52,1:12:38.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么说呢，终于考上了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:39.33,1:12:42.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种喜悦太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:42.80,1:12:44.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天要多喝一点
Dialogue: 0,1:12:48.40,1:12:49.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,1:13:08.55,1:13:09.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好喝
Dialogue: 0,1:13:10.56,1:13:13.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新东宝翻译制作\N色花堂 Yamete 圣手提取
Dialogue: 0,1:15:19.89,1:15:20.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:15:20.55,1:15:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:16:03.53,1:16:05.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你考上
Dialogue: 0,1:16:08.20,1:16:08.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好开心
Dialogue: 0,1:16:08.33,1:16:09.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好开心
Dialogue: 0,1:16:12.87,1:16:13.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好开心
Dialogue: 0,1:16:21.28,1:16:22.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有很多时间
Dialogue: 0,1:16:28.89,1:16:32.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两人一起庆祝吧
Dialogue: 0,1:16:33.69,1:16:33.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:16:34.09,1:16:34.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:17:00.79,1:17:03.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这礼物，想从哪边拆开
Dialogue: 0,1:17:05.86,1:17:06.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胸部
Dialogue: 0,1:17:09.73,1:17:10.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,1:17:12.13,1:17:15.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢我胸部吗
Dialogue: 0,1:17:15.87,1:17:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,1:17:48.70,1:17:53.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多玩弄一点喔
Dialogue: 0,1:17:54.57,1:17:56.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜
Dialogue: 0,1:18:48.49,1:18:49.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要了吗
Dialogue: 0,1:18:50.10,1:18:50.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:08.78,1:19:09.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳头硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:21.73,1:19:24.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨乳头好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,1:19:52.96,1:19:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃
Dialogue: 0,1:19:57.10,1:19:59.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳头硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:03.37,1:20:04.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:20:08.57,1:20:12.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,考上的话，都变厉害了
Dialogue: 0,1:21:16.91,1:21:17.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股
Dialogue: 0,1:21:24.38,1:21:25.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超棒
Dialogue: 0,1:21:31.32,1:21:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:22:09.90,1:22:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来
Dialogue: 0,1:22:30.58,1:22:32.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是庆祝喔
Dialogue: 0,1:22:34.59,1:22:35.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多摸一点
Dialogue: 0,1:22:43.40,1:22:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,变大了喔
Dialogue: 0,1:23:26.10,1:23:27.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:23:27.84,1:23:29.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脱不下来
Dialogue: 0,1:23:33.71,1:23:34.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:24:06.41,1:24:07.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先忍着喔
Dialogue: 0,1:24:37.38,1:24:38.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,变热了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:07.01,1:25:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多看一点吧
Dialogue: 0,1:25:09.81,1:25:11.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来
Dialogue: 0,1:25:11.94,1:25:13.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仔细看一下
Dialogue: 0,1:25:41.17,1:25:42.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好淫荡喔
Dialogue: 0,1:25:52.78,1:25:53.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多爽一点吧
Dialogue: 0,1:25:55.99,1:25:58.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨忍很久了
Dialogue: 0,1:26:05.60,1:26:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨忍很久了
Dialogue: 0,1:26:34.16,1:26:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我吧
Dialogue: 0,1:26:45.24,1:26:46.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还想看
Dialogue: 0,1:26:53.51,1:26:54.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抽搐着喔
Dialogue: 0,1:27:19.14,1:27:20.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,掰开一点
Dialogue: 0,1:27:26.21,1:27:27.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好淫荡
Dialogue: 0,1:27:34.22,1:27:35.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小穴好淫荡
Dialogue: 0,1:27:41.69,1:27:46.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话，大学的时候就是大人了
Dialogue: 0,1:27:48.10,1:27:49.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多教我一点
Dialogue: 0,1:27:52.90,1:27:54.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多玩一点
Dialogue: 0,1:28:18.13,1:28:19.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舌头好热喔
Dialogue: 0,1:28:28.67,1:28:30.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,1:28:48.69,1:28:49.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多流出来一点吧
Dialogue: 0,1:29:00.31,1:29:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,湿了喔
Dialogue: 0,1:29:17.26,1:29:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨受不了了
Dialogue: 0,1:29:28.87,1:29:29.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:29:35.14,1:29:36.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:29:54.49,1:29:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,换阿姨了
Dialogue: 0,1:30:13.58,1:30:14.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,1:30:19.32,1:30:20.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,1:30:34.53,1:30:35.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,1:30:45.48,1:30:47.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舔吧
Dialogue: 0,1:31:05.23,1:31:06.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,1:31:25.52,1:31:26.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨好会舔喔
Dialogue: 0,1:31:28.59,1:31:29.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:31:37.00,1:31:39.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们心意相通
Dialogue: 0,1:32:06.09,1:32:07.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想插入了
Dialogue: 0,1:32:11.16,1:32:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来喔
Dialogue: 0,1:32:22.51,1:32:23.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,1:32:39.86,1:32:40.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不行
Dialogue: 0,1:32:48.67,1:32:51.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢的胸部
Dialogue: 0,1:32:52.94,1:32:54.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:32:56.67,1:32:57.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不能射喔
Dialogue: 0,1:32:59.21,1:33:00.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍着喔
Dialogue: 0,1:33:02.28,1:33:06.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大学生要忍着喔
Dialogue: 0,1:33:08.55,1:33:10.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以射
Dialogue: 0,1:33:10.96,1:33:12.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,1:33:14.56,1:33:15.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: 0,1:33:22.43,1:33:25.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,换这样吧
Dialogue: 0,1:33:26.44,1:33:28.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舔阿姨小穴吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:18.62,1:34:21.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来比赛吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:30.23,1:34:31.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以射喔
Dialogue: 0,1:34:36.64,1:34:37.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以射喔
Dialogue: 0,1:34:40.91,1:34:42.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:44.38,1:34:45.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢来
Dialogue: 0,1:35:01.47,1:35:02.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想插入了
Dialogue: 0,1:35:05.47,1:35:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大声一点
Dialogue: 0,1:35:08.81,1:35:09.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:35:11.61,1:35:15.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是大学生了\N要大声一点
Dialogue: 0,1:35:17.88,1:35:22.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想要插入小穴了
Dialogue: 0,1:35:31.50,1:35:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想插入什么
Dialogue: 0,1:35:35.37,1:35:36.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,1:35:39.50,1:35:41.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想把肉棒插入小穴
Dialogue: 0,1:35:42.04,1:35:43.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:35:46.31,1:35:52.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的肉棒想要插入小穴里
Dialogue: 0,1:36:02.33,1:36:05.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们说好了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:12.34,1:36:18.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的肉棒插到我的小穴
Dialogue: 0,1:36:19.81,1:36:25.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要插到深处喔
Dialogue: 0,1:36:58.25,1:36:59.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我受不了了
Dialogue: 0,1:37:22.14,1:37:23.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多亲一点
Dialogue: 0,1:37:48.97,1:37:52.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好湿喔\N插入吧
Dialogue: 0,1:37:52.97,1:37:55.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲结合吧
Dialogue: 0,1:38:19.00,1:38:19.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:38:22.20,1:38:24.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身体好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:38:43.29,1:38:44.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,1:38:45.96,1:38:47.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:38:53.16,1:38:54.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:39:02.64,1:39:04.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,长大了喔
Dialogue: 0,1:39:23.06,1:39:23.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多插一点
Dialogue: 0,1:39:46.82,1:39:47.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:39:55.09,1:39:56.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还要
Dialogue: 0,1:40:32.46,1:40:34.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以射喔
Dialogue: 0,1:40:40.87,1:40:42.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不可以射喔
Dialogue: 0,1:40:46.48,1:40:48.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托忍着吧
Dialogue: 0,1:40:51.15,1:40:58.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我教你从后面来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:41:00.89,1:41:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道吧
Dialogue: 0,1:41:03.56,1:41:05.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会扭腰吧
Dialogue: 0,1:41:12.10,1:41:13.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要抽出来喔
Dialogue: 0,1:41:17.04,1:41:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要抽出来喔\N从后面
Dialogue: 0,1:41:22.65,1:41:23.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冷静一点
Dialogue: 0,1:41:27.45,1:41:30.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抓着脚\N换这样
Dialogue: 0,1:41:33.72,1:41:36.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开始扭腰喔
Dialogue: 0,1:41:38.93,1:41:41.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:42.67,1:41:44.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好色喔
Dialogue: 0,1:42:31.92,1:42:32.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做到了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:34.32,1:42:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他后面来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:42:39.92,1:42:41.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,继续喔
Dialogue: 0,1:42:44.86,1:42:45.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来
Dialogue: 0,1:42:50.07,1:42:52.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:53.67,1:42:54.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:43:05.42,1:43:07.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抽搐着喔
Dialogue: 0,1:43:46.26,1:43:47.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:44:16.15,1:44:18.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我到上面吧
Dialogue: 0,1:45:05.40,1:45:09.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨的小穴里
Dialogue: 0,1:45:18.62,1:45:19.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仔细看喔
Dialogue: 0,1:45:26.89,1:45:29.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨来动吧
Dialogue: 0,1:45:48.38,1:45:49.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽一下吧
Dialogue: 0,1:46:10.27,1:46:12.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来喔
Dialogue: 0,1:46:16.01,1:46:18.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样好淫荡喔
Dialogue: 0,1:46:31.76,1:46:33.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像骑马
Dialogue: 0,1:46:36.56,1:46:38.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要多爽一下喔
Dialogue: 0,1:46:55.51,1:46:56.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍着喔
Dialogue: 0,1:46:57.25,1:46:58.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不行
Dialogue: 0,1:47:02.45,1:47:04.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要忍着
Dialogue: 0,1:47:14.87,1:47:17.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍着喔
Dialogue: 0,1:47:19.00,1:47:23.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样再来
Dialogue: 0,1:47:38.89,1:47:40.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,龟头这样
Dialogue: 0,1:47:43.56,1:47:46.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,深一点
Dialogue: 0,1:47:57.31,1:48:03.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会多让你爽一下
Dialogue: 0,1:48:04.65,1:48:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油喔
Dialogue: 0,1:48:07.72,1:48:09.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油喔
Dialogue: 0,1:48:12.66,1:48:13.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:48:14.39,1:48:15.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒喔
Dialogue: 0,1:49:46.48,1:49:48.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮好几次了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:52.62,1:49:54.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好乖
Dialogue: 0,1:50:06.24,1:50:07.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以射喔
Dialogue: 0,1:50:25.46,1:50:28.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽喔
Dialogue: 0,1:50:38.40,1:50:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从下面插上来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:52:05.42,1:52:06.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:52:09.56,1:52:11.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来啊
Dialogue: 0,1:52:33.45,1:52:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要抽搐了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:36.79,1:52:37.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,1:52:39.72,1:52:41.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:53:29.91,1:53:31.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:53:31.24,1:53:31.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:55:41.64,1:55:43.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射到嘴巴里喔
Dialogue: 0,1:55:50.71,1:55:52.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不想忘记你的味道
Dialogue: 0,1:56:19.14,1:56:20.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,1:57:15.33,1:57:16.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过来
Dialogue: 0,1:57:22.27,1:57:23.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小哲
Dialogue: 0,1:57:24.81,1:57:26.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜考上了
Dialogue: 0,1:57:54.44,1:57:57.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系喔，就到这边
Dialogue: 0,1:57:57.64,1:57:58.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用送我
Dialogue: 0,1:57:59.91,1:58:01.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还会见到你吧
Dialogue: 0,1:58:04.71,1:58:09.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样牵挂着我\N是不会交到大学女朋友喔
Dialogue: 0,1:58:10.99,1:58:12.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不是大婶
Dialogue: 0,1:58:14.19,1:58:15.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真笨
Dialogue: 0,1:58:18.86,1:58:22.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我这样是好的男朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,1:58:30.47,1:58:31.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合格了
Dialogue: 0,1:58:31.41,1:58:31.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合格了
Dialogue: 0,1:58:33.54,1:58:37.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是你走的路是不一样
Dialogue: 0,1:58:39.28,1:58:40.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,1:59:02.37,1:59:02.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恵里子
Dialogue: 0,1:59:02.77,1:59:03.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恵里子

