[Script Info]
; Generated by esrXP http://ideasoft.hp.infoseek.co.jp/esrXP/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Editing: 
Original Timing: 
Synch Point: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: V4.00
Collisions: Normal
PlayResY: 0
PlayResX: 0
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000

[v4 Styles]
Format: Name,Fontname,Fontsize,PrimaryColour,SecondaryColour,TertiaryColour,BackColour,Bold,Italic,BorderStyle,Outline,Shadow,Alignment,MarginL,MarginR,MarginV,AlphaLevel,Encoding
Style: Default,楷体,20,16777215,65535,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,15,1,0

[Events]
Format: Marked,Start,End,Style,Name,MarginL,MarginR,MarginV,Effect,Text
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:44.44,0:00:45.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:45.77,0:00:46.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像没有人呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:47.91,0:00:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:51.11,0:00:52.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门没锁 进去吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:57.92,0:00:58.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:59.92,0:01:01.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经是我们家的人了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:02.46,0:01:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天开始我们暂时住这里
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:07.53,0:01:08.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是这样
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:09.40,0:01:13.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不会打扰吉秋吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:15.27,0:01:17.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是看着爸爸死去的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:19.27,0:01:23.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由职业竟然能住这么大的房子
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:24.08,0:01:25.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种在都内可不便宜
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:27.15,0:01:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公真是的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:33.82,0:01:35.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真粗心啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:36.22,0:01:37.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开着吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:47.57,0:01:49.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋不在吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:54.91,0:01:55.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:23.61,0:02:24.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:25.47,0:02:26.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时回来住
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:28.68,0:02:30.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见 吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:30.95,0:02:34.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来打扰你了 请多指教
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:42.42,0:02:49.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抢走了大嫂
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:51.90,0:02:52.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:53.37,0:02:55.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新歌完成了吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:57.37,0:02:58.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:58.97,0:03:02.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么受欢迎的歌 也让我听吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:05.25,0:03:08.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没全部完成
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:11.92,0:03:15.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难说的呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:15.92,0:03:19.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要拿出来试听才行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:21.93,0:03:25.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也要哥哥多给我点建议
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:28.07,0:03:30.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没什么水平的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:31.67,0:03:35.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做音乐也很不景气
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:36.48,0:03:40.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都没有好的歌曲\N全是无聊的歌曲
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:41.68,0:03:43.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有值得期待的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:45.29,0:03:47.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由子也很喜欢听歌吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:47.96,0:03:48.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:49.29,0:03:53.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很喜欢造秋的摇滚
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:54.63,0:03:55.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:56.23,0:04:00.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 由子以前也是吉秋的粉丝
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:00.77,0:04:01.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:03.04,0:04:09.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粉丝们们分为和也派
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:10.25,0:04:12.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有吉秋派
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:13.05,0:04:15.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然是吉秋派的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:17.45,0:04:18.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:19.45,0:04:20.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才知道呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:21.86,0:04:22.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:23.73,0:04:27.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐也很有人气的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:29.20,0:04:32.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常方便我们
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:33.87,0:04:36.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和也他们也不错的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:37.34,0:04:39.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐也喜欢听吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:39.74,0:04:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:42.54,0:04:43.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不知道呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:45.08,0:04:48.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都是由子派呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:50.29,0:04:52.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个我也才知道
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:54.29,0:04:59.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才知道他们也喜欢我呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:00.30,0:05:01.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不知道呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:04.43,0:05:06.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真怀念啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:08.17,0:05:12.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的男粉丝能较多呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:15.11,0:05:16.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:17.51,0:05:19.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 哥哥
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:19.65,0:05:22.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在工作都很忙吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:25.25,0:05:27.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上要起很早呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:29.66,0:05:30.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好为难啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:32.73,0:05:35.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要还贷款呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:36.33,0:05:37.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:39.13,0:05:40.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真为难
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:48.21,0:05:49.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:49.81,0:05:52.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以先洗澡吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:53.55,0:05:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题，他不用浴缸的，
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:00.62,0:06:01.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎不太好
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:04.36,0:06:06.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家里随便一点
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:07.16,0:06:12.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不会介意的\N随便一点比放松
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:16.24,0:06:17.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的话就好了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:20.24,0:06:21.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明夫还要早起 先睡了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:22.38,0:06:23.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:44.73,0:07:45.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:47.13,0:07:47.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公是你吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:04.81,0:09:05.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:29.90,0:09:31.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 老公
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:28.09,0:10:28.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出门了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:29.16,0:10:30.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢走 注意安全
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:46.17,0:11:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安 吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:50.30,0:11:51.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是饭做好了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:52.71,0:11:53.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:55.24,0:11:56.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你盛饭吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:58.58,0:11:58.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:58.71,0:11:58.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:58.85,0:11:58.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:58.98,0:11:59.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:59.11,0:11:59.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:04.32,0:12:05.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:07.79,0:12:08.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:10.99,0:12:12.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:13.93,0:12:14.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:15.40,0:12:16.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:19.00,0:12:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:21.54,0:12:23.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直很喜欢弥
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:24.21,0:12:26.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:27.14,0:12:28.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:31.28,0:12:35.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐太有魅力了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:38.62,0:12:39.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:41.69,0:12:45.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知何时开始就喜欢上你了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:49.70,0:12:51.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直没有说
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:51.83,0:12:51.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直没有说
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:51.97,0:12:52.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直没有说
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:52.10,0:12:52.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直没有说
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:52.23,0:12:54.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直没有说
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:55.70,0:12:56.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:57.57,0:13:04.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做音乐很好
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:07.45,0:13:08.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:08.12,0:13:08.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:15.99,0:13:16.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:19.19,0:13:20.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:31.21,0:13:32.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好喜欢你啊 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:34.41,0:13:35.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:47.22,0:13:48.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:48.16,0:13:49.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:54.56,0:13:55.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:58.43,0:13:59.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:02.97,0:14:04.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋 住手
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:06.04,0:14:06.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:08.44,0:14:09.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:11.11,0:14:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:14.72,0:14:14.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:14.85,0:14:15.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:16.58,0:14:17.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很美
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:17.79,0:14:18.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:20.72,0:14:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱掉吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:22.72,0:14:23.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:29.53,0:14:31.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:40.88,0:14:41.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:41.01,0:14:41.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:41.14,0:14:41.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:45.55,0:14:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:04.23,0:15:05.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐不要藏着
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:10.50,0:15:11.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:13.31,0:15:14.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:14.78,0:15:16.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢你
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:30.39,0:15:32.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个奶头真可爱
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:35.46,0:15:37.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要做这种事
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:40.53,0:15:41.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:42.54,0:15:43.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:59.49,0:16:00.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:04.29,0:16:04.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:04.96,0:16:05.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:06.96,0:16:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做是错的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:11.77,0:16:12.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了 
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:17.10,0:16:17.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:19.51,0:16:20.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:25.11,0:16:25.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湿了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:30.58,0:16:31.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:34.46,0:16:35.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:38.59,0:16:39.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:43.93,0:16:45.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:49.14,0:16:49.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:49.80,0:16:49.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:57.68,0:16:58.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:59.41,0:17:00.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:02.88,0:17:04.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给哥哥太浪费了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:06.89,0:17:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:11.56,0:17:12.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮肤好漂亮
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:15.43,0:17:16.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:20.77,0:17:21.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒啊 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:28.24,0:17:29.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐的屁股
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:36.92,0:17:37.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:41.19,0:17:41.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里比较爽呢 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:43.99,0:17:44.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样是错的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:46.13,0:17:47.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佳手吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:49.86,0:17:50.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:56.40,0:17:57.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:59.47,0:18:00.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湿了吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:09.08,0:18:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:14.42,0:18:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:16.56,0:18:17.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:27.10,0:18:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:31.24,0:18:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸了淫荡的地方呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:39.25,0:18:40.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这么湿呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:43.38,0:18:44.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这迹想做吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:46.85,0:18:47.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:48.32,0:18:49.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么湿呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:51.26,0:18:52.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:54.86,0:18:55.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:04.34,0:19:05.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:14.35,0:19:15.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:16.48,0:19:17.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好添啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:20.09,0:19:21.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:22.49,0:19:23.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你更爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:38.51,0:19:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:42.38,0:19:43.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫荡啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:46.51,0:19:47.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好漂亮
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:50.25,0:19:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐的身体真的好漂亮
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:56.52,0:19:57.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全看见了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:59.59,0:20:00.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼也看见了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:02.40,0:20:03.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:04.67,0:20:05.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼也要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:16.41,0:20:17.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:20.68,0:20:21.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可爱呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:25.75,0:20:26.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴也要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:28.82,0:20:30.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫荡啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:33.49,0:20:34.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢被怎么弄呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:37.36,0:20:38.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:39.63,0:20:40.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:42.97,0:20:43.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:50.31,0:20:51.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:21:00.85,0:21:01.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:21:11.67,0:21:12.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:21:18.34,0:21:19.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多拉丝哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:21:40.76,0:21:41.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:21:49.70,0:21:50.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:21:56.64,0:21:57.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:21:59.58,0:22:00.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:01.32,0:22:02.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:03.45,0:22:04.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:05.05,0:22:05.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:07.19,0:22:07.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:10.39,0:22:13.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐也兴奋了 停不下来吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:17.46,0:22:18.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:20.13,0:22:20.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:25.34,0:22:26.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得好湿啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:26.67,0:22:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:28.68,0:22:29.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:31.75,0:22:32.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜欢的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:38.15,0:22:39.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也让我爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:22:43.22,0:22:44.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:23:13.52,0:23:14.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:23:15.52,0:23:16.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,张开嘴
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:23:38.61,0:23:39.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:23:40.61,0:23:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:23:47.82,0:23:48.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:23:50.76,0:23:51.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:23:52.63,0:23:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:24:03.17,0:24:03.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:24:06.11,0:24:07.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:24:56.42,0:24:57.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:24:58.02,0:24:58.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:25:00.29,0:25:01.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:25:06.17,0:25:06.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:25:15.78,0:25:16.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:25:20.18,0:25:20.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:25:31.53,0:25:32.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:25:55.02,0:25:55.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:26:00.62,0:26:01.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:26:13.83,0:26:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:26:16.37,0:26:17.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:26:21.58,0:26:22.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:26:58.14,0:26:58.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:27:04.82,0:27:05.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:27:06.82,0:27:08.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:28:17.02,0:28:17.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:28:20.36,0:28:21.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在抽动呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:28:23.30,0:28:24.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:28:26.63,0:28:27.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:28:45.19,0:28:45.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:29:12.68,0:29:13.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:29:52.59,0:29:53.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:29:58.06,0:29:58.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腰动起来
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:30:32.23,0:30:35.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:30:38.63,0:30:39.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒插入了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:30:41.57,0:30:43.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:30:51.85,0:30:53.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:31:06.66,0:31:07.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:31:13.20,0:31:14.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:31:16.94,0:31:17.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:31:25.35,0:31:26.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:31:27.75,0:31:28.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好紧啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:31:36.29,0:31:37.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:32:04.98,0:32:06.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顶到深处了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:32:07.65,0:32:08.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:32:37.28,0:32:38.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:32:43.16,0:32:43.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:32:48.63,0:32:49.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:33:02.51,0:33:03.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:33:22.26,0:33:23.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:34:30.46,0:34:31.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:34:52.75,0:34:53.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:35:20.78,0:35:21.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:35:26.52,0:35:27.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:35:31.32,0:35:33.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:36:27.25,0:36:28.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:36:30.72,0:36:31.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:36:34.59,0:36:35.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插进去了吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:36:45.80,0:36:46.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:36:53.81,0:36:54.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:37:00.35,0:37:01.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:37:15.16,0:37:15.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:37:39.45,0:37:40.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:37:54.93,0:37:55.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:38:04.41,0:38:05.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:38:18.56,0:38:19.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:38:25.23,0:38:26.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:38:32.84,0:38:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:38:43.65,0:38:44.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:39:07.67,0:39:08.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:40:10.67,0:40:11.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:40:55.65,0:40:56.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:41:04.59,0:41:05.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:41:06.19,0:41:06.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:41:07.93,0:41:08.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射好多精子出来哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:41:11.26,0:41:12.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:41:13.80,0:41:14.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能射里面
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:41:15.94,0:41:17.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出来可以吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:42:08.65,0:42:09.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:25.80,0:43:26.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:27.13,0:43:27.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:29.00,0:43:29.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了什么吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:31.67,0:43:32.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么问
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:33.94,0:43:35.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你声音有点奇怪
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:39.01,0:43:40.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:41.95,0:43:42.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚打扫过
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:43.28,0:43:44.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点累了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:46.89,0:43:49.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那么勤快
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:51.96,0:43:55.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要干点活才行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:43:56.50,0:43:59.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天可能要晚归
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:01.30,0:44:02.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要晚归吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:02.50,0:44:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:03.84,0:44:06.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:07.17,0:44:08.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了什么吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:11.04,0:44:12.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:13.58,0:44:17.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有点寂寞
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:18.12,0:44:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:20.92,0:44:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会好好补偿你的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:43.21,0:44:44.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:45.21,0:44:46.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:46.95,0:44:48.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:54.69,0:44:55.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很寂寞吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:56.96,0:44:57.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:44:58.96,0:45:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:04.30,0:45:05.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:07.37,0:45:08.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:09.37,0:45:10.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢怎么做呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:12.04,0:45:12.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:14.71,0:45:15.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:16.18,0:45:17.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:17.91,0:45:18.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥回不来呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:20.85,0:45:22.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们好好玩吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:23.65,0:45:24.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:26.45,0:45:27.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:30.32,0:45:33.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样是错的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:46.47,0:45:47.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:55.28,0:45:56.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:45:57.15,0:45:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:02.76,0:46:03.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:13.17,0:46:14.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:16.24,0:46:17.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:25.84,0:46:27.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想要的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:35.19,0:46:36.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:41.46,0:46:42.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实点
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:44.26,0:46:45.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:48.40,0:46:49.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:50.27,0:46:51.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:51.87,0:46:53.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:46:55.34,0:46:56.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:47:03.22,0:47:04.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 放开我吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:47:20.57,0:47:21.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:47:23.50,0:47:24.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:47:27.11,0:47:28.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:47:33.11,0:47:34.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:47:42.19,0:47:43.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很着急吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:47:46.59,0:47:48.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:47:51.13,0:47:52.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有感觉吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:47:54.73,0:47:56.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋 不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:07.01,0:48:08.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:10.08,0:48:10.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被怎么弄了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:13.15,0:48:14.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:21.56,0:48:22.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:24.36,0:48:25.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放过我吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:26.23,0:48:27.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:33.31,0:48:34.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:37.31,0:48:38.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想要吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:43.98,0:48:44.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被怎么弄了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:50.26,0:48:51.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:48:53.59,0:48:54.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜迁了不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:01.87,0:49:04.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:07.61,0:49:08.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:11.88,0:49:12.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:16.42,0:49:17.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么有感觉吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:20.15,0:49:21.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 不要
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:25.09,0:49:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被怎么弄了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:27.76,0:49:28.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:44.04,0:49:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:46.98,0:49:47.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么不行呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:53.65,0:49:55.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很爽吧\N不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:49:56.05,0:49:57.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:09.53,0:50:10.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:13.54,0:50:14.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:17.41,0:50:18.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想要吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:21.28,0:50:22.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:22.88,0:50:24.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 住手吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:26.49,0:50:27.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:28.75,0:50:29.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:31.16,0:50:32.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:45.44,0:50:46.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级湿的呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:49.71,0:50:50.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我舔吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:50:54.11,0:50:55.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:51:43.23,0:51:44.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:51:50.17,0:51:50.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多舔一些
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:10.19,0:52:10.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:11.79,0:52:11.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:12.59,0:52:13.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:16.86,0:52:18.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:19.13,0:52:20.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:22.07,0:52:22.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不行吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:24.07,0:52:25.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:26.34,0:52:27.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:45.42,0:52:46.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:48.23,0:52:49.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么不行呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:53.70,0:52:54.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么有感觉
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:52:57.97,0:52:58.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有不行吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:19.06,0:53:19.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:31.20,0:53:32.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不行吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:33.87,0:53:34.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮几次了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:37.74,0:53:38.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想要的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:45.48,0:53:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:47.09,0:53:47.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:48.82,0:53:49.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:50.96,0:53:52.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:53.36,0:53:54.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:54.96,0:53:56.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做是错的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:53:57.90,0:54:00.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做很严重的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:00.97,0:54:02.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:03.10,0:54:04.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我舔吧\N不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:05.50,0:54:06.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:07.37,0:54:08.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不讨厌的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:09.64,0:54:10.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:12.84,0:54:14.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就做吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:15.78,0:54:17.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:18.72,0:54:20.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以做吗\N可以的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:21.92,0:54:23.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:24.72,0:54:25.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来插吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:27.79,0:54:28.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:38.07,0:54:40.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都做吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:45.14,0:54:46.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会让你爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:54:55.02,0:54:56.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来让我爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:55:34.79,0:55:35.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:55:39.33,0:55:40.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:55:48.41,0:55:49.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:55:56.41,0:55:57.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:56:03.22,0:56:04.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:56:12.70,0:56:13.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:56:16.57,0:56:17.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样好爽
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:56:26.18,0:56:26.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:56:36.99,0:56:37.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:56:39.12,0:56:40.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:56:44.06,0:56:45.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多舔一些
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:56:54.21,0:56:55.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:57:06.62,0:57:07.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:57:16.63,0:57:17.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:57:18.10,0:57:18.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:57:38.92,0:57:39.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:57:52.13,0:57:53.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 多舔一些
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:58:15.62,0:58:16.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:58:32.44,0:58:33.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:58:52.59,0:58:53.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:58:57.80,0:58:58.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:59:02.07,0:59:04.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽的话就发出声音吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:59:10.88,0:59:11.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:59:17.28,0:59:18.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:59:22.09,0:59:22.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:59:31.83,0:59:32.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:59:34.90,0:59:35.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:00:08.67,1:00:09.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:00:10.00,1:00:10.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:00:17.88,1:00:19.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:00:22.01,1:00:23.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:01:22.74,1:01:23.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:01:33.42,1:01:34.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:01:39.16,1:01:41.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好开心
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:01:43.70,1:01:45.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你喜欢我
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:01:47.43,1:01:48.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:01:55.44,1:01:56.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:01:58.38,1:02:01.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是最后一次
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:02:05.58,1:02:06.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好开心
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:02:07.99,1:02:08.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:02:48.83,1:02:49.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:02:50.83,1:02:51.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡着了吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:02:53.23,1:02:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:02:56.17,1:02:57.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说今晚不能回来吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:03:00.17,1:03:02.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然间很在意由子
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:03:04.31,1:03:05.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事都没有哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:03:07.38,1:03:08.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 这样就好
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:03:10.58,1:03:11.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去洗澡
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:03:55.83,1:03:56.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:03:57.30,1:03:58.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢走
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:04:38.94,1:04:39.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:04:41.47,1:04:42.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安 吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:13.91,1:05:16.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来还有点担心的呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:16.97,1:05:17.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:17.91,1:05:18.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做到了吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:20.71,1:05:22.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本完成了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:22.98,1:05:24.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以让哥哥听听了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:26.18,1:05:26.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:27.92,1:05:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:31.26,1:05:33.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你让我喜欢上音乐的
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:34.86,1:05:38.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次听到的时候觉得很厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:49.81,1:05:50.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:51.68,1:05:54.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由子今晚喝一杯吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:55.28,1:05:56.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:05:57.42,1:05:59.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久没喝了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:06:00.75,1:06:03.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那今晚我就早点回来
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:06:05.16,1:06:07.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以早回来吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:06:11.16,1:06:14.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天很重要呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:06:16.50,1:06:17.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:06:19.30,1:06:21.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和吉秋没关系的吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:06:34.79,1:06:35.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:06:36.12,1:06:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢走
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:06:39.19,1:06:39.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:07:17.23,1:07:18.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:07:19.90,1:07:20.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:07:22.03,1:07:25.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后 我一直专心做音乐
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:07:26.84,1:07:28.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也要让我听听哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:07:35.11,1:07:36.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:07:36.98,1:07:37.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:07:41.92,1:07:42.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:08:25.96,1:08:26.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:08:29.17,1:08:30.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得道么湿了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:08:34.37,1:08:35.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:08:37.31,1:08:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱了以后 变得这么湿
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:02.07,1:19:02.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好喝
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:04.20,1:19:09.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋的新作终于完成了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:10.21,1:19:12.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那么期待 我压力很大
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:13.94,1:19:14.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:19.28,1:19:20.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么公司呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:21.95,1:19:27.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次都是我自己创作\N和之前的不同
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:29.03,1:19:30.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道会怎么样呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:30.49,1:19:31.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:35.17,1:19:36.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 怎么样
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:38.37,1:19:43.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就惨了 公司要我培训明星
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:45.18,1:19:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比之前都惨
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:19:49.98,1:19:56.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪些明星虽然都有干劲\N但是没音乐才华
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:01.86,1:20:05.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些明星很没前途呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:06.40,1:20:08.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不想做
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:11.87,1:20:16.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这毕竟是我的工作
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:18.68,1:20:25.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 身边这么多年轻女孩\N真是抱歉呢 由子
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:28.15,1:20:29.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是工作而已
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:30.29,1:20:31.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不介意
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:32.02,1:20:37.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全不理解年轻女孩的兴趣
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:40.43,1:20:42.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道他们想什么
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:45.77,1:20:48.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公 你喝太多了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:20:51.91,1:20:52.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我睡一下
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:23:37.94,1:23:38.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:23:38.21,1:23:38.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:23:38.34,1:23:38.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:23:38.48,1:23:38.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:23:38.61,1:23:38.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:24:10.77,1:24:11.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:24:35.60,1:24:36.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:24:47.74,1:24:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真漂亮啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:25:07.23,1:25:08.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐真漂亮
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:25:31.25,1:25:32.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来舔吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:25:41.66,1:25:42.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:25:52.61,1:25:53.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:26:08.63,1:26:09.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:26:15.97,1:26:16.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:26:45.60,1:26:46.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真淫荡呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:27:04.95,1:27:05.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:27:10.29,1:27:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋 脱掉吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:27:42.32,1:27:43.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:27:44.72,1:27:45.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:28:12.62,1:28:13.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱掉吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:28:21.82,1:28:22.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:28:26.76,1:28:28.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全看见了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:28:29.17,1:28:30.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:28:36.11,1:28:36.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴张开了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:28:39.18,1:28:39.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:28:41.84,1:28:42.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫荡的味道
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:28:46.38,1:28:47.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让它湿深的哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:29:26.96,1:29:27.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:29:36.43,1:29:37.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:29:38.30,1:29:39.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:29:58.59,1:29:59.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:30:02.99,1:30:04.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在抽动呢\N因为好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:30:06.06,1:30:06.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:30:13.00,1:30:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:30:30.89,1:30:31.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:30:34.89,1:30:36.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫荡的声音
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:30:52.38,1:30:53.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:30:53.98,1:30:55.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:18.94,1:31:19.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:21.20,1:31:21.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:21.34,1:31:21.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:21.47,1:31:22.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:33.62,1:31:34.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又去了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:36.95,1:31:37.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:43.49,1:31:43.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:43.63,1:31:43.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:43.89,1:31:44.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:44.96,1:31:45.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:45.09,1:31:45.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:45.23,1:31:45.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:45.36,1:31:45.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:45.50,1:31:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:49.77,1:31:49.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:49.90,1:31:50.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:57.24,1:31:58.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:31:59.51,1:32:00.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫荡啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:32:04.45,1:32:05.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:32:11.79,1:32:12.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:32:24.60,1:32:25.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:32:30.47,1:32:31.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来摸吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:32:33.28,1:32:34.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得好硬啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:32:36.61,1:32:37.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:33:07.98,1:33:08.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:33:11.31,1:33:12.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:33:18.92,1:33:19.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:33:26.53,1:33:27.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:33:28.40,1:33:29.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:33:32.00,1:33:32.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:33:44.15,1:33:45.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:33:51.09,1:33:51.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:33:59.63,1:34:01.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 技术好棒
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:34:17.11,1:34:17.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:34:18.58,1:34:19.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:34:25.92,1:34:26.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:34:28.19,1:34:29.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:34:31.13,1:34:33.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真淫荡呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:34:42.61,1:34:43.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:34:49.15,1:34:50.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:35:15.30,1:35:16.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:35:34.12,1:35:35.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:35:36.39,1:35:37.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:35:47.20,1:35:48.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:36:04.42,1:36:06.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 忍不住了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:36:11.36,1:36:12.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:36:20.30,1:36:21.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:36:22.84,1:36:23.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:36:26.04,1:36:27.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也好想要
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:36:35.25,1:36:36.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想要
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:36:43.53,1:36:44.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好湿啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:36:57.67,1:36:58.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:37:15.02,1:37:15.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:37:22.10,1:37:22.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:37:24.50,1:37:25.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:37:43.85,1:37:44.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:37:51.99,1:37:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:01.34,1:38:02.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:03.61,1:38:04.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:05.21,1:38:06.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:13.35,1:38:14.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:20.16,1:38:21.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:26.43,1:38:27.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫荡啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:37.77,1:38:38.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插得好深
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:39.51,1:38:40.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:51.79,1:38:52.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:38:53.66,1:38:55.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:06.74,1:39:07.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多插一些
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:16.35,1:39:17.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:24.89,1:39:25.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:25.02,1:39:25.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:25.15,1:39:25.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:25.29,1:39:25.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:25.42,1:39:25.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:25.55,1:39:25.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:51.85,1:39:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:39:55.45,1:39:56.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:40:02.79,1:40:03.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:40:04.93,1:40:05.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:40:40.96,1:40:41.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:40:54.58,1:40:54.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:40:54.71,1:40:54.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:40:54.84,1:40:55.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:06.72,1:41:07.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:14.73,1:41:15.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:18.87,1:41:19.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:24.47,1:41:25.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐技术好棒
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:29.68,1:41:30.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:33.42,1:41:35.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:45.96,1:41:46.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:47.43,1:41:48.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:51.03,1:41:52.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:41:54.10,1:41:55.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:42:02.91,1:42:05.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐的小穴好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:42:07.85,1:42:10.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒插得好深啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:42:23.07,1:42:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:42:32.94,1:42:34.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:42:49.09,1:42:49.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:43:36.87,1:43:37.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:44:09.30,1:44:10.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:44:18.11,1:44:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:44:20.92,1:44:22.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:44:33.73,1:44:34.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:44:39.20,1:44:40.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:44:43.07,1:44:43.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:44:45.74,1:44:47.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴好紧啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:45:06.43,1:45:07.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:45:07.76,1:45:08.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:45:20.31,1:45:22.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:45:26.05,1:45:26.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级湿的
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:45:55.01,1:45:56.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 插得好深
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:46:00.48,1:46:01.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:46:02.48,1:46:03.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:46:20.24,1:46:21.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:46:33.32,1:46:34.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:46:40.26,1:46:41.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:46:44.93,1:46:45.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好湿哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:47:01.61,1:47:02.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉秋
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:47:08.82,1:47:09.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:47:29.10,1:47:29.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:47:42.32,1:47:42.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:47:42.45,1:47:42.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:47:42.98,1:47:43.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:48:00.34,1:48:01.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:48:06.48,1:48:07.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了呢
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:48:11.28,1:48:12.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:48:13.42,1:48:14.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:48:21.42,1:48:23.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个做爱太爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:48:41.71,1:48:42.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:48:43.45,1:48:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:49:08.67,1:49:09.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:49:12.14,1:49:13.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:49:24.29,1:49:25.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:50:17.94,1:50:18.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:50:24.08,1:50:24.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:50:27.28,1:50:28.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:50:31.15,1:50:31.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:50:42.10,1:50:42.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级湿的
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:50:44.77,1:50:45.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:50:47.70,1:50:48.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 出来了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:51:17.07,1:51:17.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:51:29.21,1:51:30.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:51:48.30,1:51:49.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:51:57.64,1:51:58.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:52:04.18,1:52:04.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:52:25.80,1:52:26.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:52:28.74,1:52:30.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:53:27.06,1:53:27.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:53:40.01,1:53:40.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:53:44.01,1:53:45.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:53:47.35,1:53:48.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:53:49.88,1:53:50.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:53:52.42,1:53:54.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多做一些
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:53:56.02,1:53:57.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次这么爽
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:53:58.29,1:53:59.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊 姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:54:01.76,1:54:02.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:54:12.17,1:54:13.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 又要去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:54:14.71,1:54:15.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:54:19.91,1:54:21.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:54:35.80,1:54:36.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:54:52.35,1:54:53.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:54:55.95,1:54:56.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出来吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:54:58.22,1:54:59.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射在我的嘴里
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:55:00.62,1:55:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射好多出来吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:55:12.90,1:55:13.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:55:16.91,1:55:17.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:55:34.79,1:55:35.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:55:48.27,1:55:49.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:56:09.36,1:56:10.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:56:12.69,1:56:13.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:56:17.90,1:56:18.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:56:22.30,1:56:23.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要和哥哥说哦
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:57:02.48,1:57:03.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:57:04.21,1:57:05.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始有点困难
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:57:06.75,1:57:09.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过已经解决了
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:57:10.08,1:57:10.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢哥哥
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:57:12.35,1:57:13.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公 慢走
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:58:01.60,1:58:02.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听听看吧
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:58:14.82,1:58:15.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: Marked=0,1:58:15.48,1:58:15.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
 