[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.40,0:00:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是星期四嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.65,0:00:05.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.00,0:00:06.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.20,0:00:09.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備到休息日了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.75,0:00:14.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.85,0:00:16.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚飯好吃嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.90,0:00:19.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.85,0:00:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.55,0:00:26.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這是什麼語氣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.70,0:00:27.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是你的媽媽了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.55,0:00:31.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.00,0:00:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還沒有習慣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.55,0:00:36.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.25,0:00:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然不會那麼快習慣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.75,0:00:45.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很早之前我就說過\N我會再婚的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.45,0:00:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要一起生活的 快點適應吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.10,0:00:52.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,適應需要一些時間\N(牧村彩香)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.70,0:00:57.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我祝福爸爸能夠再婚
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:00.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想和新媽媽好好相處
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.10,0:01:04.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不知該怎麼做
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.90,0:01:15.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去洗碗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.45,0:01:32.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(我和後母一起看成人電視劇\N親密的接吻場景開始了 牧村彩香)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.75,0:01:47.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在看電視劇嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.80,0:01:51.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 每週都看
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.85,0:01:59.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學校的同學說很有趣\N推薦我看
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.55,0:02:01.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天正想看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.55,0:02:03.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.20,0:02:06.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個電視劇非常有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.75,0:02:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.44,0:02:11.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友也是這麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.00,0:02:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以告訴我大概的情節嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.35,0:02:17.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.70,0:02:21.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介也喜歡這樣的電視劇嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.05,0:02:23.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.00,0:02:27.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我有很多集\N我還沒有看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.95,0:02:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要好好追趕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.95,0:02:33.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那讓我來告訴你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.10,0:02:38.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在裡面的就是主角
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.85,0:02:43.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛過去的是小宏的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.70,0:02:46.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此\N是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.40,0:02:48.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎很有趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.40,0:02:54.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劇情上有一點拖拉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.35,0:02:56.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是很有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.15,0:02:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.20,0:02:58.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.40,0:03:12.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是等不及週四了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.90,0:03:14.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天肯定有新劇情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.90,0:03:20.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我支持美裏哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.75,0:03:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.05,0:03:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.55,0:03:26.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得這個沒什麼關係呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.30,0:03:28.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.10,0:03:30.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人的感覺最準確
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.00,0:03:35.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一周以來都在聊電視劇
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.95,0:03:39.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.75,0:03:40.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.80,0:03:43.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子你和大介也能好好相處
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.70,0:03:45.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出門了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.50,0:03:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 慢走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.75,0:03:49.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出門了\N慢走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.65,0:03:49.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出門了\N慢走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.80,0:03:50.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出門了\N慢走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.75,0:03:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上小心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.30,0:03:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好期待哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.25,0:04:00.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這周的電視也開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.35,0:04:57.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 今天是星期四吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.65,0:05:05.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一周沒有聊電視劇了\N我都忘記了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.20,0:05:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你們也會一起看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.75,0:05:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.30,0:05:16.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開心真好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.85,0:05:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.60,0:06:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.60,0:06:10.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽去上廁所
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.70,0:06:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.65,0:06:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道這樣做不對
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.50,0:06:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.70,0:06:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到電視劇裡接吻
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.40,0:06:24.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.65,0:06:26.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.95,0:06:42.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.80,0:06:45.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.75,0:06:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.35,0:07:20.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.30,0:07:25.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是母子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.00,0:07:28.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.95,0:07:30.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們沒有血緣關係
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.20,0:07:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然如此
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.70,0:07:33.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想接吻哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.35,0:07:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想接吻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.05,0:08:07.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.25,0:08:09.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.80,0:08:12.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我親吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.10,0:08:21.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.90,0:08:24.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電視劇裡沒做這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.75,0:08:26.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.75,0:08:31.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要這樣模媽媽的身體
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.80,0:08:32.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.90,0:08:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.70,0:08:36.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.55,0:08:54.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.05,0:08:56.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.55,0:09:00.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.25,0:09:12.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.60,0:09:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.25,0:09:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.60,0:09:17.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.40,0:09:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.50,0:09:35.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.60,0:09:37.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.25,0:09:39.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好激烈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.50,0:09:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.90,0:09:49.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.40,0:09:51.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧\N不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.90,0:09:53.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧\N不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.70,0:09:54.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.05,0:10:17.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.35,0:10:20.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.00,0:10:22.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.25,0:10:24.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.70,0:10:32.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個姿勢好害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.75,0:10:34.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.95,0:10:39.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.60,0:10:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.55,0:10:46.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是讓爸爸知道的話
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.30,0:10:49.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.25,0:10:51.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.75,0:10:53.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對要保密哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.30,0:11:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.45,0:11:16.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.80,0:11:18.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.60,0:11:19.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.20,0:11:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.10,0:11:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.15,0:11:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.15,0:11:56.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 那裡不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.55,0:11:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.20,0:12:00.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能摸媽媽那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.75,0:12:07.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想要的意思嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.50,0:12:09.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.90,0:12:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.70,0:12:21.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.10,0:12:24.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得這麼濕了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.25,0:12:28.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好開心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.05,0:12:33.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好興奮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.40,0:12:42.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.85,0:12:48.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.30,0:13:14.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續和我接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.75,0:13:16.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.00,0:13:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.80,0:13:41.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.15,0:13:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.25,0:13:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.20,0:13:47.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.80,0:13:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好色情的氣味哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.35,0:13:59.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉開內褲看看可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.00,0:14:02.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 那樣不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.55,0:14:04.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.95,0:14:12.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.30,0:14:19.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.80,0:14:21.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得好濕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.40,0:14:25.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.50,0:14:27.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.00,0:14:31.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.00,0:14:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.40,0:14:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.25,0:14:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.15,0:14:52.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.30,0:15:01.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.30,0:15:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.75,0:15:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.15,0:15:26.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手指插進去可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.00,0:15:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.05,0:15:34.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.25,0:15:40.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽會變得奇怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.20,0:15:44.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.35,0:16:05.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.70,0:16:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.30,0:16:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.50,0:16:23.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好濕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.25,0:16:27.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好濕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.60,0:16:46.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.75,0:17:01.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.80,0:17:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.90,0:17:13.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.70,0:17:15.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.34,0:17:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.90,0:17:25.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.55,0:17:37.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.65,0:17:47.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.25,0:18:00.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.60,0:18:01.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好濕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.40,0:18:03.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.65,0:18:06.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 大介
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.15,0:18:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.40,0:18:09.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.35,0:18:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.85,0:18:13.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好忍耐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.55,0:18:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.35,0:18:17.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.35,0:18:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.50,0:18:23.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.35,0:18:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.95,0:19:03.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.95,0:19:18.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.35,0:19:21.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.50,0:19:23.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.60,0:19:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.35,0:19:35.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.55,0:19:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好硬哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.70,0:19:40.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.50,0:20:05.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.75,0:20:16.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.10,0:20:18.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.20,0:20:21.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.90,0:20:24.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.90,0:20:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.90,0:20:32.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣很爽嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.85,0:20:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.85,0:20:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.50,0:21:03.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.85,0:21:09.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.55,0:21:21.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.40,0:21:36.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.05,0:22:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.50,0:22:08.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.80,0:22:11.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.55,0:22:34.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.00,0:22:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.85,0:23:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.90,0:23:11.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.85,0:23:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.40,0:23:57.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.50,0:24:02.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.75,0:24:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.20,0:24:14.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.85,0:24:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.95,0:24:36.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.75,0:24:37.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.20,0:24:41.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.25,0:24:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.00,0:24:51.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.15,0:25:21.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.10,0:25:33.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.35,0:25:56.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.50,0:25:59.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.20,0:26:05.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想要哦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.40,0:26:15.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.55,0:26:21.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.15,0:26:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.50,0:26:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.30,0:26:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.30,0:26:37.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.10,0:26:42.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.20,0:26:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.30,0:26:52.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.45,0:26:55.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.05,0:27:02.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.85,0:27:07.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.30,0:27:13.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.90,0:27:23.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.90,0:27:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.85,0:27:28.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.05,0:27:32.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.25,0:27:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.25,0:28:15.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.60,0:28:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.20,0:28:24.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.10,0:28:27.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.85,0:28:31.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.35,0:28:35.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.55,0:28:36.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.75,0:28:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.15,0:28:49.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.40,0:28:51.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.30,0:28:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好激烈哦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.85,0:28:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好激烈哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.15,0:29:01.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.20,0:29:05.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.85,0:29:09.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.55,0:29:13.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 大介
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.65,0:29:17.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.10,0:29:30.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.60,0:29:32.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.85,0:29:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡好熱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.00,0:29:37.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡好熱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.90,0:29:40.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.85,0:29:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.10,0:29:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.45,0:30:01.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.60,0:30:07.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.15,0:30:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.70,0:30:12.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.35,0:30:17.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.30,0:30:19.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.25,0:30:21.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.25,0:30:24.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.60,0:30:25.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.95,0:30:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.20,0:30:30.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能動
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.45,0:30:34.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.60,0:30:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.90,0:30:48.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.20,0:30:50.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.30,0:30:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.40,0:30:54.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.40,0:30:57.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.45,0:31:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.80,0:31:15.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.90,0:31:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.85,0:31:18.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.40,0:31:21.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.70,0:31:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.55,0:31:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.35,0:31:55.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.35,0:31:56.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.30,0:32:13.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.65,0:32:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.35,0:32:21.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.20,0:32:24.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要和媽媽接吻
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.10,0:32:27.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.40,0:32:30.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.45,0:32:34.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.15,0:32:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.95,0:32:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.45,0:32:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.25,0:32:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.15,0:32:48.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.40,0:32:54.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.50,0:33:02.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.95,0:33:12.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.90,0:33:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.25,0:33:16.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 大介
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.70,0:33:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.90,0:33:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.00,0:33:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.95,0:33:48.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.35,0:33:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.45,0:33:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.45,0:33:58.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.55,0:34:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.05,0:34:05.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.25,0:34:09.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.05,0:34:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.19,0:34:14.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.60,0:34:17.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.35,0:34:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.00,0:34:28.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害\N不行了 去了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.15,0:34:31.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.10,0:34:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.94,0:34:37.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不能這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.25,0:34:54.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.19,0:34:57.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好濕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.80,0:34:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.90,0:35:05.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.55,0:35:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.55,0:35:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡好熱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.00,0:35:16.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.00,0:35:19.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.80,0:35:21.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大哦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.75,0:35:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.25,0:35:30.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.35,0:35:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.75,0:35:38.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.50,0:35:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.90,0:35:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.30,0:35:49.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.40,0:35:51.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.45,0:36:19.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.10,0:36:24.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.05,0:36:27.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.60,0:36:29.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腰動起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.95,0:36:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好激烈哦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.40,0:36:38.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深處
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.45,0:36:43.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深處好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.25,0:36:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頂到深處了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.60,0:36:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.25,0:36:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.90,0:36:56.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.25,0:37:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.10,0:37:23.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.30,0:37:25.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.05,0:37:29.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.45,0:37:37.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.10,0:37:42.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.45,0:37:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.85,0:37:48.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.30,0:37:55.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.70,0:38:00.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.65,0:38:06.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.90,0:38:13.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.55,0:38:15.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.65,0:38:25.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從後面插入了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.95,0:38:42.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.35,0:38:50.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.15,0:38:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.35,0:39:02.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.30,0:39:04.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.20,0:39:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.20,0:39:56.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.00,0:39:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.40,0:40:00.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.80,0:40:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.20,0:40:05.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.70,0:40:06.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.95,0:40:21.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.65,0:40:23.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.65,0:40:26.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.00,0:40:28.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 大介
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.55,0:40:30.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.65,0:40:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.75,0:40:43.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.85,0:40:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.40,0:40:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.10,0:40:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.80,0:40:54.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.25,0:41:03.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.80,0:41:06.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.45,0:41:10.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.70,0:41:12.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.95,0:41:44.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.80,0:41:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.15,0:41:52.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.45,0:41:55.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.70,0:42:19.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我遲到了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:25.05,0:42:28.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,週四我有特別的接待
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.95,0:42:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.60,0:43:07.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電視劇準備開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:09.15,0:43:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.65,0:43:50.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.15,0:43:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.40,0:43:54.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:44:16.65,0:44:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.75,0:44:19.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.45,0:44:22.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到這邊來
Dialogue: 0,0:44:27.60,0:44:28.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:44:29.25,0:44:30.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.60,0:44:31.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想斡什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.10,0:44:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.20,0:44:35.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:36.45,0:44:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安靜點就沒事了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.30,0:44:40.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:44:51.30,0:44:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.95,0:44:56.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和媽媽接吻最興奮了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:06.75,0:45:07.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.10,0:45:33.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.60,0:45:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:45:35.10,0:45:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.50,0:45:38.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:51.45,0:45:53.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能繼績了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:14.55,0:46:15.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:18.00,0:46:19.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:46:36.90,0:46:37.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:54.45,0:46:55.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:10.65,0:47:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:32.85,0:47:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:47:42.45,0:47:43.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:47:44.55,0:47:45.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:48:10.65,0:48:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:48:18.00,0:48:19.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:48:21.00,0:48:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:48:22.35,0:48:23.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:49:30.90,0:49:31.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:50:08.70,0:50:09.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:50:47.70,0:50:48.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.10,0:50:51.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:51:26.85,0:51:28.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:52:03.15,0:52:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:54:38.10,0:54:39.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:16.35,0:55:17.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:56:06.00,0:56:07.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:56:08.85,0:56:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:56:11.25,0:56:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 這個不行
Dialogue: 0,0:56:13.50,0:56:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個不行
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.20,0:56:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸會發現的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:17.85,0:56:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:20.10,0:56:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:36.30,0:56:37.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伸出舌頭
Dialogue: 0,0:56:42.45,0:56:43.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:56:44.40,0:56:45.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:48.00,0:56:49.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:56:51.15,0:56:52.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:53.40,0:56:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:56:56.40,0:56:58.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是母子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:56:59.10,0:57:00.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:57:01.05,0:57:02.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:57:04.95,0:57:06.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:07.05,0:57:07.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,0:57:08.55,0:57:09.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手吧 拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:09.90,0:57:10.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:57:14.10,0:57:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:57:16.50,0:57:18.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:57:29.70,0:57:30.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:32.85,0:57:34.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:57:35.40,0:57:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:58:16.50,0:58:17.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:58:21.15,0:58:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:58:42.90,0:58:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:59:04.95,0:59:05.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:59:16.95,0:59:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:25.20,0:59:26.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好激烈哦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:35.40,0:59:36.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:43.05,0:59:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:00:02.70,1:00:03.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 要射了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:12.45,1:00:13.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:36.75,1:00:37.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:00:38.55,1:00:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:00:40.50,1:00:42.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許會被爸爸發現的
Dialogue: 0,1:00:43.20,1:00:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點回去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:00:48.45,1:00:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道這是不對的
Dialogue: 0,1:00:51.90,1:00:53.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我忍不住
Dialogue: 0,1:01:05.55,1:01:06.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:01:06.75,1:01:07.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:09.30,1:01:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有啦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:14.40,1:01:16.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 我們走吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:17.40,1:01:18.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出門了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:19.80,1:01:20.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢走
Dialogue: 0,1:01:22.35,1:01:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:25.65,1:01:29.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之後 我們
Dialogue: 0,1:01:30.15,1:01:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有保持關係
Dialogue: 0,1:02:09.00,1:02:11.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有在電視劇接吻的時候
Dialogue: 0,1:02:13.65,1:02:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們忘記是母子
Dialogue: 0,1:02:16.50,1:02:18.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相渴望著對方
Dialogue: 0,1:03:01.35,1:03:02.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:03:04.05,1:03:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我們親熱地接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,1:03:09.90,1:03:10.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:03:31.95,1:03:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:03:34.65,1:03:36.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經潰敗了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:37.65,1:03:38.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:03:39.00,1:03:40.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到什麼了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:41.10,1:03:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴媽媽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:03:45.90,1:03:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的腦子裡面潰敗了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:51.30,1:03:53.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是很舒服的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,1:03:57.00,1:03:58.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊 媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:04:08.85,1:04:09.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:04:11.10,1:04:12.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽也
Dialogue: 0,1:04:13.65,1:04:15.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽也潰敗了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:33.15,1:04:34.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣
Dialogue: 0,1:04:36.45,1:04:37.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看著媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:04:38.10,1:04:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,1:04:52.20,1:04:52.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:04:53.85,1:04:55.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡也潰敗了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:05:07.35,1:05:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把舌頭伸出來
Dialogue: 0,1:05:55.50,1:05:56.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:05:56.85,1:05:57.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:06:37.20,1:06:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:06:48.60,1:06:49.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:00.75,1:07:01.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:07:53.25,1:07:54.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:07:56.10,1:07:57.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頂到了
Dialogue: 0,1:10:30.30,1:10:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每週四都要愉快才行哦
Dialogue: 0,1:10:52.50,1:10:53.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彩香
Dialogue: 0,1:10:55.20,1:10:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝妳
Dialogue: 0,1:10:57.75,1:10:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,1:10:59.70,1:11:02.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝妳照顧大介
Dialogue: 0,1:11:06.60,1:11:07.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,1:11:08.25,1:11:10.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一直一個人
Dialogue: 0,1:11:11.25,1:11:12.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常感謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:11:26.25,1:11:27.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:11:27.45,1:11:28.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:39.60,1:11:40.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個
Dialogue: 0,1:11:41.70,1:11:46.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再和媽媽一起看電視劇了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:49.20,1:11:50.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,1:11:52.95,1:11:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們
Dialogue: 0,1:11:56.40,1:11:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是母子呢
Dialogue: 0,1:11:59.40,1:12:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是大介的媽媽呀
Dialogue: 0,1:12:06.00,1:12:07.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧
Dialogue: 0,1:12:09.15,1:12:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個
Dialogue: 0,1:12:15.15,1:12:15.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:24.00,1:12:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天一起看電視劇吧
Dialogue: 0,1:12:28.65,1:12:31.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公司的事情處理完了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:32.10,1:12:33.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三人一起看電視吧
Dialogue: 0,1:12:37.20,1:12:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三人一起嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:13:30.45,1:13:31.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個電視劇真有趣啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:42.60,1:13:43.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:15:07.20,1:15:08.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,1:15:11.70,1:15:12.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,1:15:39.00,1:15:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:15:59.25,1:16:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊 媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:16:18.15,1:16:18.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:16:34.35,1:16:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:16:36.00,1:16:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:16:47.70,1:16:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直好想做哦
Dialogue: 0,1:16:50.55,1:16:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直很想做嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:16:56.55,1:16:57.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和媽媽做這種事
Dialogue: 0,1:16:59.10,1:17:00.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在想像嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:17:12.90,1:17:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:17:15.45,1:17:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽之前說了過分的話
Dialogue: 0,1:17:21.90,1:17:27.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽還是最喜歡大介
Dialogue: 0,1:17:30.00,1:17:33.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以忘記媧媽說的話吧
Dialogue: 0,1:17:34.95,1:17:37.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不會討厭媽媽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:17:39.15,1:17:40.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會討厭的
Dialogue: 0,1:17:43.05,1:17:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,1:17:44.25,1:17:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:17:56.40,1:17:57.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:17:58.50,1:17:59.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很興奮吧
Dialogue: 0,1:18:01.20,1:18:02.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:18:06.75,1:18:07.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:18:11.70,1:18:12.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:18:13.65,1:18:14.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡
Dialogue: 0,1:18:17.25,1:18:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大集結
Dialogue: 0,1:18:19.20,1:18:23.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡 大介這裡
Dialogue: 0,1:18:27.60,1:18:28.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:18:29.10,1:18:30.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩擦媽媽的這裡哦
Dialogue: 0,1:18:34.95,1:18:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好暖哦 大介
Dialogue: 0,1:18:40.05,1:18:42.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 很興奮吧
Dialogue: 0,1:18:43.20,1:18:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,1:18:44.70,1:18:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,1:18:47.10,1:18:49.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽也忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,1:18:50.70,1:18:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個
Dialogue: 0,1:18:56.10,1:18:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:18.75,1:19:19.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:19:20.10,1:19:20.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡
Dialogue: 0,1:19:24.45,1:19:25.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡不可以
Dialogue: 0,1:19:25.80,1:19:27.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡好舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:29.25,1:19:30.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:19:31.35,1:19:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看這邊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:42.30,1:19:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在好興奮哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:46.50,1:19:47.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:49.50,1:19:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:51.45,1:19:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:20:07.50,1:20:08.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把舌頭伸出來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:20:14.25,1:20:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對
Dialogue: 0,1:20:22.35,1:20:23.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:20:23.70,1:20:24.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃
Dialogue: 0,1:20:24.90,1:20:25.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,1:20:34.35,1:20:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽 更多
Dialogue: 0,1:20:35.55,1:20:37.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我吃妳的口水吧
Dialogue: 0,1:20:38.40,1:20:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想吃嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:20:42.00,1:20:43.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,張開嘴吧
Dialogue: 0,1:20:46.05,1:20:47.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃進去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:20:49.80,1:20:51.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃嗎\N很好吃
Dialogue: 0,1:20:55.05,1:20:57.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:21:00.15,1:21:00.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:21:01.80,1:21:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃進去了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:21:09.75,1:21:11.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很漂亮的舌頭呢
Dialogue: 0,1:21:22.20,1:21:24.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介把舌顧伸出來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:21:27.60,1:21:30.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓媽媽吃可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:21:48.00,1:21:48.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦好
Dialogue: 0,1:21:49.20,1:21:50.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:21:50.85,1:21:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:21:52.05,1:21:53.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:21:58.50,1:22:00.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直好想這樣做哦
Dialogue: 0,1:22:02.10,1:22:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:22:03.75,1:22:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽也是
Dialogue: 0,1:22:06.15,1:22:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直好想這麼做
Dialogue: 0,1:22:09.75,1:22:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽很喜歡大介
Dialogue: 0,1:22:41.70,1:22:42.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:22:43.80,1:22:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:22:48.60,1:22:49.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:22:50.85,1:22:53.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:22:57.30,1:22:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:23:07.50,1:23:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:23:12.00,1:23:13.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:23:14.40,1:23:16.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頂到了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:23:49.80,1:23:50.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:24:01.05,1:24:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:24:09.00,1:24:09.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:24:11.70,1:24:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想看媽媽的裡面吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:14.10,1:24:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想看
Dialogue: 0,1:24:15.45,1:24:16.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想看\N可以看哦
Dialogue: 0,1:24:28.05,1:24:28.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:24:29.85,1:24:32.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓媽媽看這個吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:33.60,1:24:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓媽媽看看變得怎麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,1:24:37.20,1:24:38.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以嗎\N可以哦
Dialogue: 0,1:24:46.05,1:24:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介的氣味
Dialogue: 0,1:24:49.05,1:24:49.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:51.30,1:24:52.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不害羞的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:53.40,1:24:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:55.65,1:24:56.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓媽媽看吧
Dialogue: 0,1:25:09.90,1:25:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得這麼硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:13.95,1:25:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:25:20.70,1:25:21.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:25:29.55,1:25:30.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:25:50.55,1:25:52.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:25:54.15,1:25:55.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:25:56.55,1:25:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:26:00.15,1:26:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:26:19.20,1:26:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:26:41.10,1:26:42.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個
Dialogue: 0,1:26:48.90,1:26:49.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:27:17.55,1:27:18.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:27:52.50,1:27:55.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽舔了很多呢
Dialogue: 0,1:27:59.40,1:28:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼績舔吧
Dialogue: 0,1:28:03.00,1:28:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要繼續舔嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:28:06.60,1:28:07.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:28:45.60,1:28:46.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:29:10.35,1:29:11.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:29:30.00,1:29:31.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我更舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:29:32.85,1:29:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:29:46.65,1:29:47.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:30:00.60,1:30:02.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 這樣好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:30:15.75,1:30:16.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:30:26.10,1:30:26.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:30:34.80,1:30:35.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:30:36.00,1:30:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:30:37.35,1:30:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:30:43.35,1:30:44.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:30:48.60,1:30:49.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:30:50.85,1:30:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要停下來
Dialogue: 0,1:31:13.05,1:31:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:31:14.55,1:31:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:31:29.55,1:31:30.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:31:30.75,1:31:31.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:31:45.75,1:31:47.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:31:47.85,1:31:49.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:31:50.40,1:31:51.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:31:59.70,1:32:00.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:17.70,1:32:18.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:24.90,1:32:25.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:32:33.45,1:32:34.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:38.40,1:32:39.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:40.05,1:32:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦 不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:32:42.00,1:32:43.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:32:43.95,1:32:46.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得好清楚哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:47.10,1:32:49.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:33:05.85,1:33:06.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:33:27.45,1:33:28.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:33:30.45,1:33:31.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:33:33.15,1:33:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡好熟哦
Dialogue: 0,1:33:34.95,1:33:37.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:33:55.80,1:33:56.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:34:01.95,1:34:02.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:34:04.80,1:34:06.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:34:12.00,1:34:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相舔吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:14.25,1:34:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:34:19.95,1:34:21.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:25.95,1:34:26.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:34:53.55,1:34:54.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:35:07.80,1:35:08.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:35:12.45,1:35:13.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:35:33.45,1:35:34.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:35:34.65,1:35:36.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:35:44.40,1:35:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:35:55.80,1:35:56.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:35:57.60,1:35:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:04.95,1:36:06.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:36:15.00,1:36:15.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:36:20.10,1:36:21.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:36:22.05,1:36:23.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:36:38.10,1:36:39.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:40.20,1:36:41.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:37:05.25,1:37:06.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:37:09.15,1:37:10.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:37:20.40,1:37:21.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:37:23.10,1:37:24.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽那裡好舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,1:37:28.95,1:37:29.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:37:30.90,1:37:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡好暖哦
Dialogue: 0,1:37:38.55,1:37:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:37:41.55,1:37:42.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:37:50.55,1:37:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:37:52.65,1:37:54.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:37:55.80,1:37:56.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:38:13.95,1:38:14.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:38:15.90,1:38:17.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:38:19.35,1:38:21.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,1:38:22.20,1:38:23.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:38:25.35,1:38:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:38:27.90,1:38:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,1:38:32.55,1:38:33.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以插入嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:38:39.15,1:38:40.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣摩擦嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:38:41.55,1:38:42.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣摩擦嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:38:56.10,1:38:57.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:39:00.75,1:39:01.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:39:06.00,1:39:06.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:39:10.05,1:39:11.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:39:17.85,1:39:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴好緊哦
Dialogue: 0,1:39:19.95,1:39:20.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:39:22.80,1:39:23.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:39:30.15,1:39:30.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:39:32.55,1:39:33.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:39:34.65,1:39:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進媽媽小穴裡面了
Dialogue: 0,1:39:36.75,1:39:37.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:39:38.55,1:39:40.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得好大哦
Dialogue: 0,1:39:41.70,1:39:42.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:39:53.40,1:39:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:39:58.95,1:40:01.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進去了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:40:03.15,1:40:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:40:22.50,1:40:23.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:40:26.70,1:40:28.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:40:28.65,1:40:30.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:40:38.70,1:40:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:40:54.45,1:40:55.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:40:57.00,1:40:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:40:58.65,1:41:00.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:00.75,1:41:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:03.75,1:41:05.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得好大哦
Dialogue: 0,1:41:06.45,1:41:07.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:41:08.85,1:41:09.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:41:19.20,1:41:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:20.70,1:41:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:25.35,1:41:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:26.85,1:41:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:28.65,1:41:30.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:31.50,1:41:32.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:36.15,1:41:37.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:41:38.40,1:41:39.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:40.65,1:41:43.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:43.80,1:41:44.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:49.20,1:41:49.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:50.40,1:41:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:54.75,1:41:55.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:41:56.25,1:41:58.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:41:59.85,1:42:02.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介的肉棒好硬哦
Dialogue: 0,1:42:02.85,1:42:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好硬哦
Dialogue: 0,1:42:05.40,1:42:07.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進媽媽小穴裡面了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:07.95,1:42:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:42:11.40,1:42:12.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:42:12.90,1:42:13.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:42:18.75,1:42:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:20.55,1:42:23.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:23.25,1:42:24.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:24.90,1:42:26.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:29.40,1:42:30.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:32.10,1:42:33.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:34.35,1:42:35.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:42:36.90,1:42:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:42:43.50,1:42:44.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:45.15,1:42:46.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:47.10,1:42:48.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:49.65,1:42:51.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:51.45,1:42:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:54.75,1:42:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:42:56.85,1:42:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:01.65,1:43:02.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:03.45,1:43:04.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:43:09.45,1:43:10.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:12.30,1:43:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:43:15.00,1:43:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還要繼續
Dialogue: 0,1:43:18.75,1:43:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:25.50,1:43:26.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:27.00,1:43:28.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:29.70,1:43:30.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:31.50,1:43:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:35.70,1:43:36.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:43:37.50,1:43:38.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:43.05,1:43:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:43:45.30,1:43:46.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:43:47.25,1:43:49.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:49.65,1:43:51.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:59.85,1:44:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:44:03.45,1:44:04.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:05.40,1:44:07.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:08.85,1:44:10.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:44:14.10,1:44:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:17.10,1:44:18.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:28.20,1:44:28.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:44:32.40,1:44:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:35.40,1:44:37.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介 不可以
Dialogue: 0,1:44:38.40,1:44:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 不可以
Dialogue: 0,1:44:41.10,1:44:42.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:43.35,1:44:44.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:45.15,1:44:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:50.40,1:44:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:52.50,1:44:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:44:54.75,1:44:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:58.05,1:44:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:01.95,1:45:03.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:45:03.30,1:45:05.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好大哦
Dialogue: 0,1:45:05.40,1:45:06.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大哦
Dialogue: 0,1:45:06.90,1:45:08.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:45:18.45,1:45:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:45:23.40,1:45:24.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插入深處了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:27.45,1:45:29.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:35.70,1:45:36.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:45:37.05,1:45:38.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:45:38.70,1:45:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:45:40.80,1:45:42.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:45:42.90,1:45:44.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:45:45.00,1:45:46.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:51.30,1:45:53.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:45:54.60,1:45:56.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡
Dialogue: 0,1:45:56.85,1:45:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡
Dialogue: 0,1:45:58.50,1:46:00.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡 那裡
Dialogue: 0,1:46:01.20,1:46:03.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:46:07.95,1:46:09.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:46:09.75,1:46:11.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:46:12.90,1:46:14.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡
Dialogue: 0,1:46:15.30,1:46:18.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:46:19.50,1:46:21.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:46:22.65,1:46:24.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:46:34.65,1:46:35.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:46:36.75,1:46:37.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:46:49.35,1:46:50.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:46:55.35,1:46:56.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:46:58.05,1:46:59.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:01.05,1:47:02.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要變得奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:05.85,1:47:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:47:22.65,1:47:23.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:48:31.50,1:48:32.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:48:47.55,1:48:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:48:49.95,1:48:51.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:07.35,1:49:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:49:09.30,1:49:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:49:10.80,1:49:12.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:49:12.00,1:49:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:49:23.10,1:49:24.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:49:26.55,1:49:28.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:49:31.80,1:49:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:33.90,1:49:34.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:37.50,1:49:38.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:49:39.75,1:49:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:57.75,1:49:58.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:50:04.80,1:50:05.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:50:06.30,1:50:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:09.45,1:50:10.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深處好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:50:11.85,1:50:14.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頂到舒服的地方了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:17.25,1:50:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:50:19.95,1:50:21.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:28.65,1:50:29.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:50:36.00,1:50:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:50:39.45,1:50:40.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:50:41.40,1:50:42.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:50:42.75,1:50:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好硬哦
Dialogue: 0,1:50:50.85,1:50:51.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:54.00,1:50:54.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:57.00,1:50:57.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:50:58.80,1:50:59.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:51:02.25,1:51:03.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:51:04.35,1:51:06.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:51:07.50,1:51:08.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:51:18.90,1:51:19.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:51:25.20,1:51:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:51:27.90,1:51:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:51:30.45,1:51:31.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:51:35.85,1:51:36.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:51:38.40,1:51:39.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:51:39.90,1:51:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:51:42.00,1:51:43.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大介
Dialogue: 0,1:51:43.65,1:51:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大哦
Dialogue: 0,1:51:45.45,1:51:46.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大哦
Dialogue: 0,1:51:47.25,1:51:48.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深處
Dialogue: 0,1:51:49.20,1:51:50.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深處
Dialogue: 0,1:51:58.95,1:51:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:02.55,1:52:03.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:52:05.25,1:52:06.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:07.35,1:52:08.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:11.55,1:52:12.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:16.65,1:52:17.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:52:20.85,1:52:21.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:22.95,1:52:24.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:25.20,1:52:27.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:28.20,1:52:29.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:33.60,1:52:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:43.50,1:52:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:52:45.15,1:52:47.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:47.55,1:52:49.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:50.85,1:52:52.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熱哦
Dialogue: 0,1:52:53.10,1:52:55.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:57.00,1:52:57.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:53:52.05,1:53:53.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射在裡面了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:53:55.20,1:53:56.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射很多出來了
Dialogue: 0,1:53:58.50,1:53:59.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:54:24.75,1:54:25.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是廣告
Dialogue: 0,1:54:26.85,1:54:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電視劇終於快結束了
Dialogue: 0,1:54:31.05,1:54:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不錯的電視劇
Dialogue: 0,1:54:37.50,1:54:38.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:54:41.10,1:54:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去做晚飯
Dialogue: 0,1:54:46.20,1:54:47.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也去幫忙
Dialogue: 0,1:55:12.15,1:55:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廣告結束了
Dialogue: 0,1:55:16.95,1:55:17.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,1:55:18.45,1:55:19.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我馬上來
Dialogue: 0,1:55:33.30,1:55:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(主演 牧村彩香)

