[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.12,0:00:07.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(Madonna出品)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.92,0:00:42.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(彩票中獎金額100億元)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.17,0:00:45.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表達一下你的感想
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.07,0:00:48.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界會改變
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.77,0:00:52.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這麼簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.37,0:00:57.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我1周前只有吃飯的錢了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.77,0:01:00.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你錢怎麼用啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.07,0:01:04.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個啊 我想想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.82,0:01:13.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會存錢的 不過這次買了\N很多東西哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.67,0:01:19.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 剩下的錢呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.02,0:01:23.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.72,0:01:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要嘗試之前沒做的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.62,0:01:35.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-各種各樣的事情啊  -謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.27,0:01:38.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(中100億元的話題)\N(很快在日本傳開)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.67,0:01:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(撿100億男人於十美女)\N(人生逆轉的後宮生活)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.07,0:02:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好帥氣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.12,0:03:20.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.87,0:03:21.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.67,0:03:26.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都為了我而來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.62,0:03:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.57,0:03:35.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.27,0:03:38.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老實說大家要錢吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.47,0:03:40.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老實說大家要錢吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.37,0:03:43.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.32,0:03:51.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼等下就好好享受啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.47,0:03:56.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我生活就好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.72,0:04:02.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會娶讓找最舒服的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.42,0:04:12.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當我的妻子哦 大家要加油哦\N好好服侍我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.17,0:04:14.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.87,0:04:19.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.92,0:04:57.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.07,0:05:00.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.87,0:05:10.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.72,0:05:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個感覺真是太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.87,0:05:20.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.27,0:05:29.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太客氣了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.22,0:05:33.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼想跟我結婚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.77,0:05:38.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我一直這麼想的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.42,0:05:44.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧 我都不相信啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.72,0:05:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你別這麼說 開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.07,0:05:54.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧你 這麼著急啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.37,0:05:57.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個感覺如何
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.97,0:06:18.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.27,0:06:21.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.92,0:06:24.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要繼續嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.57,0:06:58.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.67,0:06:59.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.97,0:07:02.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.72,0:07:03.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.07,0:07:05.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.02,0:07:10.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,機會難得 我想看小穴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.42,0:07:13.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.62,0:07:15.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.92,0:07:16.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.37,0:07:16.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.97,0:07:17.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.32,0:07:28.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這個感覺如何啊  -真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.82,0:07:42.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.22,0:07:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種飯太好吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.42,0:07:50.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就繼續享受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.37,0:07:55.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.62,0:08:01.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很難受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.47,0:08:11.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺好奇怪哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.82,0:08:28.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 這麼搞
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.07,0:08:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我的小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.27,0:08:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我的小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.27,0:08:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.67,0:09:05.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很有感覺哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.17,0:09:10.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.72,0:09:31.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.12,0:09:35.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.32,0:09:41.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.57,0:09:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.42,0:10:01.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼想看嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.12,0:10:14.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡會很好吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.97,0:10:19.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.87,0:10:26.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吃我們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.82,0:10:33.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.07,0:10:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就恭敬不如從命了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.47,0:10:41.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.97,0:10:52.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從你閉始嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.07,0:10:57.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-開動了哦  -好的 謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.72,0:11:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.62,0:11:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得很大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.22,0:11:46.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的嘴巴 好吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.37,0:11:49.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.82,0:11:52.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.67,0:12:12.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很在意你的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.47,0:12:18.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的是嗎  -我之前就喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.37,0:12:23.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我都知道的  -是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.47,0:12:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好來舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.22,0:12:32.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好來舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.22,0:12:48.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.47,0:12:54.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可以舔乳頭嗎  -好評啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.77,0:13:48.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫蕩的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.22,0:13:54.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.12,0:13:57.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.07,0:14:03.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.37,0:14:06.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.12,0:14:16.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特別為你準備的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.62,0:14:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.12,0:14:33.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.62,0:15:03.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.42,0:15:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然這樣子的話 我要刺激的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.27,0:15:19.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿足你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.92,0:15:42.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.17,0:16:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.72,0:16:46.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清晨就很精神
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.77,0:17:40.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛液出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.12,0:18:16.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還要嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.32,0:18:22.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就滿足你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.97,0:18:28.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.37,0:18:32.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.97,0:18:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開動了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.37,0:18:45.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開動了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.72,0:18:57.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.47,0:19:16.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-舒服嗎  -好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.37,0:19:19.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那繼續啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.07,0:19:22.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.07,0:19:27.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.27,0:19:31.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我興奮了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.22,0:19:35.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.17,0:19:59.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來摸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.57,0:20:16.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.67,0:20:19.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.57,0:20:40.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放鬆哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.97,0:20:45.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢弄我們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.77,0:20:50.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續欺負我們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.62,0:20:56.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.07,0:21:03.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了啊 不要高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.52,0:21:07.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.07,0:21:39.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼濕了啊 屁股對著我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.52,0:21:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.07,0:22:19.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很舒服啊  -好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.07,0:22:27.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.32,0:22:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.97,0:23:12.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.52,0:23:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.62,0:23:25.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽話一起來吧 很好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.17,0:24:08.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.17,0:24:12.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們要的是這個吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.37,0:24:25.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都給你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.82,0:25:10.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來讓我舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.57,0:25:14.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.32,0:25:33.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.97,0:25:53.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想成為我的女人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.52,0:25:59.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕緊來配合吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.07,0:26:19.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.27,0:26:20.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.02,0:26:21.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.87,0:26:39.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧 這個東西
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.87,0:26:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.47,0:27:19.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真是舒服啊  -是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.12,0:27:24.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.92,0:28:15.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.57,0:28:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.42,0:28:29.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放鬆吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.27,0:28:31.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.27,0:28:34.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.97,0:28:51.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看小穴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.12,0:29:00.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.47,0:29:10.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狠舒服吧 來了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.77,0:29:28.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.47,0:29:34.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個Lil Ghost小鬼\N好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.92,0:29:37.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個Lil Ghost小鬼\N好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.97,0:29:38.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個Lil Ghost小鬼\N好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.37,0:29:43.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.77,0:29:46.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.12,0:29:48.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.52,0:30:03.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊  這個
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.57,0:30:06.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.62,0:30:06.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.92,0:30:07.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.67,0:30:19.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.87,0:30:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.62,0:30:36.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.07,0:30:39.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.47,0:30:46.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次換我來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.97,0:30:48.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次換我來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.02,0:30:59.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.07,0:31:07.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.67,0:31:14.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還想要是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.72,0:31:19.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 我高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.37,0:31:21.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.12,0:31:25.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.57,0:31:30.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.87,0:31:42.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-讓我高潮吧  -再說一次
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.17,0:31:42.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-讓我高潮吧  -再說一次
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.32,0:31:46.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-讓我高潮吧  -再說一次
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.27,0:31:53.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了 讓我小穴高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.87,0:32:00.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.37,0:32:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.57,0:32:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.77,0:32:27.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.52,0:32:31.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就插進去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.97,0:32:45.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還想要吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.67,0:32:49.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.22,0:32:57.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.17,0:33:45.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.42,0:34:04.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.97,0:34:07.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我感受一下
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.17,0:34:30.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來輪到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.07,0:34:33.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來輪到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.92,0:34:39.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.02,0:34:43.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.37,0:34:43.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.97,0:35:17.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺如何啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.67,0:35:45.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.62,0:35:50.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡好舒服啊 好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.57,0:36:22.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.07,0:36:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊 這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.22,0:36:41.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.87,0:36:42.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.97,0:36:53.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.72,0:36:55.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.27,0:37:01.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小穴高潮了 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.47,0:37:22.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.27,0:37:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.47,0:38:02.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.52,0:38:48.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.37,0:39:04.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工程車 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.07,0:39:39.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉過去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.52,0:40:36.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.27,0:41:04.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.47,0:42:00.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.37,0:42:02.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.42,0:42:13.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:22.07,0:42:25.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要來了  -好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:42:42.77,0:42:45.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要繼續嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.62,0:43:00.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.87,0:43:07.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺很舒服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.82,0:43:10.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺很舒服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.02,0:43:18.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.17,0:43:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:43:50.72,0:43:51.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.77,0:43:52.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:52.97,0:43:53.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.42,0:43:53.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:57.47,0:43:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:59.87,0:44:03.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.22,0:44:10.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.82,0:44:10.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.12,0:44:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:45:00.62,0:45:05.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股對著我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.37,0:45:38.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.42,0:46:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:26.12,0:46:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:28.37,0:46:28.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:29.42,0:46:31.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.47,0:46:36.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我射了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:53.87,0:46:56.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:01.07,0:47:03.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了這麼多
Dialogue: 0,0:47:03.62,0:47:05.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:28.22,0:47:30.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:53.87,0:47:55.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:48:01.67,0:48:05.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮了啊 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.07,0:48:15.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我射了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.97,0:48:48.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何
Dialogue: 0,0:48:49.22,0:48:52.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實在太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:52.82,0:48:56.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕緊來吃我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:56.87,0:48:59.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是賞給你們的
Dialogue: 0,0:49:00.77,0:49:03.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:45.62,0:49:50.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你們說個好消息
Dialogue: 0,0:49:50.87,0:49:59.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個房間裡面\N有一億元的獎勵存在
Dialogue: 0,0:49:59.72,0:50:03.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家找找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:50:10.97,0:50:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果
Dialogue: 0,0:50:13.22,0:50:15.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最先找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:15.47,0:50:21.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就會給她一億元
Dialogue: 0,0:50:23.57,0:50:27.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 好刺激
Dialogue: 0,0:50:29.12,0:50:37.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果沒有找到的哦\N會失去收錢的前路
Dialogue: 0,0:50:37.97,0:50:43.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是這樣  -別這樣子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:50:43.97,0:50:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就準備開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:50:49.97,0:50:54.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果找到的話
Dialogue: 0,0:50:54.77,0:50:58.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有特別的獎勵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:50:59.12,0:51:02.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好好加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:51:04.37,0:51:06.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:51:06.77,0:51:08.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:09.17,0:51:10.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點哦
Dialogue: 0,0:51:24.62,0:51:27.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好忍住哦
Dialogue: 0,0:51:34.52,0:51:40.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在附近也許哦
Dialogue: 0,0:51:56.42,0:51:59.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能高潮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:52:01.22,0:52:03.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要
Dialogue: 0,0:52:04.07,0:52:05.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:52:12.02,0:52:15.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊好可疑哦
Dialogue: 0,0:52:15.77,0:52:19.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那裡對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:34.07,0:52:37.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:50.27,0:52:56.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮的話就失去資格哦
Dialogue: 0,0:53:01.97,0:53:06.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽明白了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.17,0:53:11.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我重複嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:53:11.57,0:53:13.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:53:14.42,0:53:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:37.37,0:53:39.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:39.77,0:53:44.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 我要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:44.27,0:53:47.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有知道你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:53:51.47,0:53:54.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太可愛了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:54.92,0:53:59.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都沒想到現在是這樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:53:59.87,0:54:05.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過有機會的話
Dialogue: 0,0:54:32.57,0:54:34.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:54:41.57,0:54:43.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:44.72,0:54:47.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你摸什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:54:47.27,0:54:51.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要忍住哦
Dialogue: 0,0:54:52.97,0:54:55.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心我沒收哦
Dialogue: 0,0:55:06.77,0:55:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:11.87,0:55:14.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是聰明啊
Dialogue: 0,0:55:27.92,0:55:29.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:55:30.17,0:55:32.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就給你特殊
Dialogue: 0,0:55:33.02,0:55:37.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,獎勵可以吧 好好釋放吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:56.72,0:56:01.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能亂來哦 知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:56:03.32,0:56:05.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:56:05.87,0:56:08.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:56:25.67,0:56:28.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:57:11.88,0:57:15.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:19.08,0:57:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:57:22.08,0:57:24.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不做的話
Dialogue: 0,0:57:24.48,0:57:29.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不要出現在我的面前\N知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:29.28,0:57:33.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要趁現在好好表現哦
Dialogue: 0,0:58:14.88,0:58:17.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:58:22.98,0:58:25.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:58:30.63,0:58:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:58:57.33,0:58:59.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:11.43,0:59:15.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能客氣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:17.13,0:59:19.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:24.48,0:59:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:59:30.33,0:59:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:04.38,1:01:05.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:01:11.28,1:01:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要舔 我也要
Dialogue: 0,1:01:14.58,1:01:18.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-讓我舔一下  -不行哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:18.93,1:01:22.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的 只能看哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:23.28,1:01:25.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:25.98,1:01:30.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要舔啊  -不行的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:33.03,1:01:35.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,1:01:35.58,1:01:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要舔啊  -真的是嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:01:40.68,1:01:48.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以舔嗎 這個 真是好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:00.03,1:02:03.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太狡猾了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:05.43,1:02:07.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:09.63,1:02:12.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:13.08,1:02:15.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:17.43,1:02:19.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:02:32.43,1:02:35.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個不行哦
Dialogue: 0,1:02:45.78,1:02:47.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:48.63,1:02:53.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:02:56.43,1:02:57.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好哦
Dialogue: 0,1:02:58.08,1:02:58.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好哦
Dialogue: 0,1:03:05.58,1:03:09.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要舔啊 這個
Dialogue: 0,1:03:14.13,1:03:15.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:15.93,1:03:16.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:27.18,1:03:31.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-肉棒想要嗎  -我要
Dialogue: 0,1:03:32.13,1:03:32.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:03:35.73,1:03:38.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:03:38.43,1:03:41.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉始吧
Dialogue: 0,1:03:45.48,1:03:47.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,1:03:47.73,1:03:52.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放輕鬆哦 知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:03:52.68,1:03:57.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是要這樣子哦 很棒的
Dialogue: 0,1:04:02.58,1:04:06.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒插進來了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:04:07.53,1:04:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:04:09.63,1:04:12.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:04:12.78,1:04:18.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了哦 來了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:04:31.08,1:04:33.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:04:36.48,1:04:40.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:04:40.83,1:04:43.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:04:51.48,1:04:53.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:05:14.43,1:05:17.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:05:24.18,1:05:27.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:05:28.68,1:05:33.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 就要說哦
Dialogue: 0,1:05:35.88,1:05:38.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:05:43.23,1:05:45.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:05:52.83,1:05:55.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要這個
Dialogue: 0,1:05:55.38,1:05:58.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:01.38,1:06:03.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:04.53,1:06:07.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:19.08,1:06:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:22.83,1:06:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:24.78,1:06:28.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮了 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:06:35.58,1:06:39.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:39.18,1:06:42.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:06:57.33,1:07:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:02.73,1:07:07.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能舔 可以聞一下
Dialogue: 0,1:07:11.88,1:07:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服 淫蕩的感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:19.53,1:07:23.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊 不要
Dialogue: 0,1:07:31.38,1:07:35.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:37.08,1:07:39.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,1:08:16.98,1:08:19.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不行了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:08:24.78,1:08:27.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:08:44.28,1:08:47.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:08:57.78,1:09:01.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:09:09.78,1:09:12.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒的
Dialogue: 0,1:09:30.48,1:09:33.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的棒啊
Dialogue: 0,1:10:04.68,1:10:07.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要不要
Dialogue: 0,1:10:07.38,1:10:09.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:10:10.68,1:10:12.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,1:10:34.98,1:10:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了 好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:10:40.38,1:10:42.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太過分了
Dialogue: 0,1:10:43.83,1:10:49.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能看哦 其他人
Dialogue: 0,1:11:16.98,1:11:20.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,1:11:30.18,1:11:34.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都讓你親了 要忍住哦
Dialogue: 0,1:11:49.53,1:11:54.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個太棒了 我要
Dialogue: 0,1:11:54.78,1:11:55.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:22.08,1:12:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:36.18,1:12:39.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太舒服了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:40.98,1:12:46.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要高潮了 真的不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:02.73,1:13:05.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:08.43,1:13:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣子搞吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:11.58,1:13:12.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣子搞吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:21.18,1:13:23.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:13:24.33,1:13:26.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:27.48,1:13:30.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:54.93,1:13:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:58.08,1:13:58.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:14:03.03,1:14:05.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要射
Dialogue: 0,1:14:07.23,1:14:08.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:14:12.33,1:14:15.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:14:22.68,1:14:25.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:14:26.13,1:14:29.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:14:52.68,1:14:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了啊 就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,1:14:58.68,1:15:01.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來好吧
Dialogue: 0,1:15:02.88,1:15:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:15:16.38,1:15:19.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:15:29.73,1:15:31.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:15:31.83,1:15:36.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這個感覺啊 好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:15:44.28,1:15:48.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,1:15:53.58,1:15:55.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:16:27.93,1:16:32.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 插進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:16:56.43,1:16:59.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我好好忍住哦
Dialogue: 0,1:17:00.03,1:17:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣子吧
Dialogue: 0,1:17:02.88,1:17:08.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們遊戲輸掉了
Dialogue: 0,1:17:09.03,1:17:13.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽到了沒有 給我忍住
Dialogue: 0,1:17:26.58,1:17:30.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:17:30.03,1:17:33.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會明白的
Dialogue: 0,1:17:33.63,1:17:38.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會高潮的 知道了
Dialogue: 0,1:17:38.28,1:17:41.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,1:17:54.18,1:17:56.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:17:57.03,1:17:59.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,1:17:59.58,1:18:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:18:06.78,1:18:09.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很羨慕哦
Dialogue: 0,1:18:09.48,1:18:13.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這個感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,1:18:17.13,1:18:19.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:18:19.53,1:18:23.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:18:25.23,1:18:27.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,1:18:30.03,1:18:35.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是厲害啊 這個感覺
Dialogue: 0,1:18:45.48,1:18:48.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交給我來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:18:48.63,1:18:53.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:19:10.83,1:19:13.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:16.08,1:19:18.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:19.08,1:19:22.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:19:26.43,1:19:28.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:19:29.73,1:19:31.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:32.73,1:19:35.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:41.73,1:19:44.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:54.18,1:19:57.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:59.58,1:20:03.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,1:20:07.08,1:20:10.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:20:12.78,1:20:14.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:20:18.78,1:20:22.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:20:42.93,1:20:45.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,1:20:46.08,1:20:48.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礙事得很
Dialogue: 0,1:20:48.63,1:20:48.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要插啊
Dialogue: 0,1:20:49.23,1:20:49.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要插啊
Dialogue: 0,1:20:49.98,1:20:51.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要插啊
Dialogue: 0,1:20:57.48,1:21:01.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要肉棒 來啊
Dialogue: 0,1:21:01.38,1:21:06.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來啊 插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:21:06.18,1:21:08.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,1:21:22.53,1:21:24.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,1:21:44.13,1:21:48.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好棒的
Dialogue: 0,1:21:58.08,1:22:03.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太厲害了啊 好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:22:06.33,1:22:08.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:22:12.03,1:22:14.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想要嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:22:14.88,1:22:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:22:16.83,1:22:20.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就滿足你吧
Dialogue: 0,1:22:51.63,1:22:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 這個 我還要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:23:08.28,1:23:11.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 輪到我了
Dialogue: 0,1:23:31.68,1:23:33.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:23:34.08,1:23:38.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太完美了
Dialogue: 0,1:23:38.43,1:23:43.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼啊 這樣不行
Dialogue: 0,1:23:43.38,1:23:45.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:23:54.18,1:23:57.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:10.83,1:24:16.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝今天大駕光臨
Dialogue: 0,1:24:16.98,1:24:22.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-久等了  -好好享受吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:23.73,1:24:26.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種銀座NO1啊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:26.73,1:24:33.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太棒了  -謝謝了
Dialogue: 0,1:24:33.03,1:24:36.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我最貴的酒
Dialogue: 0,1:24:36.48,1:24:40.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 沒有問題的
Dialogue: 0,1:24:43.38,1:24:46.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們很期待啊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:46.53,1:24:51.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金身在發光呢 是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:25:13.08,1:25:15.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和您口味嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:25:19.53,1:25:22.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來一杯吧
Dialogue: 0,1:25:43.83,1:25:45.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請吧
Dialogue: 0,1:25:46.68,1:25:50.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受吧
Dialogue: 0,1:25:52.38,1:25:54.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太完美了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:54.93,1:25:57.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然必須得這樣
Dialogue: 0,1:26:08.88,1:26:11.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有我的
Dialogue: 0,1:26:14.28,1:26:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝一杯吧
Dialogue: 0,1:26:40.83,1:26:43.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還合口味吧
Dialogue: 0,1:26:54.18,1:26:59.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的太完美了 客人
Dialogue: 0,1:27:00.63,1:27:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萬中挑一
Dialogue: 0,1:27:03.63,1:27:04.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人
Dialogue: 0,1:27:05.73,1:27:07.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是最棒的
Dialogue: 0,1:27:09.93,1:27:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 感覺好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:27:19.53,1:27:23.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也準備一下吧
Dialogue: 0,1:27:25.98,1:27:28.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實如此啊
Dialogue: 0,1:27:29.28,1:27:32.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪哦
Dialogue: 0,1:27:35.43,1:27:37.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明很期待的
Dialogue: 0,1:27:40.08,1:27:46.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是真的很淫蕩啊
Dialogue: 0,1:27:48.48,1:27:49.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等
Dialogue: 0,1:27:52.68,1:27:54.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫蕩哦
Dialogue: 0,1:27:55.23,1:27:57.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不對
Dialogue: 0,1:27:58.08,1:28:00.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別亂動
Dialogue: 0,1:28:00.63,1:28:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,1:28:03.63,1:28:04.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,1:28:07.38,1:28:10.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我們來做吧
Dialogue: 0,1:28:11.73,1:28:14.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有問題的
Dialogue: 0,1:28:16.08,1:28:22.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好服侍你哦 期待嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:28:33.48,1:28:36.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:28:41.43,1:28:44.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交給我們了
Dialogue: 0,1:28:51.18,1:28:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,1:28:54.03,1:28:57.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尺寸也很完美
Dialogue: 0,1:29:00.93,1:29:03.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子
Dialogue: 0,1:29:05.73,1:29:07.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠻難受的
Dialogue: 0,1:29:07.38,1:29:17.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來確實如此啊\N客人要放鬆哦
Dialogue: 0,1:29:18.48,1:29:27.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事啊 對不起哦\N別在意
Dialogue: 0,1:29:33.63,1:29:36.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,1:29:37.68,1:29:40.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子才對嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:29:45.03,1:29:46.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左撇子嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:29:51.63,1:29:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不對啊
Dialogue: 0,1:29:54.63,1:29:56.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都知道
Dialogue: 0,1:30:01.68,1:30:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太期待了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:30:16.98,1:30:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了啊 沒事的 交給我們
Dialogue: 0,1:30:23.58,1:30:25.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,1:30:32.58,1:30:35.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直完美啊
Dialogue: 0,1:30:35.43,1:30:43.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊 我要試試哦\N是不是太快了
Dialogue: 0,1:30:43.68,1:30:44.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的
Dialogue: 0,1:30:44.28,1:30:45.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的
Dialogue: 0,1:30:46.53,1:30:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕緊開始吧
Dialogue: 0,1:30:49.53,1:30:51.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好吧 真是
Dialogue: 0,1:30:52.53,1:30:54.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:30:54.48,1:30:56.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:30:57.48,1:31:01.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,1:31:02.88,1:31:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可愛的乳頭
Dialogue: 0,1:31:06.48,1:31:09.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都很棒
Dialogue: 0,1:31:20.73,1:31:26.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬邦邦的 好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,1:31:27.48,1:31:31.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你最喜歡的
Dialogue: 0,1:31:41.73,1:31:45.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全感覺不到啊
Dialogue: 0,1:31:47.73,1:31:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼強壯的啊 太棒了\N果然是一流人士啊
Dialogue: 0,1:32:05.28,1:32:07.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我試試
Dialogue: 0,1:32:10.38,1:32:15.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味道也一定很舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:32:21.78,1:32:24.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,1:32:28.83,1:32:30.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來看看
Dialogue: 0,1:32:35.13,1:32:37.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎 這個
Dialogue: 0,1:32:40.83,1:32:42.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:54.03,1:32:54.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,1:32:55.53,1:32:57.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:32:59.13,1:33:01.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們最重視客戶
Dialogue: 0,1:33:01.68,1:33:06.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎麼做都可以
Dialogue: 0,1:33:06.63,1:33:11.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就要開始服務嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:33:18.48,1:33:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是為了客人準備的
Dialogue: 0,1:33:24.78,1:33:26.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣子
Dialogue: 0,1:33:36.03,1:33:39.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺如何啊
Dialogue: 0,1:33:41.43,1:33:42.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別客氣
Dialogue: 0,1:33:42.93,1:33:49.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼感覺都可以說的\N這是我們的服務
Dialogue: 0,1:33:50.88,1:33:55.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會怪罪你的 我也要
Dialogue: 0,1:34:02.73,1:34:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:34:05.13,1:34:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼強壯的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:34:15.93,1:34:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道
Dialogue: 0,1:34:20.73,1:34:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:34:23.43,1:34:28.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:34:32.73,1:34:41.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-媽媽桑你先來啊 穩重\N-我知道 一下子
Dialogue: 0,1:34:54.03,1:34:59.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我來可以吧 是吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:59.13,1:35:01.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就開始了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:35:01.98,1:35:03.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴
Dialogue: 0,1:35:03.78,1:35:06.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開始了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:35:18.33,1:35:20.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太久了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:35:20.73,1:35:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換人
Dialogue: 0,1:35:21.93,1:35:26.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輪到你來了哦 真是討厭
Dialogue: 0,1:35:26.88,1:35:28.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,1:35:28.98,1:35:32.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實很不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,1:35:38.28,1:35:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續
Dialogue: 0,1:35:46.53,1:35:50.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫蕩的馨音
Dialogue: 0,1:36:06.63,1:36:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:36:15.33,1:36:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很明白的
Dialogue: 0,1:36:35.88,1:36:36.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:36:44.88,1:36:46.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽桑
Dialogue: 0,1:36:49.08,1:36:51.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太過分了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:36:54.93,1:36:59.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這麼狡猾啊
Dialogue: 0,1:37:48.18,1:37:51.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是很舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:37:51.93,1:37:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白
Dialogue: 0,1:37:53.43,1:37:58.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交給我來吧 很舒服的
Dialogue: 0,1:37:58.83,1:38:02.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會很喜歡吧
Dialogue: 0,1:38:58.83,1:39:06.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實如此啊 為了夢想成真\N我們要加油哦
Dialogue: 0,1:40:03.18,1:40:07.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫣媽桑乳頭都硬了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:40:26.13,1:40:28.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,1:40:29.58,1:40:29.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子我忍不往了
Dialogue: 0,1:40:42.63,1:40:43.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,1:41:06.03,1:41:06.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 沒事的啊
Dialogue: 0,1:41:07.68,1:41:09.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 沒事的啊
Dialogue: 0,1:41:16.38,1:41:18.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡哪個呢
Dialogue: 0,1:41:20.73,1:41:22.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的
Dialogue: 0,1:41:22.23,1:41:26.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不會認輸的
Dialogue: 0,1:42:00.48,1:42:03.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:42:03.33,1:42:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很軟是不是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:42:03.78,1:42:04.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很軟是不是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:42:16.53,1:42:19.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧 這個
Dialogue: 0,1:42:21.78,1:42:23.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫣媽桑也要
Dialogue: 0,1:42:25.68,1:42:27.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部射出來吧 我們很期待
Dialogue: 0,1:42:28.08,1:42:31.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部射出來吧 我們很期待
Dialogue: 0,1:42:32.13,1:42:33.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部射處理吧 我們很期待
Dialogue: 0,1:43:06.78,1:43:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起來吧 別客氣了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:07.08,1:43:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起來吧 別客氣了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:09.18,1:43:10.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起來吧 別客氯了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:13.83,1:43:13.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們開動了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:11.13,1:44:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有問題吧
Dialogue: 0,1:44:14.43,1:44:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然可以的 來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:44:21.93,1:44:24.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,1:44:27.33,1:44:30.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啊 真是的
Dialogue: 0,1:44:31.53,1:44:34.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:44:34.83,1:44:38.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫蕩的味道
Dialogue: 0,1:44:40.68,1:44:43.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺還行吧
Dialogue: 0,1:45:20.88,1:45:21.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:45:31.68,1:45:34.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺如何
Dialogue: 0,1:45:39.63,1:45:41.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間還早哦
Dialogue: 0,1:45:41.73,1:45:42.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間還早哦
Dialogue: 0,1:45:44.73,1:45:50.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們慢慢玩吧 可以吧\N這是對你的特殊服務
Dialogue: 0,1:45:50.73,1:45:52.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好享受哦
Dialogue: 0,1:46:04.38,1:46:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是命中注定
Dialogue: 0,1:46:13.53,1:46:14.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想吃掉你哦
Dialogue: 0,1:46:15.03,1:46:17.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想吃掉你哦
Dialogue: 0,1:46:27.63,1:46:29.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊
Dialogue: 0,1:46:39.93,1:46:40.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說呢
Dialogue: 0,1:47:09.18,1:47:11.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來啊
Dialogue: 0,1:47:15.63,1:47:17.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:47:22.53,1:47:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:23.58,1:47:23.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:24.33,1:47:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:34.68,1:49:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕濕的 好淫蕩哦
Dialogue: 0,1:50:24.78,1:50:28.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是喜歡啊 這個
Dialogue: 0,1:50:31.53,1:50:34.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,1:51:12.03,1:51:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出來了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:51:34.23,1:51:36.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:51:37.83,1:51:42.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好放鬆才行哦
Dialogue: 0,1:51:47.13,1:51:47.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,1:51:47.43,1:51:50.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看有什麼問題啊
Dialogue: 0,1:51:51.33,1:51:53.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道怎麼做
Dialogue: 0,1:51:55.23,1:51:57.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好
Dialogue: 0,1:52:11.43,1:52:13.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好敏感
Dialogue: 0,1:52:13.53,1:52:18.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我來最舒服的地方\N-我要啦
Dialogue: 0,1:52:28.68,1:52:32.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,1:52:42.63,1:52:45.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開勳了
Dialogue: 0,1:53:05.73,1:53:07.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:53:16.53,1:53:23.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-感覺舒服吧  -是的 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:53:47.88,1:53:50.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好想品嗜啊
Dialogue: 0,1:53:57.78,1:54:00.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還能繼續吧
Dialogue: 0,1:54:32.43,1:54:33.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎麼了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:54:42.03,1:54:45.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不到這麼舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:54:47.43,1:54:54.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種男人味十足的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:54:54.63,1:55:01.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我太爽了 你們想要試試嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:55:01.68,1:55:06.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我簡直忍不住了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:55:54.18,1:55:56.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受吧
Dialogue: 0,1:55:57.63,1:55:57.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要哦
Dialogue: 0,1:55:58.68,1:55:59.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要哦
Dialogue: 0,1:56:08.58,1:56:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,1:56:32.43,1:56:35.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換我來讓你舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:56:42.93,1:56:45.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要來了
Dialogue: 0,1:56:45.63,1:56:47.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來讓你體驗舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:57:14.58,1:57:20.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:57:20.43,1:57:21.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:57:21.18,1:57:29.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫蕩 這麼爽的 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:57:30.03,1:57:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續動起來啊
Dialogue: 0,1:57:34.23,1:57:37.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會讓你這麼快射的
Dialogue: 0,1:57:39.18,1:57:43.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要好好享受哦
Dialogue: 0,1:58:10.83,1:58:10.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:58:42.33,1:58:49.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 很厲害吧 這個感覺
Dialogue: 0,1:58:49.98,1:58:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在意哦 客人
Dialogue: 0,1:58:54.18,1:58:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會好好處理
Dialogue: 0,1:58:58.38,1:59:00.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:59:08.13,1:59:10.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要來了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:59:10.98,1:59:12.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熱熱的
Dialogue: 0,1:59:31.53,1:59:34.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好哦 一起來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:59:34.98,1:59:36.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好哦 一起來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:00:55.08,2:00:59.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:01:26.13,2:01:26.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,2:01:26.43,2:01:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,2:02:02.58,2:02:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太棒了
Dialogue: 0,2:02:03.33,2:02:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太棒了
Dialogue: 0,2:02:03.78,2:02:03.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太棒了
Dialogue: 0,2:02:04.23,2:02:09.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太櫸了
Dialogue: 0,2:02:09.18,2:02:10.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能明白的
Dialogue: 0,2:02:10.83,2:02:12.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能明白的
Dialogue: 0,2:02:14.73,2:02:18.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點來做吧
Dialogue: 0,2:02:28.23,2:02:28.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下要不要啊
Dialogue: 0,2:02:29.13,2:02:29.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高溯
Dialogue: 0,2:02:29.58,2:02:29.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮
Dialogue: 0,2:02:46.83,2:02:49.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是很爽啊
Dialogue: 0,2:02:49.98,2:02:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點來弄我啊
Dialogue: 0,2:02:57.33,2:03:01.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就喜歡你這種人
Dialogue: 0,2:03:01.53,2:03:03.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從後面來
Dialogue: 0,2:03:03.78,2:03:08.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我體會天堂吧
Dialogue: 0,2:03:12.03,2:03:14.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:03:14.43,2:03:15.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:03:23.58,2:03:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會滿足我們吧
Dialogue: 0,2:03:27.18,2:03:28.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從後面
Dialogue: 0,2:03:28.68,2:03:31.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點點來
Dialogue: 0,2:03:31.53,2:03:34.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了
Dialogue: 0,2:04:13.08,2:04:16.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事啊
Dialogue: 0,2:04:19.23,2:04:21.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子啊
Dialogue: 0,2:04:25.23,2:04:29.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你選擇一個吧
Dialogue: 0,2:04:29.43,2:04:34.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後就插進來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:04:40.98,2:04:44.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都很棒的吧
Dialogue: 0,2:04:49.38,2:04:52.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,2:04:53.28,2:04:55.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:04:56.13,2:04:59.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼東西進來了啊
Dialogue: 0,2:05:09.33,2:05:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起啊 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:05:31.83,2:05:37.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自已都動起來了
Dialogue: 0,2:05:57.03,2:06:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:06:22.08,2:06:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,2:06:27.78,2:06:30.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點啦
Dialogue: 0,2:06:51.93,2:06:53.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:07:08.43,2:07:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事嘛
Dialogue: 0,2:07:23.13,2:07:26.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定選我吧
Dialogue: 0,2:07:33.78,2:07:36.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來一次吧
Dialogue: 0,2:07:37.98,2:07:41.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你喜歡的
Dialogue: 0,2:07:55.38,2:07:58.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的太棒了
Dialogue: 0,2:08:12.03,2:08:13.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:08:22.08,2:08:24.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:08:24.93,2:08:28.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太棒了
Dialogue: 0,2:08:31.53,2:08:34.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服 好興奮
Dialogue: 0,2:08:34.68,2:08:41.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣子射出來吧 好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:08:54.63,2:08:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 繼續啊
Dialogue: 0,2:08:57.78,2:09:06.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 啪啪啪的感覺\N繼續來啊 好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:09:06.03,2:09:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,2:09:31.53,2:09:33.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:09:36.63,2:09:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要關始哦
Dialogue: 0,2:09:38.88,2:09:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要開始哦
Dialogue: 0,2:09:40.68,2:09:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道怎麼做了 讓我來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:09:48.78,2:09:50.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,2:10:10.68,2:10:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼表情啊
Dialogue: 0,2:10:14.88,2:10:17.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:10:17.28,2:10:20.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 這個
Dialogue: 0,2:10:25.38,2:10:27.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要啊
Dialogue: 0,2:10:31.38,2:10:34.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 繼續啊
Dialogue: 0,2:10:34.98,2:10:39.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,2:10:39.33,2:10:45.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不能射哦 要忍住哦
Dialogue: 0,2:10:45.63,2:10:49.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能射哦 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,2:10:49.83,2:10:49.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能射哦 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,2:10:49.98,2:10:54.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我忍住 射我
Dialogue: 0,2:10:54.33,2:10:57.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮了啊 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,2:10:58.38,2:11:01.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,2:11:12.63,2:11:17.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內射了是嗎 不是吧
Dialogue: 0,2:11:18.63,2:11:22.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,2:11:23.88,2:11:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年輕忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,2:11:27.18,2:11:32.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定很舒服吧 忍住啊
Dialogue: 0,2:11:32.73,2:11:37.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,2:11:45.63,2:11:47.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太厲害了
Dialogue: 0,2:11:48.18,2:11:49.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼多啊
Dialogue: 0,2:11:52.38,2:11:55.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會操我吧
Dialogue: 0,2:11:56.43,2:11:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:11:58.98,2:12:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們趕緊來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:12:04.98,2:12:07.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽桑的奶子
Dialogue: 0,2:12:07.83,2:12:17.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有味道的哦 如何啊\N我的奶子
Dialogue: 0,2:12:17.88,2:12:21.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軟泡泡的
Dialogue: 0,2:12:24.93,2:12:25.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:12:25.98,2:12:26.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:12:27.18,2:12:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人你是不是忍不住了啊\N會很舒服的
Dialogue: 0,2:12:46.83,2:12:50.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備好了吧
Dialogue: 0,2:12:50.28,2:12:52.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:12:55.68,2:13:03.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用我們最厲害的姿勢 趕緊
Dialogue: 0,2:13:08.28,2:13:11.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:13:31.98,2:13:33.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要啊
Dialogue: 0,2:13:57.48,2:14:00.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進去了啊
Dialogue: 0,2:14:12.48,2:14:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺如何啊
Dialogue: 0,2:14:35.43,2:14:37.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:14:37.68,2:14:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,2:14:45.78,2:14:47.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,2:14:48.63,2:14:51.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,2:14:54.63,2:14:59.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好舒服啊  -沒錯的
Dialogue: 0,2:15:00.18,2:15:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我試試吧
Dialogue: 0,2:15:11.58,2:15:14.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面到我了
Dialogue: 0,2:15:27.48,2:15:31.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是很舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:15:31.38,2:15:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦 就是這樣子哦\N好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:15:40.53,2:15:45.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬邦邦的 好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,2:15:59.13,2:16:02.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧 來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:16:02.43,2:16:07.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔細看吧 好好操吧
Dialogue: 0,2:16:14.13,2:16:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,2:16:44.88,2:16:46.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好開心
Dialogue: 0,2:16:47.28,2:16:47.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,2:16:47.73,2:16:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,2:16:50.13,2:16:50.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太開心了啊 是不是
Dialogue: 0,2:16:50.58,2:16:52.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太開心了啊 是不是
Dialogue: 0,2:16:52.53,2:16:55.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太開心了啊 是不是
Dialogue: 0,2:17:00.48,2:17:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,2:17:20.13,2:17:22.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好興奮啊
Dialogue: 0,2:17:23.58,2:17:26.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個感覺很舒眼啊
Dialogue: 0,2:17:27.03,2:17:27.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個感覺很舒那啊
Dialogue: 0,2:17:33.33,2:17:36.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:17:36.03,2:17:39.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這裡哦
Dialogue: 0,2:17:41.73,2:17:44.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事啊
Dialogue: 0,2:18:02.73,2:18:03.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,2:18:03.78,2:18:03.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,2:18:04.98,2:18:06.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽桑的小穴舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,2:18:06.93,2:18:08.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽桑的小穴舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,2:18:11.88,2:18:14.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來啊
Dialogue: 0,2:18:14.13,2:18:17.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒插進來了
Dialogue: 0,2:18:19.98,2:18:23.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓你舒服的
Dialogue: 0,2:18:23.28,2:18:25.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夾住你了
Dialogue: 0,2:18:49.38,2:18:51.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個感覺
Dialogue: 0,2:18:52.53,2:18:54.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:18:55.38,2:18:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,2:18:57.48,2:19:02.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精液的味道真棒啊
Dialogue: 0,2:19:03.18,2:19:05.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續啊
Dialogue: 0,2:19:09.48,2:19:11.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味道好棒
Dialogue: 0,2:19:18.03,2:19:20.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精液的香味飄散
Dialogue: 0,2:19:26.58,2:19:32.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想跟你結婚啊 每天都要
Dialogue: 0,2:19:41.88,2:19:43.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,2:19:44.28,2:19:46.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備好了
Dialogue: 0,2:19:48.48,2:19:50.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以脫了嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:19:53.73,2:19:54.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,2:20:10.84,2:20:12.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要
Dialogue: 0,2:20:12.94,2:20:16.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔細看哦
Dialogue: 0,2:20:32.14,2:20:33.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊
Dialogue: 0,2:21:12.34,2:21:14.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊
Dialogue: 0,2:21:20.29,2:21:21.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:21:30.04,2:21:31.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,2:21:50.74,2:21:53.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輪到你了
Dialogue: 0,2:22:03.94,2:22:05.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,2:22:07.54,2:22:09.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,2:22:23.44,2:22:25.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩擦到了
Dialogue: 0,2:22:36.94,2:22:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:22:46.99,2:22:49.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是的
Dialogue: 0,2:22:53.29,2:22:55.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊
Dialogue: 0,2:23:01.84,2:23:06.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡大奶子嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:23:10.39,2:23:14.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這個感覺哦
Dialogue: 0,2:23:16.54,2:23:18.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊
Dialogue: 0,2:23:28.54,2:23:32.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是很舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:23:36.49,2:23:39.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來讓你舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,2:23:43.09,2:23:49.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對乳頭沒有抵抗力吧
Dialogue: 0,2:24:06.79,2:24:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊 感覺
Dialogue: 0,2:24:35.14,2:24:37.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來試試吧
Dialogue: 0,2:25:13.69,2:25:15.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:25:36.19,2:25:38.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺如何啊
Dialogue: 0,2:25:51.49,2:25:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:25:53.29,2:25:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄乾淨了嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:26:12.34,2:26:15.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:27:06.49,2:27:08.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:27:11.14,2:27:14.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,2:27:29.29,2:27:30.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕掉了哦
Dialogue: 0,2:27:44.14,2:27:46.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺如何啊
Dialogue: 0,2:27:47.44,2:27:50.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服的
Dialogue: 0,2:28:25.39,2:28:27.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:28:34.39,2:28:39.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事啊 熱熱的
Dialogue: 0,2:29:41.44,2:29:44.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,2:29:46.09,2:29:47.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:29:55.84,2:29:59.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來啊
Dialogue: 0,2:30:04.69,2:30:06.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,2:30:09.19,2:30:13.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是熟練啊你
Dialogue: 0,2:30:16.99,2:30:19.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:30:19.99,2:30:23.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做更舒服的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,2:30:24.04,2:30:26.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備一下
Dialogue: 0,2:30:57.04,2:31:00.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有問題吧
Dialogue: 0,2:31:00.64,2:31:05.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下哦 馬上來哦
Dialogue: 0,2:31:27.49,2:31:31.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備好了 來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:31:36.04,2:31:39.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心一點哦
Dialogue: 0,2:31:58.24,2:31:58.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會不會冷啊
Dialogue: 0,2:31:59.89,2:32:00.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會不會冷啊
Dialogue: 0,2:32:38.59,2:32:42.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼問題嗎 繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:33:24.34,2:33:24.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是很舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:33:34.84,2:33:35.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可愛哦
Dialogue: 0,2:33:43.24,2:33:43.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受吧
Dialogue: 0,2:33:43.84,2:33:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受吧
Dialogue: 0,2:35:27.79,2:35:29.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:36:04.24,2:36:06.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:37:15.79,2:37:16.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 好淫蕩哦
Dialogue: 0,2:37:19.69,2:37:20.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 好淫蕩哦
Dialogue: 0,2:37:22.39,2:37:25.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:38:32.29,2:38:34.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:38:48.64,2:38:51.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我奶子很小的
Dialogue: 0,2:38:51.34,2:38:54.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是夾得很緊哦
Dialogue: 0,2:38:55.84,2:38:58.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換你來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:39:03.49,2:39:04.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊
Dialogue: 0,2:39:06.19,2:39:07.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:39:59.74,2:40:02.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:40:18.79,2:40:21.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴張開吧
Dialogue: 0,2:40:34.24,2:40:35.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要
Dialogue: 0,2:41:36.04,2:41:39.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來讓你濕掉
Dialogue: 0,2:42:37.69,2:42:39.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:42:46.84,2:42:54.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮 高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,2:42:55.99,2:42:56.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,2:43:04.39,2:43:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:43:05.74,2:43:07.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:43:12.49,2:43:13.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬硬的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,2:43:13.54,2:43:13.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬硬的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,2:43:15.04,2:43:16.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以插嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:43:18.49,2:43:23.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我忍不住了\N-我也是的
Dialogue: 0,2:43:23.59,2:43:26.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先來啊
Dialogue: 0,2:43:27.19,2:43:28.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來
Dialogue: 0,2:43:28.84,2:43:35.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不要 我先來啊
Dialogue: 0,2:43:35.89,2:43:42.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是要姐姐先來啊  -真是的
Dialogue: 0,2:43:44.89,2:43:48.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你快點哦
Dialogue: 0,2:43:54.64,2:43:56.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來了
Dialogue: 0,2:44:09.94,2:44:10.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好硬
Dialogue: 0,2:44:10.39,2:44:11.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好硬
Dialogue: 0,2:44:11.59,2:44:13.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好硬
Dialogue: 0,2:44:32.89,2:44:33.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 插進來了
Dialogue: 0,2:44:33.34,2:44:33.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 插進來了
Dialogue: 0,2:44:33.94,2:44:35.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 插進來了
Dialogue: 0,2:44:42.04,2:44:43.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:45:09.79,2:45:11.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好棒
Dialogue: 0,2:45:13.09,2:45:15.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是插進去了
Dialogue: 0,2:45:16.09,2:45:19.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好羨慕你啊
Dialogue: 0,2:46:02.89,2:46:07.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好硬啊 好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:46:08.29,2:46:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,2:47:08.74,2:47:09.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:48:09.34,2:48:12.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服的
Dialogue: 0,2:48:44.29,2:48:44.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好屬害
Dialogue: 0,2:48:45.94,2:48:46.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:48:49.09,2:48:51.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:49:18.49,2:49:20.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:49:24.94,2:49:27.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次啊
Dialogue: 0,2:49:28.09,2:49:31.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來試試吧
Dialogue: 0,2:49:50.44,2:49:52.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啦
Dialogue: 0,2:49:55.39,2:50:00.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來到我了
Dialogue: 0,2:50:24.79,2:50:24.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又高潮了
Dialogue: 0,2:50:25.39,2:50:26.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又高潮了
Dialogue: 0,2:50:44.44,2:50:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太淫蕩了哦
Dialogue: 0,2:51:50.14,2:51:51.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:52:20.74,2:52:24.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:52:27.49,2:52:30.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:52:33.04,2:52:34.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點啊
Dialogue: 0,2:52:35.74,2:52:38.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:52:38.59,2:52:42.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要懷上你的孩子
Dialogue: 0,2:53:13.84,2:53:17.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好溫暖哦
Dialogue: 0,2:53:18.79,2:53:22.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:53:22.54,2:53:24.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼多啊
Dialogue: 0,2:53:25.39,2:53:27.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:53:32.29,2:53:34.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過分
Dialogue: 0,2:53:36.19,2:53:38.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要
Dialogue: 0,2:53:38.44,2:53:40.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我吧
Dialogue: 0,2:53:44.14,2:53:49.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我啊 讓我懷孕
Dialogue: 0,2:54:00.79,2:54:02.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫蕩
Dialogue: 0,2:54:04.84,2:54:06.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要
Dialogue: 0,2:54:08.29,2:54:11.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茶几那裏啊
Dialogue: 0,2:54:34.09,2:54:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:54:43.99,2:54:47.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:54:49.24,2:54:54.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明才射了 還這麼硬
Dialogue: 0,2:54:58.99,2:55:02.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧 是不是
Dialogue: 0,2:55:06.19,2:55:07.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:55:08.74,2:55:11.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,2:55:21.34,2:55:24.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,2:55:37.39,2:55:39.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:56:21.04,2:56:25.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不小心高潮了呢
Dialogue: 0,2:56:30.04,2:56:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:56:39.94,2:56:43.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服 好大
Dialogue: 0,2:57:03.04,2:57:06.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,2:57:06.64,2:57:09.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了啊
Dialogue: 0,2:57:26.29,2:57:28.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,2:57:33.34,2:57:36.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,2:57:55.69,2:57:59.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部射出來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:58:31.69,2:58:34.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小穴
Dialogue: 0,2:58:35.29,2:58:36.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:58:36.79,2:58:38.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:58:39.34,2:58:42.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的才舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,2:58:42.79,2:58:45.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是啊
Dialogue: 0,2:58:46.24,2:58:48.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我啦
Dialogue: 0,2:58:49.24,2:58:52.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,2:59:05.44,2:59:06.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說上話了嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:59:06.79,2:59:10.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 當然啊
Dialogue: 0,2:59:11.29,2:59:13.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺不錯吧
Dialogue: 0,2:59:23.59,2:59:27.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直受不了啊
Dialogue: 0,2:59:32.89,2:59:34.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家
Dialogue: 0,2:59:34.69,2:59:34.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,2:59:47.74,2:59:49.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天
Dialogue: 0,2:59:50.14,2:59:51.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了我
Dialogue: 0,2:59:54.79,2:59:56.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,參加我辦的宴會
Dialogue: 0,2:59:57.04,3:00:00.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有紀念意義
Dialogue: 0,3:00:02.59,3:00:05.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雙手舉起來
Dialogue: 0,3:00:08.44,3:00:08.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之
Dialogue: 0,3:00:08.89,3:00:11.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先這麼搞吧
Dialogue: 0,3:00:50.29,3:00:50.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,3:00:50.74,3:00:51.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,3:00:51.64,3:00:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,3:00:58.69,3:01:01.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內射宴會開始了
Dialogue: 0,3:01:05.14,3:01:07.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憋著急啊
Dialogue: 0,3:01:09.79,3:01:13.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣子慢慢來
Dialogue: 0,3:01:19.69,3:01:22.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我 讓我來
Dialogue: 0,3:01:49.09,3:01:51.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,3:02:13.54,3:02:13.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,3:02:13.84,3:02:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,3:02:14.44,3:02:14.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,3:02:14.89,3:02:15.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,3:02:15.34,3:02:15.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,3:02:16.24,3:02:16.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,3:02:21.49,3:02:24.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好幸福啊
Dialogue: 0,3:02:47.89,3:02:48.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:02:48.64,3:02:48.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:02:49.09,3:02:50.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:03:13.99,3:03:17.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好羨慕哦
Dialogue: 0,3:03:20.29,3:03:25.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不錯啊 感覺好棒
Dialogue: 0,3:03:32.44,3:03:36.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輪到我了
Dialogue: 0,3:04:11.29,3:04:12.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了嘛
Dialogue: 0,3:04:21.04,3:04:25.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經夠了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:05:28.54,3:05:30.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好性感啊
Dialogue: 0,3:09:33.64,3:09:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蹂躪我吧
Dialogue: 0,3:10:04.84,3:10:07.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,3:11:17.89,3:11:19.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,3:11:20.29,3:11:21.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,3:11:44.44,3:11:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,3:12:26.14,3:12:28.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,3:12:28.24,3:12:30.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是要高潮了吧
Dialogue: 0,3:12:31.09,3:12:33.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,3:12:49.69,3:12:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要 我要
Dialogue: 0,3:12:53.14,3:12:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我先來
Dialogue: 0,3:12:57.04,3:13:00.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照順序來啊
Dialogue: 0,3:13:01.09,3:13:03.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都想吃嗎
Dialogue: 0,3:13:06.79,3:13:08.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,3:13:08.59,3:13:11.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排成一排
Dialogue: 0,3:13:13.84,3:13:16.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照順序來
Dialogue: 0,3:13:18.94,3:13:21.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣子哦
Dialogue: 0,3:13:28.99,3:13:32.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一號很不錯哦  -謝謝
Dialogue: 0,3:13:58.54,3:14:01.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,3:14:09.94,3:14:12.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個不錯
Dialogue: 0,3:14:20.44,3:14:23.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺忍不住了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:14:24.34,3:14:27.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,3:14:31.24,3:14:37.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下哦 其他人要來了
Dialogue: 0,3:14:40.24,3:14:43.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,3:14:43.54,3:14:46.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還要呢
Dialogue: 0,3:14:57.79,3:15:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺很刺激
Dialogue: 0,3:15:24.34,3:15:27.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,3:15:31.09,3:15:33.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:15:33.79,3:15:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊 這樣子會忍不住的
Dialogue: 0,3:15:39.64,3:15:41.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕緊來吧
Dialogue: 0,3:15:43.84,3:15:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉過去吧
Dialogue: 0,3:15:50.44,3:15:51.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好哦
Dialogue: 0,3:16:02.29,3:16:04.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備好了嗎
Dialogue: 0,3:16:05.14,3:16:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要插進去
Dialogue: 0,3:16:05.74,3:16:06.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要插進去
Dialogue: 0,3:16:07.54,3:16:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要插進去
Dialogue: 0,3:16:09.04,3:16:10.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要插進去
Dialogue: 0,3:16:11.14,3:16:13.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:16:31.54,3:16:36.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過是時候交換了
Dialogue: 0,3:16:38.89,3:16:41.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓緊時間
Dialogue: 0,3:17:35.44,3:17:37.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的啊
Dialogue: 0,3:17:37.24,3:17:38.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的啊
Dialogue: 0,3:17:53.74,3:17:56.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會讓我舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,3:17:56.74,3:17:58.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,3:18:06.94,3:18:09.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種地方也舔啊
Dialogue: 0,3:18:11.44,3:18:13.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:18:38.29,3:18:39.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:18:42.04,3:18:46.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔法好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:18:49.99,3:18:51.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太厲害了
Dialogue: 0,3:18:52.84,3:18:56.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換下一位吧
Dialogue: 0,3:19:21.34,3:19:27.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好品嚐哦
Dialogue: 0,3:19:36.34,3:19:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,3:20:10.69,3:20:12.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,3:20:16.24,3:20:18.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一位哦
Dialogue: 0,3:20:21.34,3:20:22.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就完了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:20:24.04,3:20:26.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有很多人
Dialogue: 0,3:20:28.24,3:20:31.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間太少了
Dialogue: 0,3:20:46.99,3:20:48.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃的樣子
Dialogue: 0,3:21:20.29,3:21:22.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:21:45.04,3:21:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一位
Dialogue: 0,3:22:46.09,3:22:48.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一位
Dialogue: 0,3:23:01.54,3:23:04.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等太久了
Dialogue: 0,3:23:05.89,3:23:09.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是嗎  -我開動了
Dialogue: 0,3:23:16.54,3:23:19.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:23:38.14,3:23:40.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一位
Dialogue: 0,3:23:40.54,3:23:43.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太快了吧
Dialogue: 0,3:23:43.54,3:23:46.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有很多人等蓄
Dialogue: 0,3:23:57.94,3:24:01.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,3:24:03.79,3:24:06.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好好做吧
Dialogue: 0,3:24:07.09,3:24:09.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,3:24:24.19,3:24:26.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,3:24:44.44,3:24:48.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結束了哦
Dialogue: 0,3:24:52.54,3:24:53.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點啦
Dialogue: 0,3:24:54.04,3:24:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點啦
Dialogue: 0,3:25:05.89,3:25:07.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家
Dialogue: 0,3:25:08.29,3:25:09.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次
Dialogue: 0,3:25:09.94,3:25:14.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看你們的屁股
Dialogue: 0,3:25:17.74,3:25:20.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓緊時間啊
Dialogue: 0,3:25:24.19,3:25:26.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,3:25:35.14,3:25:37.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,3:25:52.99,3:25:56.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,3:25:58.09,3:26:04.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該怎麼弄呢 選哪個呢
Dialogue: 0,3:26:05.14,3:26:10.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,選我 選我的
Dialogue: 0,3:26:31.54,3:26:33.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脫掉吧
Dialogue: 0,3:26:33.34,3:26:34.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,3:26:38.89,3:26:43.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是開心啊
Dialogue: 0,3:26:43.54,3:26:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內褲呢
Dialogue: 0,3:26:45.34,3:26:47.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,3:28:18.79,3:28:22.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要肉棒 肉棒好硬
Dialogue: 0,3:28:45.94,3:28:50.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是要高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:28:52.54,3:28:55.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:28:58.09,3:29:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好羨慕啊
Dialogue: 0,3:29:11.74,3:29:15.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來怎麼做呢
Dialogue: 0,3:29:26.89,3:29:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊
Dialogue: 0,3:29:48.64,3:29:50.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,3:29:51.04,3:29:53.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴濕濕的
Dialogue: 0,3:29:53.44,3:29:55.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,3:29:55.84,3:29:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,3:29:56.59,3:29:57.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,3:30:27.64,3:30:31.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要肉棒啊
Dialogue: 0,3:30:49.24,3:30:51.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,3:30:58.24,3:31:01.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,3:31:01.54,3:31:02.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:31:06.64,3:31:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不行了
Dialogue: 0,3:31:09.04,3:31:11.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:31:21.19,3:31:21.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,3:31:21.79,3:31:22.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,3:31:22.84,3:31:24.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,3:31:24.94,3:31:27.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:31:50.74,3:31:56.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣子一直操我吧
Dialogue: 0,3:31:56.89,3:31:58.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:32:08.59,3:32:13.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以一直操我嗎
Dialogue: 0,3:33:03.04,3:33:04.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:33:04.99,3:33:07.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,3:33:11.59,3:33:14.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來了
Dialogue: 0,3:33:16.69,3:33:19.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放輕鬆哦
Dialogue: 0,3:33:24.19,3:33:26.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,3:33:45.79,3:33:48.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:34:19.09,3:34:21.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然要內射
Dialogue: 0,3:34:22.24,3:34:25.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:34:33.19,3:34:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫蕩的小穴啊
Dialogue: 0,3:34:36.19,3:34:41.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好開心啊 射出來
Dialogue: 0,3:34:41.74,3:34:44.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要射了哦
Dialogue: 0,3:34:55.84,3:34:58.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,3:35:18.79,3:35:21.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:35:21.04,3:35:23.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,3:35:23.89,3:35:30.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內射啊 趕緊的
Dialogue: 0,3:35:30.04,3:35:35.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的 蠻不錯的
Dialogue: 0,3:35:39.34,3:35:42.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,3:35:47.59,3:35:50.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在斡嘛 很礙事哦
Dialogue: 0,3:36:03.04,3:36:06.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要操我嗎
Dialogue: 0,3:36:27.94,3:36:30.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,3:36:48.64,3:36:50.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:36:52.39,3:36:57.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:37:05.14,3:37:06.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:37:06.94,3:37:10.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害的啊
Dialogue: 0,3:37:10.39,3:37:12.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續啊
Dialogue: 0,3:37:15.64,3:37:17.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:37:18.64,3:37:20.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 高潮
Dialogue: 0,3:37:33.94,3:37:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼舒服的啊 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:37:46.54,3:37:47.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,3:38:10.84,3:38:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:38:23.59,3:38:25.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,3:38:37.69,3:38:40.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,3:38:46.69,3:38:49.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:38:52.54,3:38:56.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺到了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:38:58.24,3:39:01.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸到了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:39:17.44,3:39:19.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要高潮
Dialogue: 0,3:39:21.19,3:39:23.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,3:39:44.44,3:39:46.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好開心啊
Dialogue: 0,3:39:51.04,3:39:52.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好硬
Dialogue: 0,3:39:58.09,3:39:59.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:40:03.64,3:40:07.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股露出來了
Dialogue: 0,3:40:17.44,3:40:19.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:40:28.99,3:40:31.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:40:38.89,3:40:41.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:40:57.34,3:41:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,3:41:07.99,3:41:12.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好舒服啊 高潮
Dialogue: 0,3:41:12.19,3:41:13.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:41:23.74,3:41:26.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過分啊
Dialogue: 0,3:41:35.59,3:41:39.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還要繼續做啊
Dialogue: 0,3:41:51.49,3:41:53.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:41:58.99,3:42:01.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣子啊
Dialogue: 0,3:42:03.49,3:42:06.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是給大家的獎勵哦
Dialogue: 0,3:42:23.44,3:42:26.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:42:33.79,3:42:36.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,3:43:16.25,3:43:18.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦
Dialogue: 0,3:43:30.35,3:43:33.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要來
Dialogue: 0,3:43:33.05,3:43:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表情很不錯啊 誰來啊
Dialogue: 0,3:44:14.45,3:44:15.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來了
Dialogue: 0,3:44:56.75,3:44:58.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,3:45:26.75,3:45:28.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍住哦
Dialogue: 0,3:45:28.70,3:45:32.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:45:44.90,3:45:47.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,3:46:52.55,3:46:55.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,3:47:04.25,3:47:05.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好羨慕啊
Dialogue: 0,3:47:05.90,3:47:08.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來吧
Dialogue: 0,3:47:09.95,3:47:12.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼做啊
Dialogue: 0,3:47:13.25,3:47:16.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能這樣子啊
Dialogue: 0,3:47:16.85,3:47:19.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很適合你的哦
Dialogue: 0,3:47:20.60,3:47:23.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫蕩啊
Dialogue: 0,3:47:25.55,3:47:30.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個就要靠你了
Dialogue: 0,3:47:32.30,3:47:37.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是這樣子就夠了嗎
Dialogue: 0,3:47:41.00,3:47:44.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕緊來吧
Dialogue: 0,3:47:56.15,3:47:59.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,3:48:01.70,3:48:03.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速度快點
Dialogue: 0,3:48:04.85,3:48:06.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,3:48:36.95,3:48:39.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還要嗎
Dialogue: 0,3:48:43.40,3:48:43.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啊
Dialogue: 0,3:48:44.15,3:48:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啊
Dialogue: 0,3:48:51.95,3:48:53.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,3:49:03.05,3:49:05.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,3:49:22.70,3:49:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要射了
Dialogue: 0,3:49:25.55,3:49:27.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:50:09.50,3:50:13.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都出汗了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:50:13.70,3:50:13.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,3:51:54.65,3:51:56.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,3:51:56.75,3:51:58.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,3:52:11.60,3:52:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,3:53:16.25,3:53:19.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:53:22.85,3:53:25.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,3:53:42.50,3:53:45.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,3:53:58.25,3:53:59.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來吧
Dialogue: 0,3:54:00.05,3:54:03.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣子啊
Dialogue: 0,3:54:15.65,3:54:17.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:54:30.65,3:54:32.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,3:54:35.15,3:54:37.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:54:38.75,3:54:42.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 我高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:54:53.45,3:54:56.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:55:16.10,3:55:16.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我也來吧
Dialogue: 0,3:55:17.15,3:55:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我也來吧
Dialogue: 0,3:55:19.55,3:55:22.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浚有關係的
Dialogue: 0,3:55:24.05,3:55:26.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好啊
Dialogue: 0,3:55:42.65,3:55:44.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:55:57.20,3:55:59.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,3:56:47.75,3:56:50.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:57:01.10,3:57:04.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬硬的好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:57:11.60,3:57:13.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了啊
Dialogue: 0,3:57:14.15,3:57:16.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,3:57:36.80,3:57:38.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,3:57:49.55,3:57:52.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要繼續啊
Dialogue: 0,3:57:58.25,3:58:02.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:58:04.25,3:58:06.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,3:58:14.45,3:58:17.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事啊
Dialogue: 0,3:58:27.65,3:58:30.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,3:58:30.65,3:58:33.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,3:58:41.30,3:58:44.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,3:59:28.85,3:59:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真棒啊
Dialogue: 0,3:59:59.30,4:00:02.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能這麼搞啊
Dialogue: 0,4:00:05.00,4:00:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,4:00:11.75,4:00:15.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來吧
Dialogue: 0,4:00:18.50,4:00:20.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,4:00:32.15,4:00:34.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,4:00:57.05,4:00:59.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼啊
Dialogue: 0,4:01:04.40,4:01:06.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:01:08.00,4:01:10.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我精液啊
Dialogue: 0,4:01:11.00,4:01:12.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來吧
Dialogue: 0,4:01:16.10,4:01:18.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,4:01:53.75,4:01:55.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,4:02:11.15,4:02:12.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:02:14.45,4:02:17.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續來吧
Dialogue: 0,4:02:35.60,4:02:37.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要啊
Dialogue: 0,4:02:39.65,4:02:41.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,4:03:01.70,4:03:04.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺如何啊
Dialogue: 0,4:03:08.15,4:03:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腰扭起來了
Dialogue: 0,4:03:36.65,4:03:38.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕濕的
Dialogue: 0,4:03:45.80,4:03:49.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺還行吧
Dialogue: 0,4:03:49.25,4:03:51.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:04:08.75,4:04:11.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那裡啊
Dialogue: 0,4:04:15.50,4:04:18.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒啊 插進來了
Dialogue: 0,4:04:21.05,4:04:23.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,4:04:49.25,4:04:53.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,4:04:54.05,4:04:56.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來吧
Dialogue: 0,4:05:17.15,4:05:20.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事啊
Dialogue: 0,4:05:45.65,4:05:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦 真是厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,4:06:24.80,4:06:27.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,4:06:30.80,4:06:33.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮
Dialogue: 0,4:06:42.80,4:06:45.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內射了啊
Dialogue: 0,4:06:55.25,4:06:58.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好硬啊 這個
Dialogue: 0,4:07:30.35,4:07:32.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,4:07:48.50,4:07:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好開心
Dialogue: 0,4:07:52.25,4:07:54.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,4:08:04.85,4:08:08.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這氣氛不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,4:08:28.85,4:08:30.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:08:32.30,4:08:35.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好厲害
Dialogue: 0,4:08:38.90,4:08:41.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,4:08:41.00,4:08:41.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,4:08:53.15,4:08:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那個啊
Dialogue: 0,4:09:03.35,4:09:03.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:09:03.65,4:09:05.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:09:12.20,4:09:12.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好哦
Dialogue: 0,4:09:13.25,4:09:14.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好哦
Dialogue: 0,4:09:18.05,4:09:20.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,4:09:25.40,4:09:28.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊 這個
Dialogue: 0,4:09:31.55,4:09:34.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣子哦
Dialogue: 0,4:09:45.20,4:09:47.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,4:09:48.80,4:09:52.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太棒了
Dialogue: 0,4:10:05.15,4:10:06.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,4:10:18.35,4:10:20.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好哦
Dialogue: 0,4:10:21.80,4:10:24.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,4:10:24.50,4:10:27.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就開始吧
Dialogue: 0,4:10:31.25,4:10:33.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,4:10:37.55,4:10:40.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣子
Dialogue: 0,4:11:36.65,4:11:40.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要哦
Dialogue: 0,4:11:51.05,4:11:52.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我呢
Dialogue: 0,4:12:21.80,4:12:24.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,4:12:30.05,4:12:33.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,4:12:49.55,4:12:53.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪哦
Dialogue: 0,4:12:58.55,4:13:00.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,4:13:03.65,4:13:06.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太棒了
Dialogue: 0,4:13:15.05,4:13:17.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,4:13:36.35,4:13:39.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,4:13:42.20,4:13:45.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,4:14:09.95,4:14:12.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是這樣
Dialogue: 0,4:14:41.75,4:14:45.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 插進來了
Dialogue: 0,4:14:47.90,4:14:50.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續給我啊
Dialogue: 0,4:14:55.10,4:14:56.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:14:56.75,4:14:56.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:14:57.05,4:14:57.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:14:57.35,4:14:57.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:15:06.05,4:15:09.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,4:15:35.15,4:15:36.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,4:15:59.45,4:16:01.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,4:16:04.10,4:16:07.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦 這個感覺
Dialogue: 0,4:16:10.25,4:16:12.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,4:16:12.35,4:16:16.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,4:16:41.90,4:16:44.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,4:16:45.65,4:16:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 高潮啊
Dialogue: 0,4:16:57.95,4:17:01.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,4:17:46.85,4:17:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天太累了 不做了
Dialogue: 0,4:17:55.25,4:17:58.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個太棒了
Dialogue: 0,4:17:58.55,4:18:01.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,4:18:02.30,4:18:09.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經結束了哦 不行了哦
Dialogue: 0,4:18:10.55,4:18:10.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,4:18:11.45,4:18:12.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,4:18:12.35,4:18:13.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,4:18:13.25,4:18:16.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放過我吧
Dialogue: 0,4:18:17.45,4:18:18.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-下次再來吧  -不要啊別
Dialogue: 0,4:18:18.80,4:18:23.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-下次再來吧  -不要啊別
Dialogue: 0,4:18:30.20,4:18:33.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題吧
Dialogue: 0,4:18:34.25,4:18:39.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 就在去年
Dialogue: 0,4:18:39.05,4:18:42.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我中獎的
Dialogue: 0,4:18:44.00,4:18:48.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定會繼續中獎的啊
Dialogue: 0,4:19:38.45,4:19:42.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(END)

