[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,20,20,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.47,0:00:13.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\3c&Hffffff\c&Hff&\fn楷体\b1\fs16}《50倍的癡女快感!不停地\N攻擊男人的肛門 激烈性感興奮頂點》\N{\3c&H00\c&Hffffff&\fn楷体\fs12\b1}（桐嵨莉乃)\N{\fntimes new roman\fs8\b1}MIAE-105\N{\c&H3ee0fd&\fs8\fn宋体}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.33,0:00:19.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.14,0:00:21.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一章\N第一次的前列腺愛撫
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.54,0:00:28.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,該怎麼說好呢？\N真是令人神魂頓倒的身材呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.85,0:00:30.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎 有那麼令你神魂顛倒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.85,0:00:32.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.35,0:00:37.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,李野桑聽說你非常的喜歡責備男人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.45,0:00:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基本上是喜歡帶有些抖M的性質
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.86,0:00:49.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,貴備男人時他那種有感覺的表情\N讓我非常的性奮
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.77,0:00:52.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就會變得特別喜歡責備他
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.17,0:00:55.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到今天為止前一天你\N嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.97,0:01:01.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好像挑戰那個虐待男人的節目了吧？\N嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.38,0:01:05.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是我第一次那樣做
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.38,0:01:08.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一次啊\N是的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.09,0:01:10.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全沒有這方面的經驗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.49,0:01:17.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個 以前的話有一次曾經\N把手指放進屁股過
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.39,0:01:18.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.00,0:01:21.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只做過這種程度的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.00,0:01:24.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己主動做的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.70,0:01:28.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他叫我做的\N他說希望我把手指插進去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.91,0:01:33.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我問的真的嗎 真的沒問題嗎\N他說真的沒問題 插進來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.11,0:01:35.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就用手指稍微插了進去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.81,0:01:36.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是個什麼樣的感覺?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.91,0:01:44.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想想啊 不知道是食指還是中指\N像這樣啾的一下插進去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.32,0:01:48.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一邊聽著聲音一邊插進去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.83,0:01:55.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看起來很快樂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.83,0:01:59.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的很有意思\N雖然是第一次做這種事情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.34,0:02:03.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過內心卻是激動不已的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.54,0:02:06.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.24,0:02:10.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓你插屁股的洞插個爽\N好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.25,0:02:15.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盡情的疼愛男優吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.45,0:02:16.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.95,0:02:18.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很期待
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.36,0:02:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你還沒看到男優嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.36,0:02:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 還沒有看過
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.36,0:02:26.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就立馬讓你看看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.56,0:02:26.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.86,0:02:27.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.46,0:02:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.87,0:02:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這個不是已經有點勃起了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.48,0:02:41.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定是在偷看我吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.58,0:02:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.88,0:02:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.28,0:02:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我感覺到了視線了的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.38,0:02:47.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎\N嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.79,0:02:59.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,立馬就開始親嘴了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.50,0:03:01.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好下流
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.50,0:03:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突然感覺變得想要起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.82,0:03:27.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭也已經硬邦邦的了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.03,0:03:30.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己看看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.97,0:04:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.80,0:04:42.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想不想舔舔我的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.80,0:04:44.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想舔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.60,0:04:47.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就幫我脫掉衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.00,0:04:49.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.41,0:04:57.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脫掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.93,0:05:10.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.73,0:05:12.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎\N真的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.47,0:05:52.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看胸部在肉棒上門摩擦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.09,0:06:15.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不想讓我快點直接摸你的歐金金嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.99,0:06:17.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.60,0:06:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請幫在多摸摸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.00,0:06:29.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當~然了\N會給你摸個爽的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.51,0:06:36.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.91,0:06:40.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經變得硬邦邦的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.42,0:06:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.52,0:06:45.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要我幫你舔嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.72,0:06:46.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 想要你幫我舔\N想要我幫你舔嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.43,0:06:55.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.53,0:06:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不是想要我幫你舔嗎\N是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.99,0:07:54.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常的舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.49,0:07:56.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服嗎\N很舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.25,0:08:56.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我幫你弄得爽翻天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.85,0:08:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金已經
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.96,0:09:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.46,0:09:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再來接吻
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.16,0:09:05.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話會更舒服的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.70,0:09:46.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然變得這麼的堅挺
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.40,0:09:49.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再讓你體驗更舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.21,0:09:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.31,0:09:54.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就先坐在這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.41,0:09:58.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏被人看見的話會感到性奮嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.42,0:10:01.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會很性奮
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.02,0:10:06.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己知道這裏有多舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.12,0:10:09.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那今天我來教你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.94,0:10:25.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看屁股已經濕嗒嗒的了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.18,0:11:08.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經一抖抖的了呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.48,0:11:10.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股的洞穴被這樣愛撫\N很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.19,0:11:15.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請一邊幫我舔邊幫我\N玩弄小弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.19,0:11:19.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想我幫你嗎\N很想要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.70,0:11:25.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.80,0:11:28.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.01,0:11:41.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己看屁股的洞穴和歐金金\N已經非常的有感覺了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.12,0:11:50.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在就射出來的話\N還太早了點
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.53,0:11:51.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.03,0:11:54.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也還想在多玩玩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.05,0:12:13.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金硬得這麼厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.75,0:12:17.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一邊舔著你的屁穴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.45,0:12:20.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一邊玩弄著你的歐金金
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.16,0:12:23.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經快要射出來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.76,0:12:29.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就讓屁穴裏面
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.87,0:12:32.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插進手指的話會變成怎樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.37,0:12:36.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道啊\N到底會變成什麼樣呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.59,0:12:56.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金和屁穴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.49,0:12:59.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給你愛撫個夠呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.40,0:13:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天這裏的屁股可是屁穴呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.30,0:13:07.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要盡情的去感受哦\N好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.83,0:13:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴是在哪個位置啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.33,0:13:37.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是這裏嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.75,0:13:51.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.55,0:13:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.95,0:13:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要我快點插進去已經忍不住了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.56,0:14:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用我的手指插進屁穴裏面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.76,0:14:07.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是已經忍不住\N希望我趕緊插進去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.76,0:14:08.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.67,0:14:09.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.77,0:14:12.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看已經插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.38,0:14:25.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面好炙熱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.38,0:14:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的好厲害 好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.79,0:14:34.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 怎麼了\N就那麼的舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.69,0:14:36.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.19,0:14:41.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股裏面的洞穴縮得\N非常的緊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.00,0:14:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.50,0:14:45.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的就那麼舒服的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.31,0:14:59.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是這裏嗎\N肉棒變得好硬了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.32,0:15:05.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們的屁股裏面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.32,0:15:08.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夾得非常的緊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.63,0:15:11.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺怎麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.73,0:15:15.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊\N每次手指出來屁股都會縮得好緊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.53,0:15:19.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直緊抓著我的手指不讓它出來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.14,0:15:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個屁穴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.74,0:15:28.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在更多的去感受\N好的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.25,0:15:34.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人口必居然夾得這麼緊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.05,0:15:38.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏 屁穴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.56,0:15:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,實在是太緊了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.46,0:15:49.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後稍微進去一點就會\N變得如此的緊致
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.17,0:15:52.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒也會跟著變得
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.27,0:15:57.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看已經硬得不能再硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.38,0:16:04.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴和歐金金兩邊起被愛撫\N很舒服的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.60,0:16:22.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.91,0:16:34.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看好厲偉變得硬邦邦的了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.01,0:16:38.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己看嘛 已經硬成這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.82,0:16:44.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好不好 屁股裏面越來越緊了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.93,0:16:51.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是要射出來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.33,0:16:53.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.73,0:16:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.84,0:17:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.74,0:17:08.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.95,0:17:16.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏面一直緊緊的夾著\N手指不放
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.06,0:17:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在很敏感呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.46,0:17:23.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是精液可還沒有射出來哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.16,0:17:26.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個就是哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.56,0:17:28.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,極致高潮哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.77,0:17:32.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是第一次體驗到這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.97,0:17:37.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常的舒服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.67,0:17:37.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害\N非常的舒服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.97,0:17:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.48,0:17:41.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點幫我射出來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.81,0:18:14.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好不壞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.82,0:18:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精子快要射出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.02,0:18:24.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺精液要射出來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.42,0:18:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這不是件很棒的事情嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.43,0:18:38.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.46,0:19:05.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.36,0:19:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.07,0:19:13.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴和歐金金都已經濕嗒嗒的了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.07,0:19:20.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股裏面這麼的緊\N歐金金也這麼的硬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.48,0:19:24.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又變得更緊了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.78,0:19:26.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.58,0:19:30.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你夾得這麼緊\N害我的手指都有感覺了呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.99,0:19:35.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點快點\N在更有感覺一點
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.50,0:19:42.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金不是已經受不了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.30,0:19:46.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屈股裏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.80,0:19:47.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.00,0:19:49.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夾得這麼緊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.01,0:19:53.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒也這麼硬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.71,0:19:57.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.21,0:20:00.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就變得更舒服一點哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.82,0:20:03.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點射吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.52,0:20:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想射出精子來的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.23,0:20:11.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.63,0:20:14.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了要射了\N快點射出來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.73,0:20:19.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射出來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.04,0:20:24.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.64,0:20:30.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害\N屁穴裏面夾得非常緊的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.25,0:20:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的好厲害啊\N居然把精子射得這麼遠
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.96,0:20:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的就那麼的舒服的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.16,0:20:49.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的好厲害啊\N都拔不出來了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.37,0:20:53.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可以拔出來了嗎\N我要拔出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.67,0:21:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的抖動得很厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.98,0:21:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手套都濕嗒嗒的了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.59,0:21:11.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.19,0:21:18.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的很厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.00,0:21:19.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺怎麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.50,0:21:24.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能平時做的那樣要舒服的吧？\N是的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.50,0:21:28.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服的要死
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.01,0:21:34.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看起來真的很舒服呢\N我玩得非常的開心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.32,0:21:46.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺就像是要射很多次的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.52,0:21:50.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟你射得那麼遠嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.13,0:21:55.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肯定會非常的舒服對吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.46,0:22:26.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第二章\N騎乘肛門快感的做愛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.46,0:22:28.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.27,0:22:34.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想…想感受升天的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.77,0:22:37.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像女孩子那樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.97,0:22:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.38,0:22:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全像那樣嗎\N完全
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.98,0:22:45.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是像平常那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.18,0:22:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.58,0:22:48.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼今天
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.29,0:22:51.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就用我的這裏
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.89,0:22:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用我的手指和我的肉穴來
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.50,0:23:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盡情的來愛撫你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.80,0:23:08.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,過來這邊\N好的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.21,0:23:16.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把舌頭伸出來
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.13,0:23:35.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來愛撫你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.53,0:23:37.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的拜託您了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.64,0:23:40.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,過來這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.74,0:23:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,後背對著我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.14,0:23:45.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.65,0:23:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果把內褲脫掉的話\N就會看得一清二楚哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.25,0:23:55.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好丟人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.65,0:23:58.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不是很喜歡這種丟臉的事情嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.26,0:24:05.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,越被人看到越會有感覺的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.16,0:24:11.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是如何有感覺的全部讓我看清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.98,0:24:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把屁股再翹高一點
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.98,0:24:24.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.38,0:24:30.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管是屁股還是歐金金或者蛋蛋\N都非常的漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.09,0:24:37.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看我僅僅只是吹口氣\N屁股就會一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.30,0:24:48.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的口水被屁股吸進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.41,0:24:55.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可是吐了一大堆的口水了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.21,0:25:00.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.12,0:25:04.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.23,0:25:17.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.03,0:25:21.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜歡看到這種一抖一抖的屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.55,0:25:33.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始我就用我的舌頭和手指\N來好好的疼愛你呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.56,0:25:46.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的歐金金變得非常的硬了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.08,0:26:05.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來好好的愛撫你
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.58,0:26:10.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你用後背來感受我的肉穴
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.19,0:26:18.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不僅僅是肉穴
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.30,0:26:22.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連我的整個身體都變得熱了起來
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.00,0:26:31.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看不管管是肉穴還是屁穴全部\N都看得清二楚哦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.33,0:26:51.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身體好熱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.53,0:26:54.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.33,0:26:57.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.24,0:27:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想在更加的有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.25,0:27:16.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.76,0:27:22.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想讓你感覺到更爽的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.76,0:27:26.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓你這裏變得黏糊糊的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.17,0:27:37.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我現在在做些什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.08,0:27:43.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的尼般已經光亮亮的黏糊糊的了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.00,0:28:09.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變得這麼的粘稠
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.81,0:28:14.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胸部也黏糊糊的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.01,0:28:18.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要讓你爽翻天的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.73,0:28:39.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看我現在正在用我的乳頭\N玩弄著你的屁股哦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.65,0:28:56.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺怎麼樣?舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.46,0:29:02.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.87,0:29:11.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不僅僅是胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.97,0:29:14.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更加更加的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.29,0:29:35.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴正在一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.22,0:30:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.12,0:30:06.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股、屁穴也變得非常的熱了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.24,0:30:21.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的舌頭伸進屁穴 裏面了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.56,0:30:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴蛋蛋和歐金金
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.06,0:30:50.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部都變得黏糊糊的了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.97,0:31:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就讓你像女孩子那樣\N爽翻天呢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.58,0:31:06.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴在一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.19,0:31:15.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,每當我摸到它\N就會一抖一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.49,0:31:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看 我的手指要插進\N你的屁穴裏面了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.10,0:31:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.02,0:31:43.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手指插進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.52,0:31:45.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.62,0:31:47.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面好熱
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.33,0:31:51.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.73,0:31:53.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏面正在抽搐
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.23,0:31:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想要我怎麼幫你做?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.84,0:32:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面好棒夾得非常的緊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.14,0:32:07.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害裏面緊緊的夾著手指呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.15,0:32:15.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的裏面\N裏面好像要出來什麼東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.46,0:32:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.86,0:32:30.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害越是玩弄歐金金\N屁穴裏面就會越來越緊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.57,0:32:35.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害好厲害\N裏面好緊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.77,0:32:39.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒也變得硬邦邦的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.58,0:32:49.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害呢 你看你的肉棒也變得好硬
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.49,0:32:53.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看你的屁穴裏面的緊致度實在是\N太厲害了 歐金金也變得這麼的堅硬
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.40,0:33:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了我要射出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.71,0:33:11.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了射了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.12,0:33:23.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.12,0:33:30.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一點也沒有射出來的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.73,0:33:36.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.03,0:33:40.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.04,0:33:44.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用屁穴高潮掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.14,0:33:48.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.15,0:33:53.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在讓我多看看
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.55,0:33:56.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又要插進屁穴裏面了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.66,0:34:08.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 又插進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.47,0:34:12.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎 我又插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.37,0:34:23.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一邊用手行插進你的屁穴裏面\N一邊幫你舔著肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.39,0:34:38.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害好厲害\N夾得好緊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.40,0:34:43.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行裏面好緊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.11,0:34:54.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.42,0:35:10.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光是插進底穴裏面\N肉棒就變得這麼的堅硬
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.93,0:35:17.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.43,0:35:17.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又變緊了\N我又要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.73,0:35:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又變緊了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.74,0:35:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.44,0:35:27.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變得好緊裏面好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.94,0:35:30.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面好熱
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.05,0:35:33.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好帶感
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.16,0:35:50.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用屁穴高潮掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.27,0:35:53.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.87,0:36:00.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就是用這個手指插進了\N你的屁穴裏面的呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.79,0:36:13.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抖得這麼厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.49,0:36:16.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓你感受更多的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.60,0:36:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏就是我的肉穴哦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.61,0:36:36.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓你爽翻天
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.34,0:37:06.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的屁穴又一次的把我的\N手指夾著不放了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.70,0:38:04.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看沒當我摸到你的屁穴\N你的歐金金就是一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.03,0:38:31.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的好厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.73,0:38:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,每當高潮的時候\N屁穴就會緊緊的夾著我手指不放
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.54,0:38:41.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了防止我拔出去所以緊緊的夾著
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.55,0:38:53.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒也硬邦邦的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.48,0:39:26.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺怎麼樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.48,0:39:30.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.59,0:39:35.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你又高潮了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.40,0:39:44.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴真的就這麼舒服的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.30,0:39:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,濕嗒嗒的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.61,0:39:55.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的就那麼的舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.02,0:40:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽翻天了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.13,0:40:17.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下來不僅僅是屁穴
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.43,0:40:19.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想要我的肉穴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.26,0:40:47.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光是肉穴就滿足了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.47,0:40:52.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏面也想要的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.67,0:40:55.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以插進去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.99,0:41:12.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.40,0:41:25.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺怎麼樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.80,0:41:30.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴和肉穴一起干很舒服吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.01,0:41:37.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 肉穴裏面好舒服\N歐金金不斷的在變硬呢
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.93,0:41:51.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.94,0:42:03.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你又高潮了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.84,0:42:07.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是不錯的呢\N高潮時候的緊致度是最棒的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.76,0:42:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你高潮了吧？\N但是你覺得是射精了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.86,0:42:25.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要看看嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.57,0:42:32.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看 精子根本就沒有射出來
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.77,0:42:34.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是卻高潮了呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.77,0:42:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害！
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.28,0:42:43.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒還是硬邦邦的狀態
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.68,0:42:48.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看著哦 又要插進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:08.30,0:43:11.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屈穴裏面很希望我把手指插\N進去的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.01,0:43:15.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看你這裏已經濕嗒嗒的了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:17.91,0:43:18.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:21.22,0:43:23.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我要插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:43:28.73,0:43:30.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲皆變得好硬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:35.03,0:43:37.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還可以繼續做的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:43:37.43,0:43:39.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再接著高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:43:39.84,0:43:41.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓你高潮的樣子再讓我多看看
Dialogue: 0,0:43:54.25,0:43:55.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:04.46,0:44:09.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害你的這裏好緊\N屁穴裏面緊緊的夾著我的手指
Dialogue: 0,0:44:09.87,0:44:10.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.47,0:44:15.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金也在肉穴裏面一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.08,0:44:21.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.58,0:44:21.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.18,0:44:23.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.29,0:44:32.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏好濕
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.19,0:44:36.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴和歐金金都好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:44:41.40,0:44:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都高潮了這麼多次了\N這回就讓你真正的把精液射出來
Dialogue: 0,0:44:51.91,0:44:54.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最後一次
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.31,0:44:56.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就讓我看看你那純白色的精液
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.51,0:45:02.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會給你做更多舒服的事情的\N公會讓你繼續高潮的哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.33,0:45:11.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再感受更多舒服的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.33,0:45:16.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種狀態的射精可是天上人間哦
Dialogue: 0,0:45:24.94,0:45:26.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害裏面又緊緊的
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.04,0:45:29.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吶 屁穴裏面夾得好緊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.35,0:45:36.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,越進去越緊越抽動越緊
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.55,0:45:37.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.85,0:45:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的手指被裏面夾得好緊
Dialogue: 0,0:45:49.87,0:45:51.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害歐金金又變得硬邦邦的了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:02.18,0:46:03.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:03.38,0:46:05.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 快點給我射出來
Dialogue: 0,0:46:11.49,0:46:12.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲殼
Dialogue: 0,0:46:14.49,0:46:18.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害好厲害光是動動手指\N就一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:26.20,0:46:28.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吶 你的這裏真的好厲韋
Dialogue: 0,0:46:30.41,0:46:31.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好贊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:31.91,0:46:34.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了好遠
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.42,0:46:43.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的屁穴還在夾著我的手指哦
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.02,0:46:49.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看這裏 我要拔出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:46:55.03,0:46:55.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.54,0:47:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴的裏面一直都在一抖一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:47:05.84,0:47:09.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然把精子射飛這麼遠
Dialogue: 0,0:47:10.65,0:47:12.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玩得很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:13.65,0:47:14.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:16.65,0:47:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這麼的舒服嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:22.66,0:47:23.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:30.17,0:47:31.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玩得還舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:47:34.37,0:47:37.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,|比你至今為止的做愛都還要舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:39.78,0:47:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:02.90,0:48:05.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暈掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:48:15.51,0:48:15.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:15.81,0:48:16.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.11,0:48:16.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.41,0:48:16.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.71,0:48:18.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第三章 極致脫魂快感調教
Dialogue: 0,0:48:23.62,0:48:24.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們開始吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:48:25.42,0:48:26.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,開…開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.63,0:48:30.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這是要玩哪出啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:48:30.83,0:48:32.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個嗎\N嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:48:32.33,0:48:33.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下來要
Dialogue: 0,0:48:33.83,0:48:38.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了讓你變得舒服的淮備
Dialogue: 0,0:48:38.64,0:48:40.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來是這樣啊\N就是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:48:41.04,0:48:41.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還請多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:48:42.24,0:48:44.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才是請多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.94,0:48:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得舒服的地方是哪裏啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:49.15,0:48:50.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全身吧\N全身啊
Dialogue: 0,0:48:51.55,0:48:52.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對全身
Dialogue: 0,0:48:52.75,0:48:56.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那耳朵和脖子還有乳頭和肉棒都很舒服吧？\N是的
Dialogue: 0,0:48:58.45,0:48:59.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股的洞穴也舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:49:00.26,0:49:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裏的話我還沒玩過
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.66,0:49:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有那方面的經驗
Dialogue: 0,0:49:04.76,0:49:05.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:05.66,0:49:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:49:06.56,0:49:08.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還沒體驗過嗎\N是的 還是為體驗
Dialogue: 0,0:49:08.67,0:49:09.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼東西也沒有插進去過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:49:10.77,0:49:11.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幾乎沒有過
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.57,0:49:13.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.07,0:49:14.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.37,0:49:14.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.67,0:49:14.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.97,0:49:16.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我今天可高興了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.77,0:49:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:20.08,0:49:20.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.28,0:49:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來是這樣的啊\N是的
Dialogue: 0,0:49:24.88,0:49:25.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.99,0:49:32.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的歐金金已經勃起了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:49:32.39,0:49:33.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:49:33.89,0:49:35.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要道歉啊 完全沒事的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:49:36.89,0:49:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你敏感的肉棒和乳頭我全部都很喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:49:42.90,0:49:45.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光是看到我就有點小性奮
Dialogue: 0,0:49:45.90,0:49:46.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:49:48.91,0:49:52.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那還不是因為都還沒做什麼\N你的肉棒就已經變得硬邦邦的了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:56.71,0:49:57.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:57.91,0:50:00.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟乳頭跟歐金金樣
Dialogue: 0,0:50:00.32,0:50:01.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好丟人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:50:01.82,0:50:03.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,害羞嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:50:03.92,0:50:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看你的歐金金勃起的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:50:08.12,0:50:10.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看在你的內褲裏面\N看起來非常的苦痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:50:10.53,0:50:11.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:12.03,0:50:13.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以脫掉嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:50:13.23,0:50:14.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:15.33,0:50:16.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:20.14,0:50:21.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好雄壯
Dialogue: 0,0:50:23.14,0:50:25.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金已經硬邦邦的了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:50:26.44,0:50:27.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:50:28.24,0:50:29.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好大呀
Dialogue: 0,0:50:29.45,0:50:29.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:29.75,0:50:30.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:31.25,0:50:31.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:36.05,0:50:38.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常的堅硬哦
Dialogue: 0,0:50:38.76,0:50:40.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,硬邦邦的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.27,0:50:53.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如何
Dialogue: 0,0:50:55.27,0:50:56.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼啦？
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.08,0:51:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個僅僅只是吐了點口水\N上去而已哦
Dialogue: 0,0:51:05.78,0:51:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的好敏感
Dialogue: 0,0:51:08.79,0:51:10.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:51:35.21,0:51:37.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你能夠感受得到我在摸你的屁股嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:51:39.42,0:51:42.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能夠感覺摸到裏面了\N感覺好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:51:45.72,0:51:49.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在是插進你的屁眼裏而了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:51:50.53,0:51:51.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏
Dialogue: 0,0:51:55.93,0:51:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來檢查檢查
Dialogue: 0,0:51:59.24,0:52:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞\N有什麼害羞的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:52:04.04,0:52:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然害羞但是很舒服的\N所以就別管了
Dialogue: 0,0:52:11.25,0:52:12.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:14.85,0:52:15.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:52:29.87,0:52:30.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抖得好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:52:45.78,0:52:47.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣?插入進去的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:52:48.79,0:52:50.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然只是摸摸
Dialogue: 0,0:52:55.99,0:52:58.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光是摸摸的話不能滿足你的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:53:00.50,0:53:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下來就讓我來教你爽\N上天的做法
Dialogue: 0,0:53:05.60,0:53:06.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,首先是
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.80,0:53:08.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先放鬆身體\N好的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.51,0:53:11.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,張開雙腿
Dialogue: 0,0:53:13.11,0:53:14.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像女生那樣張開腿
Dialogue: 0,0:53:16.71,0:53:18.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好羞恥
Dialogue: 0,0:53:19.12,0:53:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全身放鬆下來\N慢慢的一步步的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:44.64,0:53:46.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股那邊我還沒有開始正式的玩弄哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:53:49.15,0:53:52.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好敏感
Dialogue: 0,0:53:57.85,0:53:58.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身體放鬆下來
Dialogue: 0,0:53:59.36,0:54:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:01.46,0:54:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行?\N我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:11.97,0:54:13.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先放鬆身體
Dialogue: 0,0:54:15.27,0:54:17.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插進去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:54:19.18,0:54:20.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面好緊
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.58,0:54:23.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:54:30.59,0:54:32.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抖得這麼厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:54:55.21,0:54:56.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了去了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:04.22,0:55:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:55:08.12,0:55:11.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明沒有射出來就高潮了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:55:12.33,0:55:13.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個是因為
Dialogue: 0,0:55:13.83,0:55:15.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,絕頂高潮就是這樣的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:55:18.03,0:55:20.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一次做這個感覺怎 麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:21.34,0:55:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很爽的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:55:23.44,0:55:26.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股的洞穴裏非常的炙熱
Dialogue: 0,0:55:29.45,0:55:31.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明都插這麼進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:33.95,0:55:36.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看稍微動下就會\N進到深處去了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:55:47.46,0:55:48.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.27,0:55:51.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放過我吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:55:53.17,0:55:54.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太丟臉了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:55.27,0:55:57.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的中指過經濕嗒嗒的了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:55:59.18,0:56:01.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.29,0:56:18.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放進兩根手指的話\N不知道會變成什麼樣子呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:56:19.60,0:56:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧？把雙腳分開點
Dialogue: 0,0:56:22.90,0:56:25.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又要插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:56:37.91,0:56:38.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:56:41.82,0:56:43.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服對吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:48.12,0:56:54.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金好硬\N屁股的洞穴裏也非常的緊
Dialogue: 0,0:56:57.73,0:56:59.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:57:00.14,0:57:04.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股裏面也很厲害呢\N緊緊的纏著我的手指
Dialogue: 0,0:57:06.44,0:57:07.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒越來越硬了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:08.55,0:57:10.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:16.95,0:57:17.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:57:18.76,0:57:20.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股緊緊的夾著我的手指
Dialogue: 0,0:57:21.46,0:57:23.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射出一大堆黏糊糊的精子
Dialogue: 0,0:57:26.26,0:57:29.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:57:33.17,0:57:35.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了好多
Dialogue: 0,0:57:36.77,0:57:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在一抖一抖呢
Dialogue: 0,0:57:38.88,0:57:40.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我動下手指就會一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,0:57:46.08,0:57:49.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒不行?\N不能拔出來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:57:49.69,0:57:51.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要拔出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:57:57.79,0:57:59.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:58:01.70,0:58:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股的裏面和肚子上面都粘乎乎的
Dialogue: 0,0:58:11.61,0:58:13.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛才真正的射精了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:58:14.91,0:58:18.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了這麼多黏糊糊的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:58:20.62,0:58:22.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:58:27.52,0:58:29.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第四章 淫語回春美容沙龍
Dialogue: 0,0:58:29.93,0:58:31.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:34.73,0:58:37.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天選擇本店真是十分感謝！
Dialogue: 0,0:58:38.03,0:58:40.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天還請多多指教呢
Dialogue: 0,0:58:41.04,0:58:41.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:58:41.64,0:58:42.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請多指教\N好的
Dialogue: 0,0:58:43.14,0:58:44.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我就拿掉這邊的毛巾了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:49.45,0:58:51.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這位客人
Dialogue: 0,0:58:51.85,0:58:56.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,首先這個毛巾上女性用的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:58:57.25,0:58:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您為什麼會戴著這個啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:59:02.36,0:59:03.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:59:07.16,0:59:09.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那現在我是開始清洗您的身體
Dialogue: 0,0:59:20.38,0:59:22.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我失禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:25.18,0:59:25.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:59:27.28,0:59:29.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力度怎麼樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:59:31.79,0:59:33.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:35.09,0:59:36.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身體有點僵硬呢
Dialogue: 0,0:59:39.00,0:59:40.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我注意到了的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:45.30,0:59:48.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個有點礙事我可以\N脫掉嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:59:56.41,0:59:58.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的 脫掉了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:03.62,1:00:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是下流的乳頭
Dialogue: 0,1:00:08.42,1:00:10.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用那麼害羞的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:00:11.43,1:00:13.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我經常看護乳頭的
Dialogue: 0,1:00:16.83,1:00:17.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:00:17.13,1:00:20.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要開始這邊的按摩了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:00:29.45,1:00:32.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我失禮了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:36.35,1:00:37.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:00:38.76,1:00:40.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,客人您非常的敏感呢
Dialogue: 0,1:01:04.28,1:01:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺客人您
Dialogue: 0,1:01:07.28,1:01:09.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下面已經完全勃起了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:11.49,1:01:13.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:01:14.79,1:01:16.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:01:18.39,1:01:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:01:25.60,1:01:27.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在感覺更多也是可以的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:30.71,1:01:36.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,客人您的蛋蛋從內褲裏面\N露出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:37.61,1:01:39.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,內褲有點小是不是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:01:46.62,1:01:50.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼這個下流的地方我也要開始\N按摩了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:01:54.13,1:01:56.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,1:02:16.95,1:02:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,客人您非常的緊張呢
Dialogue: 0,1:02:20.86,1:02:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:02:21.16,1:02:23.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是按摩按摩歐金金而已哦
Dialogue: 0,1:02:26.56,1:02:28.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做了這種事情害我都變熱\N起來了
Dialogue: 0,1:02:33.47,1:02:36.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可以脫掉衣服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:02:39.18,1:02:40.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我失禮了
Dialogue: 0,1:02:43.38,1:02:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:02:50.59,1:02:52.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,客人
Dialogue: 0,1:02:53.89,1:02:55.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個是什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:57.19,1:03:00.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是已經硬邦邦的了嘛！？
Dialogue: 0,1:03:03.50,1:03:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好硬啊
Dialogue: 0,1:03:11.01,1:03:18.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看見客人您這個樣子\N我就越來越想要您變得更舒服了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:03:25.72,1:03:28.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看見這麼硬邦邦的雞雞
Dialogue: 0,1:03:32.63,1:03:34.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連我都
Dialogue: 0,1:03:35.03,1:03:37.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺
Dialogue: 0,1:03:38.03,1:03:40.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變得性奮起來了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:03:58.45,1:04:02.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您不想變得更加更加的舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:04:05.06,1:04:11.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼前列腺的按摩開始了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:04:13.77,1:04:15.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我先準備好
Dialogue: 0,1:04:17.07,1:04:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請稍微等一下呢
Dialogue: 0,1:04:20.38,1:04:22.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您這就張開了雙腿
Dialogue: 0,1:04:22.78,1:04:25.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想快點讓我手指插進去嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:04:27.28,1:04:30.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做出這麼變態的姿勢
Dialogue: 0,1:04:31.19,1:04:34.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您這是在誘惑我嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:04:34.49,1:04:36.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您真的很變態呢
Dialogue: 0,1:04:37.19,1:04:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過我最喜歡像您這樣的變態
Dialogue: 0,1:04:40.50,1:04:41.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,1:04:42.30,1:04:44.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就開始幫您按摩了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:04:54.91,1:05:00.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒?我只是摸了摸你厄股的洞穴
Dialogue: 0,1:05:00.32,1:05:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這不已經濕嗒嗒的了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:05:04.52,1:05:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然變態的人就是不一樣呢
Dialogue: 0,1:05:10.23,1:05:11.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,1:05:12.03,1:05:13.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就特別的為您
Dialogue: 0,1:05:15.93,1:05:18.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像這樣做怎麼樣啊？
Dialogue: 0,1:05:23.14,1:05:26.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您很營歡被這樣做的吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:05:33.05,1:05:35.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股的洞穴
Dialogue: 0,1:05:35.45,1:05:37.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看得非常的清楚哦
Dialogue: 0,1:05:40.86,1:05:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,洞穴都在開始吸允我的手指了
Dialogue: 0,1:05:54.37,1:05:55.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:05:57.67,1:05:59.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛才吸進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:06:02.78,1:06:04.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您的哪裏有感覺啊？
Dialogue: 0,1:06:11.19,1:06:14.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏 這裏嗎?好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:06:15.69,1:06:19.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連蛋蛋都變得一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:06:25.30,1:06:28.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金也已經硬邦邦的呢
Dialogue: 0,1:06:30.11,1:06:33.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然變態就是和一般人不一樣呢！
Dialogue: 0,1:06:34.01,1:06:37.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做出這樣丟臉的姿勢
Dialogue: 0,1:06:38.21,1:06:40.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒居然會變得硬邦邦的
Dialogue: 0,1:06:41.52,1:06:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經變得很興奮了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:06:45.42,1:06:46.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:06:50.83,1:06:52.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:06:53.83,1:06:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,緊緊的夾著我的手指
Dialogue: 0,1:07:12.15,1:07:19.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看你的屁股直在收縮\N連我的指尖都有感覺了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:21.46,1:07:24.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對就是這樣\N再有感覺點也是可以的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:07:25.66,1:07:28.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很想看見您那舒服的表情
Dialogue: 0,1:07:30.77,1:07:33.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吶 告訴我你的敏感處吧
Dialogue: 0,1:07:37.67,1:07:39.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:07:44.88,1:07:47.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變得越來越舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:08:09.21,1:08:11.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能一個人擅自都就高潮哦
Dialogue: 0,1:08:12.21,1:08:14.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮的時候費好好的給我說哦
Dialogue: 0,1:08:15.81,1:08:23.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我非常的想看見\N您高潮時候的表情
Dialogue: 0,1:08:29.02,1:08:31.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經這樣的
Dialogue: 0,1:08:33.23,1:08:35.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一進一出
Dialogue: 0,1:08:42.54,1:08:44.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的很舒服對吧
Dialogue: 0,1:08:47.94,1:08:50.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是這裏嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:08:50.35,1:08:52.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏到底怎麼樣啊？
Dialogue: 0,1:08:53.65,1:08:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏還是那裏?
Dialogue: 0,1:09:06.26,1:09:09.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我很舒服嗎?
Dialogue: 0,1:09:09.87,1:09:13.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我僅僅只是摸了摸您的屁股\N您居然就發出了如此下流的聲音！
Dialogue: 0,1:09:26.08,1:09:26.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:09:30.89,1:09:32.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面抖動得非常的厲氣
Dialogue: 0,1:09:33.59,1:09:35.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股裏面變得好緊
Dialogue: 0,1:09:37.19,1:09:39.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮的時候記得給我講
Dialogue: 0,1:09:46.20,1:09:49.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要高潮了嗎\N快點給我說出來啊
Dialogue: 0,1:10:00.92,1:10:04.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您看您的裏面收縮得非常的緊
Dialogue: 0,1:10:06.32,1:10:08.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:10:10.53,1:10:12.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好高興
Dialogue: 0,1:10:13.53,1:10:16.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,畢競手指插入到深處了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:10:21.04,1:10:23.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然這麼的
Dialogue: 0,1:10:24.34,1:10:26.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插到了深處
Dialogue: 0,1:10:33.65,1:10:36.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您看插到了這麼深的位置
Dialogue: 0,1:10:37.55,1:10:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您居然這麼的有感覺
Dialogue: 0,1:10:40.56,1:10:42.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是變態到極致了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:10:43.86,1:10:46.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我最營歡您這樣的變態哦
Dialogue: 0,1:10:48.97,1:10:54.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您看您的肉棒\N忍耐汁居然流出了這麼多來
Dialogue: 0,1:11:11.19,1:11:14.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您是在忍著不射精嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:11:19.30,1:11:25.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您是想真正的把精液射出來嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:11:30.71,1:11:32.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像這樣
Dialogue: 0,1:11:33.41,1:11:35.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手指插到菊花深處
Dialogue: 0,1:11:36.71,1:11:39.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後一邊幫你擼肉棒\N可是最舒服的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:11:42.72,1:11:45.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽翻天了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:11:49.33,1:11:51.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒已經硬邦邦的了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:12:02.84,1:12:04.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您的變態菊花
Dialogue: 0,1:12:05.24,1:12:09.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射出來吧\N我想看到您射出來的樣子
Dialogue: 0,1:12:09.15,1:12:13.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您的那變態菊花緊緊收緊的感覺
Dialogue: 0,1:12:14.25,1:12:16.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼的有感覺
Dialogue: 0,1:12:16.95,1:12:20.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後肉棒硬邦邦的\N我最喜歡了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:44.88,1:12:49.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,硬邦邦的肉棒和收緊的變態菊花
Dialogue: 0,1:13:00.20,1:13:02.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了嗎 快點射出來啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:09.81,1:13:11.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒也在一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:13:15.51,1:13:16.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:13:18.21,1:13:20.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然射出了這麼多
Dialogue: 0,1:13:35.33,1:13:37.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:39.24,1:13:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然會射出來這麼的精子
Dialogue: 0,1:13:43.44,1:13:43.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:13:43.74,1:13:46.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股的洞穴就這麼的舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:13:46.74,1:13:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:13:48.55,1:13:50.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都插入到了深叢
Dialogue: 0,1:13:53.65,1:13:55.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然射出這麼多
Dialogue: 0,1:13:56.65,1:13:58.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的手指還沒有從菊花裏面出來呢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:01.46,1:14:03.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:14:05.06,1:14:08.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精子射飛得這麼遠
Dialogue: 0,1:14:08.97,1:14:11.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您的屁穴果然很厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:13.77,1:14:16.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您看著 我要拔出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:14:23.38,1:14:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:14:24.88,1:14:29.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的手指上沾滿了您屁穴\N裏流出的愛液
Dialogue: 0,1:14:40.20,1:14:44.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然射出來這麼多的精液
Dialogue: 0,1:14:47.40,1:14:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼黏糊糊的精液
Dialogue: 0,1:14:53.11,1:14:56.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平時是不會射出這樣的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:14:57.01,1:14:59.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為這是一邊在玩弄你的菊花
Dialogue: 0,1:15:01.22,1:15:03.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才會導致您射出來這樣的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:15:05.12,1:15:07.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您真變態
Dialogue: 0,1:15:18.03,1:15:19.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您感覺怎麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,1:15:19.84,1:15:21.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,絕頂高潮後的射精
Dialogue: 0,1:15:24.04,1:15:25.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最棒的吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:15:31.55,1:15:33.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然抖動得這麼激烈
Dialogue: 0,1:15:35.15,1:15:42.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼舒服的事情\N做其他的時候也不會有的吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:15:51.37,1:15:53.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玩得還舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:15:55.57,1:15:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎您再次光顧哦
Dialogue: 0,1:16:06.38,1:16:06.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:16:19.60,1:16:21.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害的敏感度
Dialogue: 0,1:16:22.90,1:16:24.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:16:24.40,1:16:25.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:16:26.50,1:16:28.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等下有更舒服的事情等著你的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:17:10.35,1:17:13.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想要我的口水的吧\N想要
Dialogue: 0,1:17:14.25,1:17:15.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把嘴巴張開
Dialogue: 0,1:17:22.06,1:17:23.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幫我把這裏的口水舔掉
Dialogue: 0,1:17:27.76,1:17:29.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:17:29.57,1:17:29.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:17:47.58,1:17:49.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭就已經勃起了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:17:49.99,1:17:50.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為非常的舒服\N乳頭就已經勃起了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:17:50.29,1:17:52.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為非常的舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:17:52.39,1:17:53.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服?
Dialogue: 0,1:17:53.29,1:17:53.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服\N舒服?
Dialogue: 0,1:17:53.59,1:17:54.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:17:55.09,1:17:57.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聲音在大聲一點
Dialogue: 0,1:17:57.79,1:17:59.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞
Dialogue: 0,1:17:59.30,1:17:59.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,害羞才會覺得舒服吧？\N好害羞
Dialogue: 0,1:17:59.90,1:18:01.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,害羞才會覺得舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:18:04.40,1:18:07.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害抖抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:18:08.00,1:18:10.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很喜歡我幫你舔乳頭嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:18:12.51,1:18:15.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很喜歡這樣嗎\N很喜歡
Dialogue: 0,1:18:33.23,1:18:34.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:18:34.73,1:18:36.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:18:37.43,1:18:39.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有更舒服的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:18:42.24,1:18:44.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看你這裏
Dialogue: 0,1:18:44.94,1:18:46.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,內褲裏面鼓起的歐金金
Dialogue: 0,1:18:55.75,1:18:58.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏面發出了淫蕩的味道
Dialogue: 0,1:19:04.76,1:19:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒也非常的有感覺了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:09.87,1:19:11.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏也很喜歡的吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:19:12.87,1:19:14.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很喜歡對吧
Dialogue: 0,1:19:19.78,1:19:22.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點說請把你的手指趕緊\N插到自己的菊花裏面
Dialogue: 0,1:19:24.28,1:19:26.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股的洞穴飢渴難耐了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:28.48,1:19:29.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞
Dialogue: 0,1:19:30.29,1:19:33.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,害羞嗎\N那就讓你感覺到更害鑿吧
Dialogue: 0,1:19:35.09,1:19:37.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把屁股轉過來
Dialogue: 0,1:19:39.00,1:19:41.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把屁股翹著對著我
Dialogue: 0,1:19:49.81,1:19:54.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害\N一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:20:07.82,1:20:09.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我故意讓它陷進去的
Dialogue: 0,1:20:11.73,1:20:15.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,內褲陷進去屁股就會一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:20:28.55,1:20:30.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看你這個發熱的屁股
Dialogue: 0,1:20:32.45,1:20:33.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好丟臉呀
Dialogue: 0,1:20:34.55,1:20:36.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點讓我看你的屁股
Dialogue: 0,1:20:40.86,1:20:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金變硬擋住了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:20:45.06,1:20:45.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:20:54.37,1:20:54.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,1:20:54.67,1:20:56.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,1:20:56.17,1:20:56.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,1:21:06.98,1:21:12.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個位置的話不管是屁穴還是蛋蛋\N還是雞雞全部都看得很清楚哦
Dialogue: 0,1:21:25.60,1:21:29.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的口水讓你的屁穴\N粘糊糊的了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:21:38.21,1:21:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想讓我幫你舔屁股嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:21:39.12,1:21:40.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要你幫我舔
Dialogue: 0,1:21:40.62,1:21:41.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼?
Dialogue: 0,1:21:41.52,1:21:42.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要你幫我舔
Dialogue: 0,1:21:43.92,1:21:44.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我就幫你舔了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:22:13.95,1:22:16.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:22:19.96,1:22:22.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再讓你感覺更多的快感哦
Dialogue: 0,1:22:31.37,1:22:33.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:22:41.28,1:22:45.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,僅僅只是舔了舔你的菊花\N歐金金的前端就流出忍耐汁了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:22:45.78,1:22:46.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起對不起
Dialogue: 0,1:23:02.60,1:23:04.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:23:08.91,1:23:09.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:23:11.01,1:23:15.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,每次我舔歐金金\N你的屁穴就會抖抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:23:17.01,1:23:18.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趕緊說快點把我的手指\N插進你的屈穴裏面
Dialogue: 0,1:23:22.42,1:23:24.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,往這個屁穴裏面
Dialogue: 0,1:23:26.32,1:23:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:23:27.82,1:23:29.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:23:30.83,1:23:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一邊幫你擼歐金金
Dialogue: 0,1:23:34.13,1:23:36.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手指要插進去了哦！
Dialogue: 0,1:23:36.53,1:23:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要插進你的屁六里面了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:23:39.54,1:23:41.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插進這個一抖一抖的屁股裏面
Dialogue: 0,1:23:43.74,1:23:47.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面好厲害\N這個屁穴是什麼情況啊？
Dialogue: 0,1:23:48.55,1:23:51.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:23:52.45,1:23:53.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不要呀
Dialogue: 0,1:23:53.95,1:23:58.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行?一邊喊著不行\N屁穴卻緊緊的夾著我的手指
Dialogue: 0,1:23:58.45,1:23:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:23:59.66,1:24:01.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:24:03.26,1:24:05.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 要被屁股吸進去了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:05.66,1:24:05.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:24:08.36,1:24:10.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:17.37,1:24:20.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個好厲害啊\N手指全部插進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:24:21.88,1:24:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏很舒服嗎\N很舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:24:24.28,1:24:25.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的很變態呢
Dialogue: 0,1:24:27.58,1:24:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 我不想當變態
Dialogue: 0,1:24:29.09,1:24:31.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不想當變態嗎 我可是很喜歡變態的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:24:33.29,1:24:35.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變得更丟臉吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:24:35.39,1:24:37.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服\N很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:24:37.79,1:24:39.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服的地方變得更爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:44.70,1:24:48.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好厲害啊\N這個屁穴吸得實得實在是太緊了
Dialogue: 0,1:24:50.71,1:24:57.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,每當我這樣對底穴插入插出\N歐金金就會變得越來越硬
Dialogue: 0,1:24:58.21,1:25:00.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去光靠手指\N我就會有感覺了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:25:05.72,1:25:07.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,1:25:20.44,1:25:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,民穴裏面很想要手指插進去的吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:25:22.54,1:25:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想要
Dialogue: 0,1:25:25.24,1:25:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的肉棒已經硬邦邦的在抖動了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:25:27.94,1:25:30.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又要高潮了嗎\N是的
Dialogue: 0,1:25:30.95,1:25:33.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來了來了！
Dialogue: 0,1:25:37.85,1:25:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部插進去了哦！
Dialogue: 0,1:25:41.46,1:25:43.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:25:44.16,1:25:50.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部插進去了？我的手指\N被你的屁穴全部系進去了哦！
Dialogue: 0,1:25:52.87,1:25:55.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒也硬邦邦的\N屁穴也收縮得這麼緊
Dialogue: 0,1:25:56.47,1:25:58.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行\N這樣做不行嗎?
Dialogue: 0,1:25:58.58,1:26:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害\N很厲害嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:26:00.98,1:26:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害\N繼續說啊
Dialogue: 0,1:26:03.68,1:26:05.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會讓你的這裏更加的舒服的
Dialogue: 0,1:26:06.98,1:26:09.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面緊緊的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:26:09.99,1:26:10.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:26:12.39,1:26:13.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:26:14.79,1:26:16.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服的吧?\N很舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:26:17.49,1:26:18.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:26:36.11,1:26:38.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又把我的 手指吸進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:26:38.82,1:26:42.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 你真的好厲岸
Dialogue: 0,1:26:48.42,1:26:50.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊不行 手指又進來了
Dialogue: 0,1:26:50.53,1:26:54.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴和肉棒都很有感覺哦\N你真的好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:26:57.13,1:26:59.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手指被吞進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:27:03.74,1:27:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:27:10.95,1:27:13.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:27:13.35,1:27:15.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再讓你做更多舒服的事情呢
Dialogue: 0,1:27:16.35,1:27:18.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請幫我做\N我會幫你做的
Dialogue: 0,1:27:34.37,1:27:35.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:27:37.97,1:27:40.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊不行 好厲害 身體都脫力了
Dialogue: 0,1:27:41.28,1:27:43.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服得沒氣力了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:27:44.88,1:27:46.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又要插進裏面去了哦\N好的
Dialogue: 0,1:27:48.79,1:27:49.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:27:50.89,1:27:52.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插進來了\N進來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:27:52.99,1:27:53.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:27:53.29,1:27:53.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:27:53.89,1:27:54.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:27:54.19,1:27:54.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:28:00.50,1:28:02.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害好厲害\N夾得越來越緊了
Dialogue: 0,1:28:02.60,1:28:02.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:28:05.30,1:28:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:28:08.00,1:28:11.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽好舒服\N很帶感嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:28:13.41,1:28:15.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏面也好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:28:18.21,1:28:19.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給我更多更多的快感
Dialogue: 0,1:28:20.02,1:28:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:28:22.12,1:28:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊那裏那裏好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:28:27.82,1:28:28.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面變得好緊
Dialogue: 0,1:28:52.75,1:28:54.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再讓我感受到更多的快感吧
Dialogue: 0,1:28:55.45,1:28:57.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要手指插進去嗎\N想要插進去
Dialogue: 0,1:28:58.15,1:28:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插到深處去嗎\N想要想要
Dialogue: 0,1:29:00.26,1:29:02.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個屈穴真的是很淫蕩呢\N對不起
Dialogue: 0,1:29:02.96,1:29:05.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為實在是太舒服了嘛\N很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:29:06.56,1:29:08.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部插進去屁穴裏面了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:29:08.97,1:29:09.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,1:29:10.17,1:29:12.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的這裏真的是很厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:29:13.77,1:29:15.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏很舒服嗎?
Dialogue: 0,1:29:17.67,1:29:19.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都怪你害我的肉穴\N都跟著有感覺了
Dialogue: 0,1:29:20.38,1:29:22.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把手指插進屁穴裏面去的話
Dialogue: 0,1:29:26.68,1:29:28.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要我幫你做更多的嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:29:34.79,1:29:35.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太爽太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,1:29:47.10,1:29:48.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:29:52.21,1:29:55.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行不行啊
Dialogue: 0,1:30:11.13,1:30:12.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股裏面好緊
Dialogue: 0,1:30:19.84,1:30:21.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面抽動得非常的激烈
Dialogue: 0,1:30:22.54,1:30:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你高潮掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:30:26.74,1:30:27.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺怎麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,1:30:27.94,1:30:28.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服\N感覺怎麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,1:30:28.85,1:30:29.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:30:31.85,1:30:33.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又去掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:30:40.56,1:30:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的這裏真厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,1:30:55.27,1:30:57.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是太厲害了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:30:57.67,1:30:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的就這麼的舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:30:59.78,1:31:02.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那這回換你來讓我舒服了
Dialogue: 0,1:31:04.58,1:31:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自從我手指放進你的屁穴裏面\N我的肉穴就一直是濕嗒嗒的
Dialogue: 0,1:31:28.91,1:31:30.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:31:30.71,1:31:32.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服嗎\N嗯
Dialogue: 0,1:31:34.31,1:31:36.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從剛才就在抽搐呢
Dialogue: 0,1:31:37.31,1:31:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在幫你多舔舔
Dialogue: 0,1:31:40.92,1:31:41.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:31:52.63,1:31:53.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 太爽了
Dialogue: 0,1:31:54.73,1:31:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:32:05.24,1:32:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等下 我的肉穴裏面
Dialogue: 0,1:32:09.45,1:32:11.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等下 你好狡猾啊
Dialogue: 0,1:32:12.45,1:32:13.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:32:13.65,1:32:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也好舒服哦\N好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:32:14.25,1:32:15.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也好舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:16.95,1:32:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起變得舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:32:44.58,1:32:45.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:32:59.30,1:33:01.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行 要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:33:04.10,1:33:07.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行去了去了去了
Dialogue: 0,1:33:24.52,1:33:25.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:33:29.33,1:33:31.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害\N不行不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:33:34.73,1:33:35.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:33:43.44,1:33:44.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:33:44.64,1:33:46.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:33:53.05,1:33:55.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有高潮了嗎\N好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:34:04.46,1:34:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏面插進手指很舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:18.58,1:34:20.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想做更多舒服的事情
Dialogue: 0,1:34:23.08,1:34:24.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看這個
Dialogue: 0,1:34:27.88,1:34:29.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把這個
Dialogue: 0,1:34:32.99,1:34:35.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放進屁穴裏面的話
Dialogue: 0,1:34:39.60,1:34:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那樣我尚定會瘋掉的我不要
Dialogue: 0,1:34:44.10,1:34:44.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太丟人了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:34:44.70,1:34:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很丟人嗎?\N太丟人了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:34:45.00,1:34:46.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很丟人嗎?
Dialogue: 0,1:34:47.10,1:34:49.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丟瞼才會讓人舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:51.61,1:34:52.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:34:52.21,1:34:54.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要給你放進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:34:57.31,1:35:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屈穴和肉棒兩個一起讓你爽翻天呢
Dialogue: 0,1:35:03.62,1:35:05.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行進來了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:35:07.22,1:35:09.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的屁穴再說快點進來忍不住了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:35:10.53,1:35:12.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎\N你自己看嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:35:12.33,1:35:12.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎\N你自己看嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:35:12.63,1:35:14.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別啊 別放進去啊
Dialogue: 0,1:35:16.23,1:35:17.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插進來了!
Dialogue: 0,1:35:24.34,1:35:26.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看你這裏好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:35:28.85,1:35:30.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個好殘忍
Dialogue: 0,1:35:37.85,1:35:38.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點讓我去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:35:38.76,1:35:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我這就讓你高潮\N快點讓我去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:35:39.96,1:35:40.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我這就讓你高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:35:40.56,1:35:40.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的好厲害啊\N我這就讓你高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:35:40.86,1:35:41.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:35:42.96,1:35:43.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看你的屁股
Dialogue: 0,1:35:45.66,1:35:47.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:35:52.87,1:35:54.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服\N很舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:35:56.77,1:35:57.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽\N很帶勁的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:36:01.58,1:36:04.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屈穴和雞雞都很想舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:36:05.78,1:36:07.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經不知道哪裏舒服了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:09.39,1:36:11.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,分不清楚了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:14.49,1:36:16.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:36:16.59,1:36:18.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把跳蛋吸進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:19.00,1:36:21.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的是太厲害了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:21.40,1:36:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部進去了哦 太厲害了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:24.10,1:36:25.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,進去了嗎進去了嗎\N進去了哦進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:36:28.00,1:36:28.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:36:29.21,1:36:31.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:36:33.41,1:36:35.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所有地方都讓你爽個夠哦
Dialogue: 0,1:36:36.71,1:36:38.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光是摸就能感覺到很激烈的震動呢
Dialogue: 0,1:36:40.62,1:36:41.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太厲害了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:42.72,1:36:44.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經受不了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:36:49.63,1:36:51.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行別別這樣
Dialogue: 0,1:37:01.34,1:37:03.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裏那裏是哪裏啊
Dialogue: 0,1:37:03.74,1:37:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你猜下我在舔哪裏啊
Dialogue: 0,1:37:08.24,1:37:10.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 好舒服\N很舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:37:12.15,1:37:13.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再讓你感覺更舒服的\N好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:37:20.56,1:37:23.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的好厲害啊\N一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:37:27.46,1:37:29.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射出來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:37:30.47,1:37:32.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又高潮了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:37:32.57,1:37:34.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面抖抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:37:34.67,1:37:38.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然是一抖一抖的啊\N你看你的這裏根本就不想放跳蛋出來
Dialogue: 0,1:37:41.88,1:37:43.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴在說不想讓它出來
Dialogue: 0,1:37:47.88,1:37:49.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看出來的這個
Dialogue: 0,1:37:50.59,1:37:52.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,1:37:58.70,1:38:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃
Dialogue: 0,1:38:02.60,1:38:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然抖動得這麼厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:38:07.10,1:38:09.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下來你想要讓我對你做什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:38:09.51,1:38:10.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要停下來
Dialogue: 0,1:38:10.41,1:38:11.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要停下舒服的事情\N不要停下來
Dialogue: 0,1:38:11.31,1:38:12.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想繼續嗎\N不要停下舒服的事情
Dialogue: 0,1:38:13.11,1:38:14.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想做更加舒服的事情的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:38:18.82,1:38:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做好覺悟了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:38:23.32,1:38:25.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓你爽翻天的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:38:25.42,1:38:26.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經無法回頭了
Dialogue: 0,1:38:26.62,1:38:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是當然的啦\N我已經老法回頭了
Dialogue: 0,1:38:27.52,1:38:28.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是當然的啦
Dialogue: 0,1:38:30.53,1:38:32.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:38:36.83,1:38:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又一次的進到裏面了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:38:39.84,1:38:41.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話連手指都可以\N一起放進去的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:38:42.24,1:38:42.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:38:45.54,1:38:47.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看\N好厲害啊啊!
Dialogue: 0,1:38:47.64,1:38:49.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把手指吸進去了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:38:50.05,1:38:52.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:38:53.35,1:38:55.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:38:56.95,1:38:59.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部
Dialogue: 0,1:39:00.86,1:39:02.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個好刺激
Dialogue: 0,1:39:02.36,1:39:04.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好刺激不妙啊\N不妙？
Dialogue: 0,1:39:05.96,1:39:08.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:39:08.67,1:39:10.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽死我了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:39:12.57,1:39:14.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所有地方都會讓你舒服的
Dialogue: 0,1:39:28.18,1:39:32.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,擺出這樣下流的姿勢\N想要更舒服的嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:39:33.89,1:39:35.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,張開嘴巴
Dialogue: 0,1:39:45.90,1:39:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏面很舒服嗎\N這個這個好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:39:52.51,1:39:54.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害好厲害好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:40:07.52,1:40:09.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了去了
Dialogue: 0,1:40:13.83,1:40:14.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:40:16.53,1:40:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好帶感
Dialogue: 0,1:40:21.34,1:40:22.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服\N很舒服吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:40:22.84,1:40:23.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服\N很舒服吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:40:23.14,1:40:24.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的屁穴真厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:40:26.44,1:40:26.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:40:27.64,1:40:30.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏面濕嗒嗒黏糊糊的呢
Dialogue: 0,1:40:37.55,1:40:38.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,受不了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:40:41.46,1:40:43.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好~厲~害
Dialogue: 0,1:40:43.56,1:40:43.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:40:43.86,1:40:44.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:40:46.56,1:40:49.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然會這麼激烈的高潮
Dialogue: 0,1:40:53.47,1:40:55.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變得這麼舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:40:56.77,1:40:59.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個放進去我的肉穴\N也會黏糊糊的峨
Dialogue: 0,1:41:03.38,1:41:05.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我的肉穴也舒服起來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:41:22.30,1:41:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服\N舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:41:25.30,1:41:28.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭和肉棒的快感連接在一起
Dialogue: 0,1:41:28.30,1:41:30.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在一起的嗎?\N嗯
Dialogue: 0,1:41:31.01,1:41:33.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舔乳頭肉棒也會跟著好舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:41:36.41,1:41:38.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:41:38.51,1:41:40.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兩邊都硬邦邦的了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:41:43.92,1:41:46.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,覺得舒服嗎?
Dialogue: 0,1:42:07.34,1:42:08.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好喝嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:42:14.55,1:42:16.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想要更多舒服的事情
Dialogue: 0,1:42:16.95,1:42:19.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎 那你想被怎麼做?
Dialogue: 0,1:42:39.78,1:42:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金要插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:42:43.68,1:42:45.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常的粗大
Dialogue: 0,1:42:45.78,1:42:47.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面嘎吱嘎吱的
Dialogue: 0,1:42:54.79,1:42:55.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:42:56.59,1:42:58.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:43:09.81,1:43:11.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:43:11.91,1:43:13.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:43:15.21,1:43:17.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,實在是太爽了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:18.21,1:43:20.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的這個好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,1:43:20.62,1:43:22.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽死了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:25.72,1:43:27.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉穴的裏面好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:43:29.63,1:43:31.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等下 好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:43:36.53,1:43:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:41.34,1:43:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行去了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:54.25,1:43:56.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股 屁股插進去
Dialogue: 0,1:43:56.35,1:44:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然 你的屁股我也會好好的愛撫的哦！
Dialogue: 0,1:44:07.16,1:44:08.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被我的口水弄的濕嗒嗒的了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:44:11.37,1:44:13.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,濕嗒嗒的呢
Dialogue: 0,1:44:14.97,1:44:17.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,濕嗒嗒的屁穴裏面
Dialogue: 0,1:44:18.27,1:44:20.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又要把我的手指吸進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:44:30.29,1:44:32.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,覺得舒服嗎?
Dialogue: 0,1:44:37.49,1:44:39.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的這個好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:44:40.20,1:44:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏面有我的手指\N肉穴裏面有的你雞雞
Dialogue: 0,1:44:50.41,1:44:52.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服\N舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:44:52.81,1:44:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裏面好緊啊
Dialogue: 0,1:44:59.12,1:45:01.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也變得好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:45:03.92,1:45:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:06.32,1:45:08.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 我也要去了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:24.04,1:45:25.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:45:32.15,1:45:34.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你高潮了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:45:35.75,1:45:37.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們一起高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:47.46,1:45:49.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓你更舒服的呢
Dialogue: 0,1:46:01.28,1:46:03.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插進去了呢我又插進去了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:46:05.48,1:46:10.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個位置不管是屁穴還是\N肉棒都看得一清二楚呢
Dialogue: 0,1:46:11.79,1:46:12.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很害羞嗎?
Dialogue: 0,1:46:12.99,1:46:15.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是舒服吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:46:15.69,1:46:17.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也很舒服的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:46:51.73,1:46:53.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:46:58.94,1:47:00.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了去了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:13.65,1:47:16.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的好厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,1:47:17.25,1:47:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是太棒了呢\N屁穴裏面一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:47:20.56,1:47:22.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又高潮嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:47:22.06,1:47:22.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行\N又高潮嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:47:22.66,1:47:23.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行
Dialogue: 0,1:47:23.26,1:47:27.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行？就是在你最敏感的時候\N才是最舒服的吧？\N不行不行不行
Dialogue: 0,1:47:40.08,1:47:42.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再給你做更多舒服的事情
Dialogue: 0,1:47:51.49,1:47:53.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金硬得好誇張
Dialogue: 0,1:48:07.10,1:48:09.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好帶感
Dialogue: 0,1:48:15.21,1:48:17.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:48:21.22,1:48:23.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭\N想要我幫你弄乳頭嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:48:29.63,1:48:31.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣做很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:48:34.43,1:48:36.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,1:48:37.73,1:48:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再讓我看看你更多舒服的表情
Dialogue: 0,1:48:41.94,1:48:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要變的奇怪了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:48:43.44,1:48:45.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓你變得更奇怪的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:49:01.16,1:49:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊不行 好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:49:06.26,1:49:09.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 太爽了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:10.77,1:49:12.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 去了去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:20.68,1:49:22.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行太爽了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:49:28.79,1:49:30.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:49:35.39,1:49:37.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要玩這個嗎?\N想玩
Dialogue: 0,1:49:38.09,1:49:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就給你放進去了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:49:44.70,1:49:45.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想要的吧？
Dialogue: 0,1:49:48.61,1:49:51.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒\N放進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:49:59.12,1:50:00.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服對吧
Dialogue: 0,1:50:00.92,1:50:01.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害漸漸吸進去了很舒服對吧
Dialogue: 0,1:50:01.22,1:50:03.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害漸漸吸進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:07.22,1:50:09.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的很厲害呢\N進到我的深處了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:09.93,1:50:12.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏進去了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:50:14.13,1:50:15.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:50:26.74,1:50:27.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉穴舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:50:27.64,1:50:29.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,緊緊的夾著我的肉棒\N是嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:50:31.25,1:50:34.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為你的肉棒硬邦邦的\N害得肉穴都變得緊了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:42.96,1:50:43.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好想要\N想要嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:50:45.36,1:50:47.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉穴和屁穴裏面兩邊一起\N很舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:50:56.77,1:50:57.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了\N不行?
Dialogue: 0,1:50:58.58,1:50:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭的快威和屁股上連在一起的
Dialogue: 0,1:51:00.08,1:51:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連接在一起的呢
Dialogue: 0,1:51:01.58,1:51:02.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全身都會很舒服呢\N連接在一起的呢
Dialogue: 0,1:51:02.18,1:51:03.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歐金金也連在一起的話\N全身都會很舒服呢
Dialogue: 0,1:51:05.18,1:51:06.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點變得越來越好舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:51:08.79,1:51:10.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:51:18.39,1:51:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好爽 好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:51:21.40,1:51:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了\N我也要一起去了
Dialogue: 0,1:51:24.40,1:51:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了去了
Dialogue: 0,1:51:29.21,1:51:32.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來了來了\N一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:51:33.11,1:51:34.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一庫一庫一庫
Dialogue: 0,1:51:45.42,1:51:47.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 歐金金好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:51:49.33,1:51:51.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在肉穴裏面攪來攪去的
Dialogue: 0,1:51:53.83,1:51:55.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服好舒服\N繼續舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:51:56.53,1:51:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也玩得好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:52:03.14,1:52:06.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:52:12.45,1:52:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了\N一庫一庫一庫一庫
Dialogue: 0,1:52:19.36,1:52:21.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行要出來了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:25.36,1:52:27.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了 我不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:52:29.57,1:52:31.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:52:40.68,1:52:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了高潮了高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:53:00.50,1:53:01.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要變得奇怪起來了
Dialogue: 0,1:53:09.51,1:53:11.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉穴一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,1:53:12.51,1:53:14.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來我這
Dialogue: 0,1:53:18.51,1:53:20.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 這裏還這麼濕
Dialogue: 0,1:53:22.12,1:53:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給你做更多更多舒服的事情呢
Dialogue: 0,1:53:25.72,1:53:26.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在濕成這樣
Dialogue: 0,1:53:28.73,1:53:30.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又要把手指插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:53:39.24,1:53:41.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 手指被吸進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:53:44.94,1:53:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:53:50.05,1:53:51.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的肉穴好想要肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:54:11.37,1:54:13.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:54:14.67,1:54:16.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個姿勢很厲害吧?
Dialogue: 0,1:54:23.98,1:54:25.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒很厲害的插了進來
Dialogue: 0,1:54:28.48,1:54:30.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的肉棒好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:54:31.49,1:54:33.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變得越來越舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:54:35.69,1:54:36.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:54:37.79,1:54:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏也好緊
Dialogue: 0,1:54:45.30,1:54:47.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:54:47.10,1:54:48.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要來了 要去了\N來了?去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:54:50.11,1:54:51.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:54:51.31,1:54:51.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打我 打我\N去吧 去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:54:51.91,1:54:52.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打我 打我
Dialogue: 0,1:54:52.81,1:54:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了去了
Dialogue: 0,1:54:57.01,1:54:58.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:55:12.33,1:55:15.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能停下來啊
Dialogue: 0,1:55:26.14,1:55:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:55:30.05,1:55:31.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情我還是第一次
Dialogue: 0,1:55:32.75,1:55:33.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:55:34.25,1:55:36.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:55:40.86,1:55:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了那麼多次
Dialogue: 0,1:55:43.56,1:55:45.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想射精的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:55:48.06,1:55:49.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經不知道了
Dialogue: 0,1:55:49.57,1:55:50.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道歐金金的感覺了嗎\N我已經不知道了
Dialogue: 0,1:55:50.17,1:55:51.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道歐金金的感覺了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:56:00.98,1:56:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在射精的話\N會變成什麼樣子呢
Dialogue: 0,1:56:06.98,1:56:07.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好怕
Dialogue: 0,1:56:07.88,1:56:08.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怕?
Dialogue: 0,1:56:09.69,1:56:11.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可怕嗎？但是我可是很期待的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:56:31.01,1:56:33.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想全部射出來的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:56:33.71,1:56:35.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:56:36.41,1:56:38.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒已經硬邦邦的了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:56:52.03,1:56:54.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:57:00.14,1:57:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:57:11.55,1:57:13.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎?
Dialogue: 0,1:57:16.65,1:57:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒硬邦邦的
Dialogue: 0,1:57:19.06,1:57:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下插到我的深處
Dialogue: 0,1:57:22.36,1:57:23.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經插到底了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:57:25.96,1:57:28.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插進去了嗎 好舒服\N舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:57:34.97,1:57:37.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會讓你爽上天的
Dialogue: 0,1:57:37.97,1:57:39.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會讓你全部射出來的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:57:50.89,1:57:52.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是第一次玩得這麼爽
Dialogue: 0,1:58:05.30,1:58:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:58:12.81,1:58:13.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:58:16.41,1:58:16.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,1:58:21.22,1:58:23.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:58:25.72,1:58:26.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:58:26.92,1:58:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以去嗎\N我又要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:58:27.52,1:58:29.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以去嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:58:29.33,1:58:32.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 去了去了去了
Dialogue: 0,1:58:34.43,1:58:36.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一庫一庫
Dialogue: 0,1:58:41.34,1:58:42.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行
Dialogue: 0,1:58:53.05,1:58:55.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股也要把手指插進去呢
Dialogue: 0,1:59:13.17,1:59:14.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:59:17.67,1:59:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光是動動手指 肉棒就變得好硬啊
Dialogue: 0,1:59:24.88,1:59:25.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:59:26.38,1:59:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了?
Dialogue: 0,1:59:33.59,1:59:35.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要去了\N要去了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,1:59:35.69,1:59:37.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很想射出來吧?\N想射出來
Dialogue: 0,1:59:41.10,1:59:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想射出來?
Dialogue: 0,2:00:05.12,2:00:06.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:00:29.15,2:00:30.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來親嘴
Dialogue: 0,2:00:38.76,2:00:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做得很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:00:44.46,2:00:46.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒已經硬邦邦的了
Dialogue: 0,2:00:47.46,2:00:49.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部都很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:00:51.07,2:00:54.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁穴裏面收得非常的緊哦
Dialogue: 0,2:00:54.67,2:00:56.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又變得好緊 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:01:12.39,2:01:14.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在幫我多吸吸
Dialogue: 0,2:01:18.39,2:01:19.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣嗎\N好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,2:01:19.60,2:01:21.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣做很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:01:21.70,2:01:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:01:22.90,2:01:25.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:01:25.60,2:01:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:01:31.31,2:01:33.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:01:34.31,2:01:36.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在變得更舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,2:01:37.61,2:01:39.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,2:01:40.62,2:01:42.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:02:00.74,2:02:01.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要來了?
Dialogue: 0,2:02:03.44,2:02:04.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股在激烈點
Dialogue: 0,2:02:04.94,2:02:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要激烈點?\N可以再激烈點嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:02:07.64,2:02:09.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看你看 又全部插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,2:02:12.15,2:02:13.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣很舒服嗎\N對對對就是那裏
Dialogue: 0,2:02:13.95,2:02:16.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裏很舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:02:16.95,2:02:17.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了\N要去了?
Dialogue: 0,2:02:18.15,2:02:20.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點射吧\N屁穴和肉棒都已經在抽搐了
Dialogue: 0,2:02:35.27,2:02:36.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:02:37.07,2:02:39.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一抖一抖一抖的呢
Dialogue: 0,2:02:49.39,2:02:52.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:02:52.09,2:02:52.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行了\N好厲害 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:02:52.39,2:02:52.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行了
Dialogue: 0,2:02:52.99,2:02:54.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行了\N不行不行不行了
Dialogue: 0,2:02:54.19,2:02:54.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了嗎\N不行不行不行了
Dialogue: 0,2:02:54.79,2:02:56.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射出來射出來
Dialogue: 0,2:03:02.90,2:03:05.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:03:08.00,2:03:09.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:03:12.81,2:03:14.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一抖一抖的
Dialogue: 0,2:03:14.91,2:03:17.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屈穴裏面好緊啊
Dialogue: 0,2:03:35.93,2:03:37.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然射出來這麼多
Dialogue: 0,2:03:40.14,2:03:42.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:03:55.15,2:03:56.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是太棒了
Dialogue: 0,2:04:03.56,2:04:05.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我還是第一次做這種事情
Dialogue: 0,2:04:21.28,2:04:24.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個可能會上癮啊！

