[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(禁止發聲東縛內射強轟)\n(有阪深雪主演)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.91,0:00:19.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(3:57分私立學校)\n(玉井北校走廊下)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.44,0:01:20.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天在拍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.18,0:01:22.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.85,0:01:26.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷拍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.98,0:01:33.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-沒有的 只是玩手機\n-為什麼這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.22,0:01:38.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是玩玩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.19,0:01:40.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用在這裡弄吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.77,0:01:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要報告老師
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.44,0:01:51.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-別這樣做\n-別過來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.94,0:01:54.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜歡這樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.05,0:02:10.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(時間3:59)\n(私立玉井學園北校)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.56,0:02:13.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別叫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.70,0:02:18.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是看看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.60,0:02:20.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.32,0:02:26.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別發聲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.39,0:02:29.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.83,0:02:34.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.34,0:02:37.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小聲點
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.97,0:02:41.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發出聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.44,0:02:44.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就會暴露的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.15,0:02:55.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我看看 手舉起來別動哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.87,0:03:08.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別動
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.71,0:03:16.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 好美的身體啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.72,0:03:36.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能住手的 是你不好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.83,0:03:42.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿的這麼色情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.14,0:03:48.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能怪你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.72,0:04:02.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這樣被看到很不好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.79,0:04:07.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都看到你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.01,0:04:48.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴濕了嗎 很敏感吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.19,0:04:58.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.40,0:05:00.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真色
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.85,0:05:21.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.39,0:05:30.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.78,0:05:52.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.22,0:06:05.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜歡被這樣弄吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.64,0:06:20.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要繼續摸哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.25,0:06:30.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什麼內褲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.49,0:08:24.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別動啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.80,0:10:16.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.21,0:10:24.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要叫哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.88,0:10:30.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.77,0:11:46.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都看到了呢 好色呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.79,0:12:31.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.02,0:19:22.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.61,0:19:27.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下來腿
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.33,0:21:37.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.90,0:22:19.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.70,0:22:59.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.47,0:23:04.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.91,0:23:22.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.48,0:23:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.25,0:23:30.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我也喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.26,0:23:37.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以考慮下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.80,0:24:11.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.62,0:24:46.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-對不起我先走了\n-等我下
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.29,0:25:01.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想去呢 這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.56,0:25:04.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.37,0:25:10.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桃子的?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.44,0:25:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(私立下井學院北準備室)\N(PM4:31)
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.59,0:25:33.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老實點
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.86,0:25:37.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要叫
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.93,0:25:40.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會滿足你的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.97,0:25:48.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想發出聲音也可以\n不怕暴露的話
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.06,0:26:11.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.45,0:26:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別動哦
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.57,0:27:08.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.29,0:27:24.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺怎麼樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.75,0:27:58.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舌頭伸出來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.53,0:29:16.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.18,0:30:04.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.54,0:30:32.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡這樣的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.22,0:30:39.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.83,0:31:20.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶頭硬了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.90,0:31:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.84,0:31:58.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.31,0:32:17.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡敏感嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.57,0:33:29.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.34,0:33:37.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真色啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.27,0:34:38.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真變態啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.61,0:34:49.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼噴水了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.57,0:35:14.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.91,0:35:48.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,潮噴了呢 怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.58,0:36:39.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕透了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.96,0:36:50.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要看我
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.22,0:37:40.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.90,0:37:58.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.57,0:38:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.14,0:38:43.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.17,0:38:46.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.39,0:38:59.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.87,0:39:11.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.62,0:39:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.93,0:39:36.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.46,0:40:16.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.63,0:40:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.78,0:40:48.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.73,0:41:17.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要肉棒了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.14,0:41:20.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很臭的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.03,0:41:26.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是汗味的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.02,0:41:41.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點張嘴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.56,0:41:52.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點舔我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.25,0:42:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.39,0:42:33.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續吸我
Dialogue: 0,0:43:09.02,0:43:12.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要停下
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.96,0:43:34.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.32,0:44:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-插入吧 -不行啊 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.50,0:44:28.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.75,0:44:36.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.01,0:45:34.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要高潮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.75,0:45:41.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:45:53.39,0:45:59.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行 高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.13,0:46:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:27.92,0:46:29.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.85,0:47:51.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.50,0:48:09.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常喜歡這樣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:32.23,0:48:36.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.46,0:49:08.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行 高潮了啊 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:08.46,0:50:12.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:20.97,0:50:23.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.88,0:50:28.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:33.18,0:50:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股翹起來吧 舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:14.73,0:51:18.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好過來這邊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:32.66,0:52:38.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:19.29,0:54:25.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:33.36,0:54:36.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:41.18,0:55:43.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:55:43.33,0:55:47.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不行 -要射了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:55:52.17,0:55:54.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:11.61,0:57:17.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(私立玉井北校保健室)\N(PM1:26)
Dialogue: 0,0:57:21.99,0:57:27.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-幹嘛 -別問了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:30.56,0:57:33.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事情嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:57:33.90,0:57:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:57:37.27,0:57:41.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說我在吸煙了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:42.49,0:57:44.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你不好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:46.77,0:57:54.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-管你什麼事情\n-你自作自受
Dialogue: 0,0:57:54.72,0:57:59.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要去上課了\n-等一下 別走
Dialogue: 0,0:58:02.96,0:58:06.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-住手 -別動
Dialogue: 0,0:58:06.30,0:58:09.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老寶點
Dialogue: 0,0:58:15.18,0:58:17.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:18.21,0:58:25.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-誰讓你多管間事\n-你幹嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:58:26.79,0:58:31.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這是什麼 -安靜點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:58:44.81,0:58:49.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別得意忘形了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:05.56,0:59:08.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別發聲
Dialogue: 0,0:59:28.78,0:59:34.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡沒有其他老師來了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:37.94,0:59:41.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上課真無聊
Dialogue: 0,0:59:44.99,0:59:47.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小聲點
Dialogue: 0,0:59:47.73,0:59:52.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴露了對你不好的
Dialogue: 0,0:59:52.63,0:59:57.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年也可以順利了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:05.15,1:00:11.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-住手 -都硬了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:00:29.58,1:00:34.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶頭都硬了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:01:38.31,1:01:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:44.74,1:01:47.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎麼樣 -不行啊
Dialogue: 0,1:01:48.08,1:01:50.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要忍耐
Dialogue: 0,1:01:53.89,1:01:58.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:58.79,1:02:04.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:21.68,1:02:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:02:51.62,1:02:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這裡嗎 -不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:03:35.91,1:03:38.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:42.62,1:03:45.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:51.19,1:03:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了幾次啊
Dialogue: 0,1:04:15.32,1:04:21.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要插入啊 -安靜點
Dialogue: 0,1:04:24.17,1:04:27.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺到了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:04:34.54,1:04:37.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:04:37.31,1:04:43.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行 不行啊
Dialogue: 0,1:05:00.20,1:05:05.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了 高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:05:18.82,1:05:21.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:01.60,1:06:07.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-舒服吧 -不要啊住手
Dialogue: 0,1:06:10.74,1:06:14.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-舒服吧 -住手
Dialogue: 0,1:06:26.32,1:06:32.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小聲點 好厲害的小穴呢
Dialogue: 0,1:06:40.07,1:06:43.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:52.88,1:06:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:57.79,1:07:03.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要這樣 不行
Dialogue: 0,1:07:08.46,1:07:12.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:28.62,1:07:35.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼噴水了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:35.36,1:07:42.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼多水 真變態啊
Dialogue: 0,1:09:27.13,1:09:28.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別發聲
Dialogue: 0,1:11:38.79,1:11:45.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在可以發出聲音了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:06.28,1:12:10.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:10.55,1:12:11.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:27.67,1:12:29.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:12:48.12,1:12:53.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(私立玉井學院)\N(PM2:47)
Dialogue: 0,1:12:53.30,1:12:58.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以老師沒有意識到
Dialogue: 0,1:12:58.80,1:13:04.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-需要在研修下\n-不知道呢
Dialogue: 0,1:13:05.54,1:13:09.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師也很辛苦的
Dialogue: 0,1:13:09.81,1:13:13.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的沒什麼時間呢
Dialogue: 0,1:13:14.39,1:13:19.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說的也有道理的
Dialogue: 0,1:13:19.60,1:13:26.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-會告訴部長的 -是嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:13:26.32,1:13:30.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩有時間嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:13:31.19,1:13:35.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,1:13:35.80,1:13:37.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個
Dialogue: 0,1:13:37.63,1:13:43.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 我們會調查的
Dialogue: 0,1:13:43.41,1:13:50.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 你不知道
Dialogue: 0,1:13:50.15,1:13:53.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行吧 不和你們說了
Dialogue: 0,1:13:53.48,1:13:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去校長那裡問問
Dialogue: 0,1:14:00.52,1:14:05.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下等下 怎麼回事啊
Dialogue: 0,1:14:05.40,1:14:09.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這是什麼態度
Dialogue: 0,1:14:10.00,1:14:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,1:14:17.94,1:14:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也是老師的
Dialogue: 0,1:14:23.43,1:14:31.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎 你是學生\n我們教你知識的
Dialogue: 0,1:14:33.51,1:14:36.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:14:36.28,1:14:41.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 最近的學生
Dialogue: 0,1:14:42.08,1:14:45.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要懲罰一下你呢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:49.72,1:14:54.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 你覺得呢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:56.75,1:14:59.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你老實點
Dialogue: 0,1:14:59.82,1:15:04.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘記最近是誰了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:15:19.99,1:15:26.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也忍耐很久了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:15:32.50,1:15:34.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,1:15:49.29,1:15:52.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體這麼敏感
Dialogue: 0,1:15:52.96,1:15:57.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也想要吧
Dialogue: 0,1:16:06.41,1:16:09.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別發聲哦
Dialogue: 0,1:16:51.94,1:16:53.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:17:23.39,1:17:28.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不聽我們的話
Dialogue: 0,1:17:28.90,1:17:34.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就沒有未來了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:12.46,1:19:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:33.52,1:19:38.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經興奮了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:20:43.46,1:20:48.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,1:21:35.40,1:21:40.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多水啊
Dialogue: 0,1:21:40.91,1:21:45.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子
Dialogue: 0,1:22:14.81,1:22:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:57.25,1:22:59.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噴了這麼多水
Dialogue: 0,1:23:09.47,1:23:13.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:23:15.87,1:23:19.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:24:42.96,1:24:49.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好吃吧
Dialogue: 0,1:25:09.22,1:25:12.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊還有
Dialogue: 0,1:25:41.91,1:25:46.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好吃吧
Dialogue: 0,1:28:04.87,1:28:09.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我看看裡面
Dialogue: 0,1:28:34.17,1:28:39.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣 能長點記性了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:28:59.83,1:29:05.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(私立玉井學院體育館更衣室)\N(PM5:04)
Dialogue: 0,1:29:23.95,1:29:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人在這裡做什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:29:30.06,1:29:34.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:29:34.33,1:29:38.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陪陪我們怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,1:29:43.51,1:29:47.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們不要這樣子
Dialogue: 0,1:29:47.78,1:29:52.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說話
Dialogue: 0,1:30:57.13,1:31:02.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真下流啊
Dialogue: 0,1:31:30.09,1:31:34.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶子真好看
Dialogue: 0,1:32:00.96,1:32:06.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接摸更加舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:32:28.42,1:32:29.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,1:32:52.57,1:32:57.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,1:33:09.69,1:33:16.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:33:16.39,1:33:22.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣非常舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:33:49.69,1:33:53.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:33:53.37,1:33:59.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 不要脫
Dialogue: 0,1:34:03.14,1:34:05.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腿張開給我看看
Dialogue: 0,1:34:09.25,1:34:13.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡摩擦吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:24.50,1:34:27.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:32.14,1:34:36.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧 感覺怎麼樣啊
Dialogue: 0,1:34:41.31,1:34:47.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-高潮了 高潮了\n-舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:35:32.62,1:35:39.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕糟糕 好多水呢 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:35:52.47,1:35:55.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想插入試試呢
Dialogue: 0,1:35:55.84,1:35:58.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎廖樣啊
Dialogue: 0,1:35:58.58,1:36:00.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑道吧
Dialogue: 0,1:36:02.85,1:36:06.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好喝
Dialogue: 0,1:36:11.72,1:36:19.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還在流呢 好厲害啊\n停不下來呢
Dialogue: 0,1:36:26.39,1:36:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還在流呢
Dialogue: 0,1:36:35.26,1:36:38.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕透了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:36:38.90,1:36:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害呢 真色啊
Dialogue: 0,1:36:48.97,1:36:51.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多水呢
Dialogue: 0,1:36:51.44,1:36:58.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真色啊 這裡很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:37:01.52,1:37:04.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看這裡啊
Dialogue: 0,1:37:12.81,1:37:15.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可愛呢
Dialogue: 0,1:37:23.82,1:37:27.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要高潮了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:37:27.50,1:37:31.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常舒服吧 好厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,1:37:47.35,1:37:51.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趴下來吧 趴下來
Dialogue: 0,1:37:52.24,1:37:56.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看這邊
Dialogue: 0,1:38:08.44,1:38:14.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡好色呢
Dialogue: 0,1:38:15.16,1:38:17.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽到了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:38:17.63,1:38:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓他們也參加嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:38:23.10,1:38:27.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別發聲哦
Dialogue: 0,1:39:08.91,1:39:11.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來次吧
Dialogue: 0,1:39:12.28,1:39:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫你吧
Dialogue: 0,1:39:24.49,1:39:28.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:40:00.25,1:40:03.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多肉棒呢
Dialogue: 0,1:40:08.19,1:40:11.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:40:19.47,1:40:24.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深入點
Dialogue: 0,1:40:31.08,1:40:37.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊還有呢
Dialogue: 0,1:40:37.19,1:40:40.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,1:40:40.26,1:40:45.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看這裡
Dialogue: 0,1:40:52.14,1:40:55.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手也動起來
Dialogue: 0,1:41:26.94,1:41:30.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深入點
Dialogue: 0,1:41:32.75,1:41:39.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以停下的 繼續吧
Dialogue: 0,1:41:43.10,1:41:46.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不 -沒關係的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:41:52.28,1:41:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別發聲哦
Dialogue: 0,1:41:57.15,1:42:03.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插入了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:42:14.87,1:42:19.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常喜歡這樣吧
Dialogue: 0,1:42:24.65,1:42:29.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多水呢
Dialogue: 0,1:42:29.22,1:42:36.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真騷呢 舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:42:36.52,1:42:43.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜歡吧 有感覺了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:42:50.57,1:42:53.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:42:58.51,1:43:02.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:43:03.72,1:43:07.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,1:43:19.29,1:43:24.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:43:24.20,1:43:26.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,1:43:27.23,1:43:31.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小聲點哦
Dialogue: 0,1:43:55.03,1:43:58.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:44:10.01,1:44:13.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股動起來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:44:27.36,1:44:33.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行啊 高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:44:56.09,1:44:59.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:45:04.30,1:45:08.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:15.58,1:45:19.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊 這邊 這邊
Dialogue: 0,1:45:47.04,1:45:50.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:56.79,1:46:01.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不行不行 -繼續哦
Dialogue: 0,1:46:01.99,1:46:04.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,1:46:04.73,1:46:10.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:46:11.44,1:46:14.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:46:31.92,1:46:37.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣 非常舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:46:49.58,1:46:54.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不可以啊
Dialogue: 0,1:47:00.59,1:47:03.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:47:08.83,1:47:12.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服 受不了了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:15.54,1:47:19.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:47:46.97,1:47:50.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真下流啊
Dialogue: 0,1:47:54.31,1:47:57.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:47:57.98,1:48:04.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-糟糕 太舒服了呢\n-不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:48:16.30,1:48:22.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直很敏感呢 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:48:41.33,1:48:46.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得好熱啊
Dialogue: 0,1:48:46.54,1:48:49.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:48:52.64,1:48:54.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕啊
Dialogue: 0,1:48:56.91,1:49:03.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要射了 受不了了\n-射我啊
Dialogue: 0,1:49:03.32,1:49:08.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了 射了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:49:12.76,1:49:18.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安靜點吧 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:49:32.92,1:49:37.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了好多呢 精子
Dialogue: 0,1:49:38.12,1:49:45.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股翹起來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:49:57.04,1:50:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了太多吧 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:50:09.52,1:50:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真緊啊
Dialogue: 0,1:50:14.72,1:50:20.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看這裡
Dialogue: 0,1:50:22.37,1:50:29.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要發出聲音呢 -不行
Dialogue: 0,1:50:31.51,1:50:35.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常舒服呢
Dialogue: 0,1:50:36.71,1:50:41.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-高潮了 高潮了 -可以
Dialogue: 0,1:50:46.79,1:50:53.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受不了了 要射了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:50:55.00,1:50:58.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害哦 舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:51:02.65,1:51:06.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常緊呢
Dialogue: 0,1:51:15.47,1:51:17.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:51:25.86,1:51:28.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:51:42.34,1:51:45.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:51:54.25,1:51:58.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:52:01.86,1:52:05.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了好多呢
Dialogue: 0,1:52:06.16,1:52:12.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎 繼續躺下來做吧
Dialogue: 0,1:52:17.74,1:52:21.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓他們也參加吧?
Dialogue: 0,1:52:24.20,1:52:26.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:52:27.83,1:52:32.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多水啊 這裡
Dialogue: 0,1:52:44.37,1:52:46.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,1:53:09.12,1:53:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真色啊
Dialogue: 0,1:53:27.40,1:53:29.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕啊
Dialogue: 0,1:53:31.07,1:53:35.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:53:39.61,1:53:46.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕啊 要高潮了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:53:47.55,1:53:50.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:53:57.33,1:54:03.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好緊啊 對不起 很舒服呵
Dialogue: 0,1:54:15.06,1:54:18.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真騷啊
Dialogue: 0,1:54:18.73,1:54:24.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,1:54:24.84,1:54:30.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起來 給我們看看
Dialogue: 0,1:54:30.94,1:54:35.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡舔乾淨吧
Dialogue: 0,1:54:48.36,1:54:52.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:55:04.54,1:55:08.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:55:30.80,1:55:35.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 看這邊
Dialogue: 0,1:55:43.32,1:55:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:55:45.45,1:55:47.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舌頭伸出來
Dialogue: 0,1:55:52.16,1:55:56.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:55:56.46,1:56:02.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受不了了 要射了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:56:08.98,1:56:11.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,1:56:12.01,1:56:18.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服啊 太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:56:31.86,1:56:35.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,1:56:41.34,1:56:45.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真舒服啊 謝謝

