[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,MS Sans Serif,8,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,15,0

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.57,0:00:05.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(MOODYZ出品)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.22,0:00:32.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(茱莉亞)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.67,0:01:27.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(茱莉亞J杯)\N(超極品陪浴女)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.82,0:01:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(馬上口交與馬上上床)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.22,0:01:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎光臨 我是茱莉亞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.42,0:01:43.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎光臨 我是茱莉亞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.67,0:01:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天請多指教 這邊請
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.27,0:01:54.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請進
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.12,0:02:00.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外套脫給我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.62,0:02:18.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我給你脫衣服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.42,0:02:36.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-第一次來這種地方嗎\N-是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.62,0:02:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼今天和茱莉亞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.72,0:02:43.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.57,0:02:51.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓忍耐已久的都出來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.22,0:02:53.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.82,0:03:10.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面也脫哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.07,0:03:35.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以親你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.17,0:04:27.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-讓你這裡也舒服哦  -好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.62,0:05:20.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉樓也這麼硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.22,0:05:36.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.97,0:06:01.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡可以摸嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.47,0:06:25.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你脫了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.77,0:06:49.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.42,0:06:55.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼大了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.32,0:07:04.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍著的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.77,0:07:25.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好硬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.97,0:07:28.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好硬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.37,0:07:33.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形狀也很好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.57,0:07:39.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.22,0:07:58.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以舔嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.07,0:08:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事 不洗也不髒的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.07,0:08:37.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好美味
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.32,0:08:55.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.47,0:09:14.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要含住了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.22,0:09:51.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.12,0:10:01.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也可以舔嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.77,0:10:29.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睪丸舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.77,0:11:32.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想摸嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.07,0:11:34.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.87,0:11:37.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.52,0:12:11.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.82,0:12:33.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也舒服起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.82,0:12:36.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.67,0:12:48.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用這個讓你舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.22,0:13:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這樣如何  -好舒服\N-舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.97,0:13:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快一點的話呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.47,0:13:56.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒越來越硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.87,0:14:13.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.12,0:14:40.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.77,0:14:52.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了的話 可以射哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.17,0:15:04.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.87,0:15:10.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想這樣射嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.02,0:15:52.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熟練
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.37,0:16:10.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可以舔嗎  -舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.07,0:16:30.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很會舔哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.77,0:17:11.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸我這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.57,0:18:38.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好會摸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.17,0:19:07.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我裡面也舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.77,0:19:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這裡嗎  -好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.37,0:19:56.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何 用兩根手指讓我舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.37,0:19:58.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.07,0:20:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.22,0:21:49.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了 有什麼出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.77,0:21:53.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕濕的了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.42,0:21:53.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕濕的了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.37,0:23:17.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插入吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.62,0:23:23.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.92,0:24:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.52,0:25:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.02,0:26:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.17,0:26:32.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來動
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.12,0:27:37.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得見插入的地方嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.02,0:27:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.57,0:28:00.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.02,0:28:07.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滑出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.47,0:29:14.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.32,0:29:19.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-從後面插入吧 看  -好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.62,0:29:53.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.67,0:29:57.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.92,0:30:06.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.22,0:30:08.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.82,0:30:18.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熟練
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.32,0:31:24.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣轉過去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.02,0:31:57.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面好大
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.97,0:31:59.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面好大
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.72,0:32:00.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面好大
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.77,0:33:35.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.27,0:33:39.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.27,0:35:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.52,0:36:01.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躺下來 繼續吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.12,0:37:40.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好舒服  -這裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.72,0:39:51.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.07,0:40:22.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了 要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.82,0:40:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了 要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.87,0:40:44.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我給你弄乾淨
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.42,0:41:22.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了好多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.72,0:41:27.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 才剛開始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.72,0:41:42.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.62,0:41:45.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 給你洗泡泡浴\N(椅上洗浴)
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.62,0:41:53.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要開始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.87,0:42:02.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多泡泡很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.52,0:42:11.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也是
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.92,0:42:20.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從上半身開始哦
Dialogue: 0,0:42:26.27,0:42:28.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從手開始
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.87,0:42:31.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用胸部給你洗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.62,0:42:48.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-舒服嗎  -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.47,0:42:49.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.07,0:42:52.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很光滑很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.97,0:42:54.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很光滑很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.17,0:42:55.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很光滑很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.82,0:43:07.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後用胸部給你洗
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.67,0:43:15.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後是手腕
Dialogue: 0,0:44:01.07,0:44:04.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-胸部洗得舒服嗎\N-是的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.57,0:44:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-軟嗎  -好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.37,0:44:11.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.42,0:44:11.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.57,0:44:17.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-接下來是身體  -好
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.22,0:44:42.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭和乳頭在摩擦哦
Dialogue: 0,0:44:53.57,0:44:54.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.07,0:45:00.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好舒服  -舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.57,0:45:10.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來是肚子
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.07,0:45:38.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 這邊哦
Dialogue: 0,0:45:51.62,0:45:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-手舉起來  -這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:46:06.47,0:46:07.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抬起來
Dialogue: 0,0:46:38.42,0:46:42.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 用其他地方冼
Dialogue: 0,0:46:48.02,0:46:49.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-稍等  -好
Dialogue: 0,0:47:08.42,0:47:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不痛吧  -好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:47:36.62,0:47:40.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何 被胸部和下面洗
Dialogue: 0,0:47:43.67,0:47:46.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-奇怪的感覺嗎  -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:47:55.37,0:47:59.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 另一邊哦
Dialogue: 0,0:48:34.67,0:48:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一雙手也伸過來
Dialogue: 0,0:48:43.52,0:48:45.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你洗兩隻手
Dialogue: 0,0:49:08.12,0:49:12.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-屁股的感覺不一樣了嗎\N-是的
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.47,0:49:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這個也好舒服\N-這個也舒服嗎 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:36.47,0:49:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.62,0:50:44.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛洗了上半身\N接下來是下半身
Dialogue: 0,0:51:10.22,0:51:13.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續用胸部洗
Dialogue: 0,0:51:30.47,0:51:34.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-大腿感覺不一樣嗎\N-是的
Dialogue: 0,0:52:18.62,0:52:21.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夾住腿了
Dialogue: 0,0:52:24.77,0:52:27.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-沒有這樣過  -真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:52:28.67,0:52:30.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那這是初體驗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.77,0:53:08.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:46.37,0:53:49.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 洗兩隻腳
Dialogue: 0,0:53:49.37,0:53:51.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心摔倒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:54:02.27,0:54:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,癢嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.47,0:54:28.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼接下來
Dialogue: 0,0:54:33.02,0:54:34.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊來
Dialogue: 0,0:54:47.87,0:54:50.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡不癢嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:55:27.32,0:55:32.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這樣摩擦很舒服  -真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:55:53.42,0:55:56.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腿頂著這裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:58.82,0:55:59.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點反應哦
Dialogue: 0,0:56:24.17,0:56:27.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 洗背後
Dialogue: 0,0:57:03.63,0:57:05.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:17.28,0:57:23.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-先清洗一下吧  -好
Dialogue: 0,0:57:36.33,0:57:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有還很濕的地方了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:40.98,0:57:46.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 我用嘴把肉棒弄乾淨
Dialogue: 0,0:58:14.88,0:58:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經這麼硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:33.63,0:58:35.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睪丸也舔哦
Dialogue: 0,0:58:45.93,0:58:50.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 用這個姿勢繼續舔哦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:21.18,0:59:22.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡也是
Dialogue: 0,0:59:30.18,0:59:31.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不癢嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:00:27.18,1:00:30.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-睪丸也舒服嗎  -是的
Dialogue: 0,1:01:35.58,1:01:36.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比剛剛硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:38.88,1:01:40.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:02:25.38,1:02:28.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好硬  -好屬害\N-看
Dialogue: 0,1:02:34.83,1:02:34.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一點點出來了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:13.68,1:03:18.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是用嘴舒服還是胸部舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:03:58.38,1:03:59.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣呢
Dialogue: 0,1:04:02.58,1:04:03.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好屬害
Dialogue: 0,1:04:04.53,1:04:05.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頂著胸部了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:17.73,1:04:19.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好舒服  -舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:04:33.93,1:04:34.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:04:47.58,1:04:48.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三明治
Dialogue: 0,1:05:31.68,1:05:35.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道說 又要射了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:05:36.18,1:05:36.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,1:05:39.03,1:05:41.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好啊 射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:08.13,1:06:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要射了  -要射了嗎 好
Dialogue: 0,1:06:12.03,1:06:14.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-射胸部上  -可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:06:16.23,1:06:18.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,1:06:22.08,1:06:23.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:06:34.38,1:06:37.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 射了好多
Dialogue: 0,1:06:42.93,1:06:45.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用嘴給你弄乾淨
Dialogue: 0,1:07:21.93,1:07:25.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好厲害 射了好多\N-好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:07:27.33,1:07:28.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好開心
Dialogue: 0,1:07:28.68,1:07:28.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好開心
Dialogue: 0,1:07:36.18,1:07:37.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泡澡舒服嗎\N(潛望鏡)
Dialogue: 0,1:08:03.03,1:08:05.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人 一直盯著呢
Dialogue: 0,1:08:07.83,1:08:09.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼想看嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:08:20.13,1:08:21.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說
Dialogue: 0,1:08:23.13,1:08:28.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一起洗澡開始\N還是看到胸部開始
Dialogue: 0,1:08:31.23,1:08:33.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒這麼硬了?
Dialogue: 0,1:08:35.73,1:08:36.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可愛
Dialogue: 0,1:08:40.08,1:08:41.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,1:08:42.33,1:08:45.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在浴池裡 繼續做舒服的事吧
Dialogue: 0,1:08:59.28,1:09:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒頂著了 不好動
Dialogue: 0,1:09:25.68,1:09:27.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是胸部還不夠嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:09:31.68,1:09:32.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我給你舔
Dialogue: 0,1:09:48.03,1:09:49.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顫抖得好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:09:57.93,1:10:00.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-舒服嗎  -好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:10:27.33,1:10:30.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒在顫抖呢
Dialogue: 0,1:13:39.18,1:13:40.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在摩擦哦
Dialogue: 0,1:14:27.48,1:14:29.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊的腿也想被摸呢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:40.98,1:14:42.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還想要嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:15:20.28,1:15:21.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在摩擦胸部
Dialogue: 0,1:15:36.03,1:15:41.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-胸部頂著舒服嗎  -好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:15:51.63,1:15:53.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部也在說很舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,1:16:03.03,1:16:06.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-如何 不冷吧  -沒事
Dialogue: 0,1:16:13.23,1:16:15.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來是這裡
Dialogue: 0,1:17:10.83,1:17:13.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近想被舔的地方了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:17:16.68,1:17:18.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是還不給你舔
Dialogue: 0,1:17:45.03,1:17:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代替舔
Dialogue: 0,1:17:49.23,1:17:51.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先享受下胸部吧
Dialogue: 0,1:18:27.03,1:18:29.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比剛剛硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:18:38.58,1:18:40.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想被舔了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:18:42.18,1:18:43.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法
Dialogue: 0,1:18:48.48,1:18:51.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看看
Dialogue: 0,1:20:06.63,1:20:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:11.88,1:20:13.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好硬
Dialogue: 0,1:20:26.88,1:20:28.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多想被含住了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:21:15.48,1:21:16.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好硬
Dialogue: 0,1:21:23.88,1:21:25.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來用胸部
Dialogue: 0,1:21:43.38,1:21:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-胸部舒服嗎  -好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:21:52.23,1:21:57.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個 還是這樣呢
Dialogue: 0,1:21:57.93,1:22:00.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好舒服  -這邊舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:22:04.53,1:22:06.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頂著乳頭了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:57.33,1:22:59.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在摩擦兩邊的胸部哦
Dialogue: 0,1:23:02.28,1:23:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在看嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:23:09.33,1:23:12.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:23:42.03,1:23:43.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-舒服嗎  -好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:23:56.28,1:23:59.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要射了  -要射了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:24:00.48,1:24:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:03.48,1:24:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是剛已經濕了很多了\N還能射嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:26:04.08,1:26:06.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要射了  -要射了嗎 好
Dialogue: 0,1:26:08.73,1:26:10.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了好多
Dialogue: 0,1:26:24.63,1:26:25.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,1:26:27.48,1:26:30.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才射了好多\N又射了好多
Dialogue: 0,1:26:33.33,1:26:34.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能射多少啊
Dialogue: 0,1:26:38.73,1:26:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射到胸部上了
Dialogue: 0,1:26:48.78,1:26:49.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡也是
Dialogue: 0,1:26:58.68,1:27:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你弄乾淨哦
Dialogue: 0,1:27:54.33,1:27:58.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乾淨了嗎 舒服了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:28:00.63,1:28:02.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 好開心
Dialogue: 0,1:28:09.18,1:28:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼接下來
Dialogue: 0,1:28:12.03,1:28:13.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在墊子上進行哦\N(墊上洗浴)
Dialogue: 0,1:28:14.43,1:28:19.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是用泡沫\N用潤滑油 會更舒服的
Dialogue: 0,1:28:19.53,1:28:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你洗哦
Dialogue: 0,1:28:29.88,1:28:31.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕濕的了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:28:51.03,1:28:55.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先 從背後開始洗
Dialogue: 0,1:29:06.18,1:29:08.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道胸部的感覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:29:19.98,1:29:20.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好光滑
Dialogue: 0,1:29:20.43,1:29:20.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好光滑
Dialogue: 0,1:29:21.18,1:29:21.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好光滑
Dialogue: 0,1:29:21.48,1:29:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好光滑
Dialogue: 0,1:29:22.08,1:29:22.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好光滑
Dialogue: 0,1:29:39.03,1:29:42.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用胸部在洗屁股哦
Dialogue: 0,1:29:49.83,1:29:51.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來
Dialogue: 0,1:29:52.83,1:29:54.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腋下呢
Dialogue: 0,1:30:09.63,1:30:11.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:31:11.43,1:31:11.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何
Dialogue: 0,1:31:14.88,1:31:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一邊也洗哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:02.73,1:32:04.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼接下來
Dialogue: 0,1:32:10.83,1:32:12.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗另一邊
Dialogue: 0,1:33:07.23,1:33:08.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次是
Dialogue: 0,1:33:11.88,1:33:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用潤滑油在洗哦
Dialogue: 0,1:33:15.78,1:33:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和泡沫比哪個舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:33:30.78,1:33:32.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腳也洗
Dialogue: 0,1:33:54.93,1:33:56.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不癢吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:05.73,1:34:08.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和泡沫不一樣吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:48.33,1:34:50.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腳也給你弄乾淨哦
Dialogue: 0,1:35:22.08,1:35:23.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也給你弄乾
Dialogue: 0,1:35:41.43,1:35:43.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腳不癢嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:36:15.63,1:36:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 面朝上躺著
Dialogue: 0,1:36:24.48,1:36:25.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你洗乾淨
Dialogue: 0,1:37:10.38,1:37:13.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續給你洗正面
Dialogue: 0,1:38:08.88,1:38:10.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡也有反應哦
Dialogue: 0,1:38:16.38,1:38:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,潤滑油讓你舒服嗎\N摸得舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:38:26.88,1:38:29.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,1:38:40.68,1:38:41.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,1:39:09.78,1:39:12.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:39:29.43,1:39:30.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你這裡也舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:39:46.53,1:39:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越硬了
Dialogue: 0,1:40:08.28,1:40:10.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕濕的潤滑油
Dialogue: 0,1:40:10.98,1:40:13.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是濕濕的舌頭讓你舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:40:27.18,1:40:28.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然這個更好嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:40:52.98,1:40:58.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上半身洗了以後\N該洗腳了
Dialogue: 0,1:41:50.43,1:41:52.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣如何
Dialogue: 0,1:42:05.88,1:42:06.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒摸肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:42:07.38,1:42:07.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒摸肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:42:12.03,1:42:13.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣摸
Dialogue: 0,1:43:02.88,1:43:04.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來
Dialogue: 0,1:43:11.28,1:43:12.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊
Dialogue: 0,1:43:53.13,1:43:56.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡如何 舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:44:30.18,1:44:30.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來
Dialogue: 0,1:44:33.78,1:44:36.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用嘴讓你舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:45:52.38,1:45:53.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣呢
Dialogue: 0,1:47:27.48,1:47:29.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越大了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:48.03,1:47:49.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:48:24.03,1:48:25.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也好舒服嗎？
Dialogue: 0,1:49:51.18,1:49:54.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多該插入了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:55.53,1:49:57.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以插入嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:50:01.38,1:50:03.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 看好插入的地方哦
Dialogue: 0,1:50:37.08,1:50:38.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:56.88,1:50:58.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:51:10.53,1:51:14.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 肉棒插在小穴裏
Dialogue: 0,1:51:15.63,1:51:20.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得清楚嗎 好好看看
Dialogue: 0,1:51:38.28,1:51:40.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插得好深
Dialogue: 0,1:52:45.33,1:52:48.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 看後入我
Dialogue: 0,1:53:10.83,1:53:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何 看得清嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:54:47.28,1:54:49.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插得好深
Dialogue: 0,1:54:51.48,1:54:51.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:54:51.78,1:54:52.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:54:52.23,1:54:52.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:54:52.68,1:54:52.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:54:56.28,1:54:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:54:57.78,1:54:58.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:55:55.83,1:55:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 後入我
Dialogue: 0,1:56:35.28,1:56:35.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:56:35.73,1:56:35.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:56:38.88,1:56:40.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:57:37.23,1:57:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:59:00.48,1:59:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:00:04.23,2:00:05.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,2:00:24.18,2:00:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了好多
Dialogue: 0,2:00:29.43,2:00:30.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我給你弄乾淨
Dialogue: 0,2:01:33.48,2:01:35.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我反而舒服起來了
Dialogue: 0,2:01:37.98,2:01:39.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服了嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:01:42.78,2:01:43.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就妤
Dialogue: 0,2:02:12.48,2:02:17.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服了嗎 真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:02:18.18,2:02:19.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,2:02:23.43,2:02:26.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 還不夠？
Dialogue: 0,2:02:30.18,2:02:31.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是慾望強呢
Dialogue: 0,2:02:38.88,2:02:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼 坐你旁邊嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:02:59.28,2:03:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個
Dialogue: 0,2:03:04.83,2:03:07.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又硬了嗎 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:03:07.98,2:03:09.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經射了好多了
Dialogue: 0,2:03:11.28,2:03:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還能射嗎 真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:03:17.43,2:03:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 再做一次舒服的事吧
Dialogue: 0,2:03:34.68,2:03:35.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,2:03:49.08,2:03:50.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想摸嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:03:54.63,2:03:56.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛明明摸了這麼久
Dialogue: 0,2:03:58.83,2:04:01.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是沒事 那麼
Dialogue: 0,2:04:02.88,2:04:03.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做你想做的吧
Dialogue: 0,2:04:27.33,2:04:28.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡胸部嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:04:32.13,2:04:33.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續讓我舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:04:55.23,2:04:56.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接摸嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:05:29.43,2:05:30.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:06:05.13,2:06:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是這麼熟練呢
Dialogue: 0,2:06:12.03,2:06:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這樣我乳頭會硬的
Dialogue: 0,2:07:12.18,2:07:14.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要讓我舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:08:01.08,2:08:02.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接摸嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:09:30.48,2:09:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面也好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:10:10.23,2:10:12.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好會舔
Dialogue: 0,2:12:22.23,2:12:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然這麼會舔
Dialogue: 0,2:12:31.53,2:12:33.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,2:12:46.08,2:12:48.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,2:14:34.98,2:14:36.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大肉棒
Dialogue: 0,2:14:58.68,2:15:01.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好硬
Dialogue: 0,2:15:13.08,2:15:15.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越舒服了
Dialogue: 0,2:15:21.18,2:15:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來
Dialogue: 0,2:15:26.43,2:15:28.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來讓你舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:15:46.83,2:15:47.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,2:16:09.93,2:16:11.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舌頭伸出來
Dialogue: 0,2:16:58.38,2:16:59.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:17:05.28,2:17:07.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也讓你舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:18:38.58,2:18:41.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡想被舔嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:18:50.28,2:18:51.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我舔
Dialogue: 0,2:19:17.73,2:19:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是最硬的一次
Dialogue: 0,2:20:24.19,2:20:26.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越硬了
Dialogue: 0,2:20:32.89,2:20:35.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊我也舔吧
Dialogue: 0,2:20:40.54,2:20:42.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股抬起來
Dialogue: 0,2:22:03.19,2:22:04.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡也讓你舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:22:09.94,2:22:10.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,2:23:04.24,2:23:06.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部夾住了
Dialogue: 0,2:23:14.14,2:23:15.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬硬的
Dialogue: 0,2:24:00.94,2:24:04.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是 一起舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,2:24:13.24,2:24:15.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讓我舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:25:16.84,2:25:17.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:25:46.69,2:25:48.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,2:25:49.69,2:25:50.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以插進來嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:26:00.79,2:26:03.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看插入的地方
Dialogue: 0,2:26:16.54,2:26:17.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:27:00.04,2:27:01.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:27:13.54,2:27:17.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是想看臉\N可以轉過來嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:27:43.54,2:27:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:27:49.24,2:27:51.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸我
Dialogue: 0,2:29:02.29,2:29:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插得好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:29:49.69,2:29:51.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個姿勢
Dialogue: 0,2:30:06.64,2:30:09.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看插入的地方
Dialogue: 0,2:30:10.24,2:30:12.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:31:31.69,2:31:32.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣呢
Dialogue: 0,2:31:33.94,2:31:35.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一樣的姿勢呢
Dialogue: 0,2:31:41.59,2:31:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插得好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:32:12.04,2:32:15.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續 繼續讓我舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:32:43.99,2:32:46.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插得好深
Dialogue: 0,2:32:51.79,2:32:53.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:33:19.39,2:33:22.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 後入吧
Dialogue: 0,2:33:44.14,2:33:45.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:34:06.79,2:34:08.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉著我的手
Dialogue: 0,2:34:11.89,2:34:13.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:34:30.49,2:34:31.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:35:18.79,2:35:20.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:35:54.94,2:35:58.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從前面插入吧
Dialogue: 0,2:36:59.74,2:37:00.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,2:37:43.24,2:37:44.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸我
Dialogue: 0,2:38:03.19,2:38:05.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插好深
Dialogue: 0,2:38:33.19,2:38:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要射了  -要射了嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:38:37.24,2:38:39.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出來吧 射出來
Dialogue: 0,2:38:58.39,2:38:59.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你弄乾淨
Dialogue: 0,2:39:37.84,2:39:39.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天射了好多呢
Dialogue: 0,2:39:40.99,2:39:42.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服了嗎
Dialogue: 0,2:39:44.29,2:39:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎 好關心
Dialogue: 0,2:39:50.59,2:39:54.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能一起舒服 太好了
Dialogue: 0,2:40:04.24,2:40:07.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(謝謝觀看)

਍