Subtitles by EroJapanese.com
Copyright 2017
I didn't think I'd get that far.
I'd like to start the appraisal stage.
I'm sure you already know...
this is an auction where the highest bidder wins the prize.
Please consider carefully and buy your preferred wife.
What are they doing?
How did I end up here?
It's been a year since I married my husband who works at a large corporation.
I was well-off.
Oh hello, I made a reservation. I'm Okita.
Yes, I want to talk to you about the main course.
I want to serve the best wine to the ladies I invited.
Can I speak to the chef?
Oh hello, it's Okita.
I want to serve the meat with...
a suitable side dish for the children.
I want something from 2000 or 2005, a vintage.
What? If you don't have it on stock, why don't you look for it?
It's an important party with my husband's partners's wives.
Don't say it's impossible.
Yes. Oh I need to go. Bye.
Make sure you have the wine ready... Thanks.
Oh hello, honey? How are you?
I was just making sure they will serve the right wine for dinner.
What's wrong? Honey?
What do you mean you don't have money?
What do you mean you have a debt?
Apologizing doesn't make any difference. What happened?
Hey, what happened?
Honey? You need to talk to me.
Oh no!
Are you awake?
I know you're confused.
It's best that you see this.
Honey... I'm sorry...
- Honey...
- I'm sorry this is happening.
It's all my fault.
It's all because I gambled and bought risky stocks.
All the investments I made thinking of you...
I don't remember much after that.
My husband was close to bankruptcy...
I understood he needed to pay off this debt.
We bought you as a payment for interests for your husband's debt.
We're going to make you work.
Don't touch me.
Excuse me.
The piece is not treating you well.
The "piece"?
You are going to be auctioned off soon.
- Would you like this?
- Thanks.
Enjoy.
Hello.
- Is it your first time?
- Yes, indeed.
- I've heard there're a lot of good pieces today.
- Oh really?
I'm looking forward to it.
Is it starting?
Thank you for coming today to the wife auction.
I would like you to consider these high quality wives.
I'll now call the high quality wives.
Entry number 1, Ayako-san.
Ayako-san is 29 years old.
She's been married for 3 years.
She works as a cabin attendant and her husband is an international pilot.
Entry number 2, Mari-san.
Nice.
She is 30 and has been married for 5 years.
She is a career woman working at a large cosmetics company.
She has one child.
They all look good.
Yes.
Entry number 3, Anri-san.
She is the youngest wife today.
You're going to be sold at an auction.
What? Auction?
Auction? But I want to see my husband!
This can't be right!
Your husband already agreed to this.
This contract was proposed by your husband.
Your price will pay off the interest he owes us.
But if the price is not enough, you may not see your husband ever again.
So sexy.
She is 28 years old and has been married for a year.
Her husband is on the board of directors.
She has worked as a model.
That looks very good.
That's Mr Okuta's wife.
- Why? - What's wrong?
- Oh, nothing.
I'd like to move on to the evaluation.
As I'm sure you know, this is an auction where the highest bidder wins the wife.
Please consider carefully and make your decision.
They all look so good.
So sexy.
I like women with no pubes.
Please don't touch them until you're given permission.
I couldn't help myself.
They smell so sexy.
So sexy.
Mr Tabuchi!
I knew it... It's you!
Please enjoy these wives as much as you like.
Nice.
Kneel.
Hurry.
Get on your hands and knees.
She has a nice body.
Hurry up.
Don't look away.
Go faster.
Hurry up.
Make sure all the customers can see you well.
Let them see your face.
She's very cute.
If you don't look cute, no one is going to bid for you.
Come on, look around.
Everyone is having fun.
Right? Isn't it so?
Touch my cock.
If you don't do it, you won't be bought at a good price.
Exactly.
You're a valuable piece.
You have to show your face to the customers.
Nice nipples.
Open your legs.
Come on.
You're not going to be bought.
This is getting in the way.
Let me smell you.
You're still resisting. You look like you're not enjoying this.
You have to look like you love it.
- Isn't that right, sir?
- You're right.
You're not going to be bought.
Look at this.
It smells good, doesn't it?
You want to be bought at a good price, don't you?
Come on.
Come on, look at me.
Look that way.
Enjoy it.
Come on, suck it.
Such an erotic face.
You have to suck it.
You'll regret it later.
What a lewd face.
I think this customer is interested.
Make him watch you.
You have to move your head.
Make some dirty noise.
Otherwise, you won't be bought.
You're doing well.
She's a wife.
Why are you looking away?
That's not good enough.
You're so erotic.
Why are you resisting?
Suck it.
You don't understand what's going on, do you?
Are you sure you don't want to be sold at a good price?
This is happening because your mind is not into it.
You have a lot of courage, don't you?
What do you think you are?
Say you want cock so the customers are happy.
Don't you want to be bought?
You'll never be able to see your husband ever again.
Is that what you want?
Come on, say you want cock.
I can't hear you.
Again.
I want cock.
Say it again.
"I can't live without cock," say it.
I can't live without...
I can't hear you.
I can't live without cock.
If that's true...
Suck it deep.
If you want to be bought do it deeper and slower.
You love this cock.
Say it.
I love this cock.
Do you think you can satisfy customers like that?
Come on. Get in.
She's so sensitive.
She's twitching so much.
Get up.
This is day two and I'd like you to see how much these slaves can do.
Entry number 3, Anri-san.
Come on.
Walk!
No!
Open your legs.
No, stop.
Your hand's in the way.
Stop it.
She's got big tits.
You're resisting too much.
I need you to be sold at a good price.
Spread your legs.
Spread them.
Don't move.
It's starting to feel good, isn't it?
You need to be seen by them.
No.
No... No...
It's starting to feel good, right?
No.
You want to be a slave for our customers, don't you?
No... No...
No.
Get on your hands and knees.
I don't want to.
You're so erotic.
No.
This is the best.
Look at this.
Oh no.
Don't say no.
You need to show this.
No.
Stick it out more.
Don't do this to me.
Don't do this.
You're so wet right here.
Oh no.
You're moving by yourself.
No.
Don't say that.
You're driving me crazy!
You can go crazy if you want.
Have them look at you more.
That's nice.
Don't look at me there.
Don't look... Don't look.
You're so wet.
Look at how wet her pussy is.
Please don't.
No... please.
I can't take it.
I think she needs more of that drug.
No, stop!
I think the drug is working.
Oh no, you're turning me on.
Do you want me to apply more?
Oh no, please don't. Not inside me!
Oh my god.
Don't do it deep inside me.
You're going to drive me insane!
You're so wet.
Stop it.
I don't want it.
This is wrong! Oh no!
- You want this, don't you?
- I can't suck it.
I can't do this.
Suck it.
I don't want cock anymore.
You love it, don't you?
I can't. No...
- Do it.
- No.
- You can do it.
No...
No.
Suck mine too.
Suck it more.
Open your legs.
Let me fuck you.
Come on.
Oh no.
Do you want cock?
You know you want it.
Cock... No... Cock... No.
- No.
- You want it, right?
No, cock... No.
Are you sure?
- No.
- Are you sure?
Don't put your cock in.
- Don't put it in.
- Are you sure you don't want it?
Don't put it in.
- No.
- But you hips are reaching out.
No... it's not about it.
Don't put your cock in.
Are you sure you don't want it?
Please look at her, sir.
You want it, don't you?
No, don't touch it.
You like it, don't you?
Don't put it in, please.
Change positions.
Please, don't put it in... Don't put it in.
No, don't put it in.
You want it, don't you?
No... cock.
Suck it.
No...
Did you see that, sir?
The customer is watching.
Don't look away.
No.
I'm going to break.
This is too much.
Oh no, I'm going to cum.
Come on.
Move.
Don't you like it?
Hold onto him.
No.
Oh no.
I don't want to do this position.
I don't want to do this.
You're in so deep.
We're not done... Stand up.
Stick your ass out.
The customer is watching.
Don't look away from the customer.
Look closely.
You want him to buy you.
You're driving me insane.
I'm going to cum.
Move by yourself.
Get on top of me.
- Hurry up.
- Yes.
Oh no.
Nice.
I can see clearly.
I don't want this.
Nice.
It feels good. It feels good.
It feels so good.
You like it, don't you?
Your cock feels amazing.
I'm going to cum. It feels so good. I'm going to cum!
You're so tight.
I want her.
- Cock.
- Do you want cock so much?
I want cock so much.
I want it.
It feels so good. It's so good.
Cock feels so good.
You're driving me insane.
I want more.
It's so good it's driving me crazy.
I feel it so much.
It feels amazing.
I love it so much.
You're getting so hard.
Your cock is so hard.
Give it to me.
I want your hard cock.
It's so good.
Your cock is so hard.
You want cum so much, right?
I want all your cum... I want all of it.
Give me all your cum.
Clean it up.
Cum feels so good.
You're going to give me more?
- More.
- You want it?
Please give me more cock.
I want more cock inside my pussy, please.
Nice.
Does that feel good?
It's so good.
It feels amazing. Your cock feels amazing.
Look at me.
Do you prefer my cock or your husband's cock?
I like your cock more.
It's better than my husband's cock.
Did you hear that?
My pussy!
It's so hot. It's so good!
I'm so close.
I'm going to cum.
Shoot it on my face.
What a nice woman.
I'm going to bid for her.
Nice.
She's so horny.
I want cock.
What a sexy wife.
Finally... It's time to test-drive these wives.
And then we'll start the bidding.
Please go ahead and enjoy yourselves.
Is this your favorite wife?
Please enjoy her
as much as you'd like.
Please look at my pussy all you want.
This is my pervert pussy.
Open it more.
So the customer can see.
Please look really deeply.
My clit is so horny and hard.
It feels so good.
I want you to smell it.
Don't just look, you can do more.
Can you smell the sexy smell?
Can you smell my pussy juice?
This is so erotic.
Oh my god.
Please look at how horny I am.
Please.
Please spread it and look at my pussy.
Please look at my married pussy.
Please do all sorts of things to me.
Please do all you want to my married dirty pussy.
Please.
I want more. Please stimulate me more.
Please give it to my horny pussy.
Spread your pussy yourself.
Please give it to me more.
Please give it to me.
It's so good.
It's so good...
I want more.
I want more...
I want it so much.
Please look inside too.
You can taste it with your mouth.
Please lick me.
So sexy.
Oh my god, you're going to make me cum!
You made me cum so much.
Please check what's it like inside.
I want you to see how it's like inside.
You're in so deep!
It's so good on my pussy!
You're making my pussy so wet!
I want you deep inside me.
I can feel you so much.
I can't help tightening my pussy!
I'm wrapping it around your finger!
It's so good!
I'm melting!
It's so good.
I love it! Oh my god!
I'm going to cum again!
Oh my god.
Ah...
What do you think, sir?
It's so good.
I've made my decision.
I'm going to announce the outcome.
The person who received the highest bid is...
entry number 3, Anri-san!
The highest bidder was... Mr Tabuchi.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Please enjoy yourself as much as you want.
You're the wife of Mr Okita, aren't you?
I knew it.
I can't believe it.
I'm spending time with such a beautiful woman.
Please don't tell my husband that I had sex with
his subordinate.
I know.
You're so risky.
I can't believe it.
Please, let me please you.
You're so sexy.
I'm so happy.
I can do something like this with such a beautiful lady.
I've been looking forward to this.
Let's keep this from my husband, ok?
Of course.
You're so hard.
Do you like it?
It's bigger than my husband's.
- More than Mr Okita?
- Yes, you're bigger than him.
I'm so excited.
You were watching, weren't you?
Do you want to see this too?
Please play with them gently.
Are you turned on?
I want to lick them.
Do you want to lick them?
Please suck them well.
This is your chance.
Please touch me a lot.
Do you like it?
I love it. It's so good.
It's someone else's wife so it's a lot better.
Please enjoy as much as you want.
Does your husband do this?
He sucks them like a baby.
I'm sure he's powerful at work.
But he's like a baby at home.
So please suck as much as you want.
You're sucking a lot more than my husband.
You're touching me so much.
They're so big.
I love them.
So huge!
Do you like big tits?
I love them.
It feels so good.
Do you like it too?
You're so hard.
You're so hard you're going to rip off your boxers.
I want your cock so bad.
What a nice cock.
Do you think so?
Oh my god.
Oh wow, this is what you were hiding?
What a big cock!
- Can I suck it?
- Yes, please.
There's so much pre-cum.
Ma'am...
It feels so good, I love it.
Your hips can't be still, can they?
It's too good.
Please look at my pussy too.
Please check if my pussy is worthy of your cock.
That's so sexy.
Do you like a horny pussy like this?
I love it.
Please look closely... Closer!
You're staring so much!
Do you like it?
You're buried in pussy!
Do I have a cute pussy?
Yes... you do.
I'm going to take off my panties so please look more.
More... please, look more.
- Ma'am...
- Please look at your boss's wife's pussy really well.
Yes, I will.
It's so embarrassing.
You're going to look there too?
- Your pussy and asshole. I'll look at everything.
- You're staring too much. It's embarrassing.
Ma'am...
Please look more.
My pussy loves it.
It's so good.
Please, come closer.
Oh yes, right there.
That place is reserved for my husband but you're touching it.
It's so good.
I want you more.
Please lick me here.
Here.
Your tongue feels so good.
You're licking me so much.
How is it, compared to my boss?
You're a lot better than my husband!
You're so good at it.
Your tongue feels so good.
I'm going to cum!
There's so much horny juice coming out of my pussy.
You're so good with your tongue.
Do you like it?
Come here.
- Please lie down.
- Like this?
My tits are getting in the way.
So big... Oh my god, your tits.
Please eat me more.
I'm going to eat your delicious cock.
Please eat a lot.
I'm so close.
You're going to cum? Don't!
You haven't fucked me yet.
It's because you're so hot.
- Can I do something that's going to make you want to cum even more?
- What is it?
Please lift your hips.
This is something I've never done to my husband.
I'm going to put your cock between my tits.
Oh my god.
You're thrusting your hips.
Do you like it?
This is going to make me cum!
You can't cum yet. You have to fuck my pussy.
Oh my!
You're going to make me cum.
You came!
Your sperm came out!
It's not good to cum first!
Did my tits make you cum?
Yes...
We've got to fuck my pussy now, ok?
I'm going to put it between my tits, ok?
- Are you ready?
- Yes, please.
There's cum everywhere and smells like sperm.
It was like your sperm flowed out of you.
I want you to hold back.
Ma'am.
Do you like it?
- It feels amazing.
- You haven't done me yet so please don't cum.
Oh my god, I can smell your sperm so much.
Do you like this too?
It feels so good.
Your cock is so hard.
It looks like it's still excited.
I'm going to ride you, ok?
Ma'am.
It's like I'm dreaming.
- You're really big.
- Am I?
I'm going to put it in, ok?
Ma'am.
You're so hard.
You're so hard and big.
It's inside me.
Give me your hands.
You can't stop thrusting it, can you?
You're bigger than my husband! You're bigger and harder than my husband!
You're loving it and it's so cute!
Oh, sir, are you close to cumming? We've only started!
Hey sir!
Don't cum yet!
I think you're having the time of your life!
Sir, I think your cock is really close to cumming.
Oh sir, don't take it out of me.
Are you close to cumming?
- Ma'am, you're so hot.
- What a horny man!
It makes me want to fuck even more.
You're too attractive.
I want you to fuck me more.
Could you sit on me?
Are you going to take a break? You're such a pervert.
Do you like this?
If it's you, yes.
Your tongue feels so good.
Your tongue is inside me!
Oh my god.
Can your cock take it now?
Do you want to fuck me from behind?
Are you going to fuck me from behind?
Don't cum without telling me, ok?
Fuck me.
Your cock is so hard and big.
It's not going to go in as smoothly as my husband, will it?
Oh my god, it's deep inside me!
Ma'am.
Sir, fuck me hard.
Ma'am!
Ma'am.
More.
- More!
You're going to make me cum!
I'm cumming!
It feels so good.
I love it.
Sir, it's so good.
You're so horny, aren't you?
Ma'am!
Your cock! Rub your cock inside me!
Oh my god!
You're like a dog!
It feels so good.
- You make me want to cum really fast.
- Oh really?
Oh sir!
What are we going to do?
I love it so much.
You can't hold back anymore?
Sir.
Fuck me.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
You're going to make me cum.
Ma'am.
You're going to shoot your load inside me.
Are you ok, sir?
Are you going to cum?
This feels so good.
Ma'am.
It's so good.
I'm going to cum.
I can't help twitching.
Are you always this intense?
I'm used to plain sex.
It's because it's with you that I'm doing much much.
It's so good.
I'm going to cum.
You pulled out?
- I nearly came.
- Oh really?
Please, fuck me.
I can't fuck you!
You can't keep it inside me, can you?
What's the matter?
Slowly.
My husband can't last three minutes.
Oh really?
I'm going to burst!
I'm going to break!
- Sir!
- Ma'am!
I can feel you so much.
- It's so good.
- I love it. - Oh really?
I'm going to burst!
Your cock is going to explode!
I'm going to cum!
Oh my god... I can even feel your veins.
Ma'am...
I can't take it any longer.
Please, cum on my face.
Please cum on my face all you want.
I want all of your cum.
I want to see it so please cum on me.
Yes.
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum!
Your cum is so thick!
You gave me such thick cum!
I want more cock!
I want more cock...
Subtitles by EroJapanese.com
Copyright 2017