[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,MS Sans Serif,8,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,15,0

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.54,0:00:14.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一個新聞\N(富田優衣)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.04,0:00:17.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從監務所逃出的佐瀧嫌犯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.05,0:00:19.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依然不見蹤影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.55,0:00:21.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前當局正全力搜索中\N(武田大樹 相原一洗)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.15,0:00:23.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可怕呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.15,0:00:28.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是往北海道逃跑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.26,0:00:32.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是這樣啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.96,0:00:34.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.46,0:00:37.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定會保護妳的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.97,0:00:42.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝老公
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.69,0:01:04.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(脫獄者 富田優衣)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.20,0:01:12.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.70,0:01:14.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這三天出差加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.80,0:01:16.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝妳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.30,0:01:17.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託妳看家囉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.81,0:01:21.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出門了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.71,0:01:22.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上小心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.52,0:06:36.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於醒啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.03,0:06:43.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳還不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.97,0:07:26.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.33,0:08:25.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.03,0:10:03.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.84,0:10:14.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.55,0:10:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.58,0:10:50.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.02,0:11:38.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.48,0:14:19.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.05,0:17:07.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.36,0:17:10.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.96,0:17:11.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.29,0:17:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.25,0:18:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有點中意妳了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.57,0:19:01.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.27,0:19:04.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我丈夫就回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.58,0:19:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到時真的回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.58,0:19:17.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就殺了妳的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.68,0:20:51.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳老公不是沒回來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.29,0:21:03.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳這樣害我興奮了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.30,0:21:14.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫我含一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.81,0:21:25.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽不懂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.22,0:21:30.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫我含
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.32,0:21:32.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有聽到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.02,0:21:39.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快一點 含住
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.16,0:22:12.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.16,0:22:16.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是不含的話
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.17,0:22:19.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳明白吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.47,0:22:25.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就該這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.69,0:22:49.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是含進去可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.01,0:23:00.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別輕舉妄動啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.21,0:23:04.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖含著
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.83,0:23:20.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 繼續含啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.05,0:23:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰說可以停下了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.57,0:24:01.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.07,0:24:06.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣含很痛苦嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.47,0:24:08.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辦不到嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.18,0:24:14.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那來這
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.89,0:24:20.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己過來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.69,0:24:24.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都扶妳起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.79,0:24:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.61,0:24:44.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點 這個
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.32,0:24:55.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.92,0:25:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣吸比較方便吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.84,0:25:18.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.85,0:25:23.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主動來吸
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.36,0:25:31.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我含到深處
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.79,0:26:04.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事都做不到嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.41,0:26:28.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己過來含
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.42,0:26:31.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快繼續啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.84,0:26:55.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本沒吸到深處啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.94,0:26:57.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深處呢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.95,0:27:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沒有用心在吸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.57,0:27:21.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又鬆口了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.99,0:27:41.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.99,0:27:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這表情很讚嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.31,0:28:00.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.72,0:28:16.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換來這邊 過來
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.65,0:28:45.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣才進得到深處嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.26,0:28:58.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亂動的話會嗆到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.18,0:29:18.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖的含 別亂動
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.29,0:29:30.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本沒到深處啊 深處
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.80,0:29:35.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,含深一點
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.22,0:29:50.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再給我繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.44,0:30:18.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒結束啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.76,0:30:36.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又隨便鬆口
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.78,0:30:57.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本沒進去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.49,0:31:00.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那站起來好了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.29,0:31:06.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把肉棒全部含下去
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.10,0:31:13.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢含進去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.61,0:31:21.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都要 全部
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.02,0:31:33.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然這樣最容易達成
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.22,0:31:36.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.93,0:31:42.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.43,0:31:46.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不住手
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.23,0:31:48.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出來前都給我含
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.24,0:31:51.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准給我吐出來
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.85,0:32:06.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對就這樣 不要吐出來
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.46,0:32:10.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射之前都要這樣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.97,0:32:20.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.67,0:32:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會讓妳等太久
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.87,0:32:24.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別給我鬆嘴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.78,0:32:31.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.40,0:32:51.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抬頭我瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.92,0:33:16.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子餓了歎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.50,0:34:36.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃好飽
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.51,0:34:42.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是久違的一餐
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.42,0:34:54.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.72,0:34:58.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.93,0:35:02.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳要待在這多久
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.63,0:35:04.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待多久
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.94,0:35:12.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就算一個人住在這
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.04,0:35:13.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也無所謂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.35,0:35:23.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳就盡量討好我
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.45,0:35:26.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然下場妳也明白吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.27,0:35:48.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好服侍我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.22,0:36:37.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都要舔到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.34,0:36:54.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是只有龜頭
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.34,0:36:56.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都要舔
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.68,0:37:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那個聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.48,0:37:37.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,含累了的喘息
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.72,0:38:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.64,0:38:29.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.34,0:38:32.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再深一點
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.55,0:38:46.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多也該習慣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.06,0:38:50.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.28,0:39:16.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近一點
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.20,0:39:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邊舔邊用手打
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.00,0:39:39.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辦得到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.91,0:39:44.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起來
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.72,0:39:51.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邊舔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.22,0:40:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好好做可要挨打的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.95,0:40:29.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽得到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.66,0:40:34.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就乖乖的吸
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.46,0:40:36.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起來
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.37,0:40:44.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我站著含啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.19,0:41:00.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本沒有好好做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.50,0:41:18.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳的聲音真棒歎
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.21,0:41:21.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被打屁股後更是
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.01,0:41:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉過來翹高一點
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.22,0:41:31.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股朝這邊翹高
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.33,0:41:44.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也要
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.34,0:41:53.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看仔細點
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.16,0:42:16.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳喜歡這樣呀
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.17,0:42:28.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.39,0:42:43.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳看這裡都這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.69,0:42:48.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-住手\N-這叫我怎麼住手
Dialogue: 0,0:43:08.61,0:43:10.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換我來好好舔遍妳
Dialogue: 0,0:43:40.75,0:43:42.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就硬起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:54.26,0:43:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:44:16.48,0:44:17.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.91,0:44:41.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來換這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.91,0:44:47.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.32,0:44:55.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹嘛遮起來
Dialogue: 0,0:45:00.33,0:45:01.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是說要服侍我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:45:07.53,0:45:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說要幫妳舔了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.30,0:46:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:46:32.82,0:46:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.82,0:46:36.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻過來我看
Dialogue: 0,0:46:41.53,0:46:42.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快一點
Dialogue: 0,0:46:51.14,0:46:52.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對就這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:46:58.34,0:46:58.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.86,0:47:18.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:47:35.88,0:47:37.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是說會舔遍嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:48:02.61,0:48:03.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准動
Dialogue: 0,0:48:28.43,0:48:29.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要動維持這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.14,0:48:32.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己用手張開
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.65,0:48:45.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再張開一點
Dialogue: 0,0:49:00.27,0:49:02.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-手幹嘛放開 -不要
Dialogue: 0,0:49:03.27,0:49:04.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快給我一直張開
Dialogue: 0,0:49:07.77,0:49:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點張開
Dialogue: 0,0:49:23.09,0:49:23.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼
Dialogue: 0,0:50:24.05,0:50:25.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我過來
Dialogue: 0,0:51:33.72,0:51:35.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰說可以隨便動了
Dialogue: 0,0:51:36.42,0:51:37.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:51:37.92,0:51:39.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣不行的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:43.93,0:51:45.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,服侍呢
Dialogue: 0,0:51:46.33,0:51:48.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳可要坐好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:51:50.24,0:51:51.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:51:55.64,0:51:55.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下來
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.56,0:52:18.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搖一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:52:38.28,0:52:39.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腰多搖下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:52:43.99,0:52:45.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要像這樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:52:58.10,0:52:59.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再繼續搖
Dialogue: 0,0:53:01.71,0:53:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要像這樣啊 這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:53:23.93,0:53:25.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來很爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:48.01,0:54:48.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱上來
Dialogue: 0,0:55:40.87,0:55:42.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來
Dialogue: 0,0:55:48.07,0:55:48.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:08.55,0:57:09.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:57:09.15,0:57:11.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-沒有... -怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:57:45.19,0:57:46.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躺下
Dialogue: 0,0:58:31.74,0:58:33.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加快速度
Dialogue: 0,0:58:47.35,0:58:47.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:58.76,0:58:59.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:01.47,0:59:02.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:59:04.47,0:59:05.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行
Dialogue: 0,0:59:07.17,0:59:08.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又進來
Dialogue: 0,0:59:09.87,0:59:10.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:21.59,0:59:23.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太刺激了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:59:39.00,0:59:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:59:45.31,0:59:46.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會更爽
Dialogue: 0,0:59:50.11,0:59:51.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴夾得更緊了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:19.00,1:01:19.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我來
Dialogue: 0,1:01:32.52,1:01:34.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己再張開一次
Dialogue: 0,1:01:37.62,1:01:38.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己用
Dialogue: 0,1:01:48.73,1:01:49.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點
Dialogue: 0,1:02:01.35,1:02:05.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說啊 請插進來
Dialogue: 0,1:02:16.06,1:02:17.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請插進來
Dialogue: 0,1:02:31.98,1:02:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說幾次啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:34.38,1:02:35.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請插進來
Dialogue: 0,1:02:37.68,1:02:38.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說
Dialogue: 0,1:02:41.29,1:02:42.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請插進來
Dialogue: 0,1:03:09.81,1:03:11.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:03:37.44,1:03:38.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:03:40.44,1:03:41.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不說我可要射進去了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:46.45,1:03:47.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好緊
Dialogue: 0,1:03:51.26,1:03:52.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快射了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:37.80,1:04:39.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是做得很棒嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:04:44.11,1:04:44.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,1:04:46.21,1:04:46.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給妳獎賞
Dialogue: 0,1:04:49.21,1:04:53.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不破壞妳的日常
Dialogue: 0,1:05:14.74,1:05:16.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來囉
Dialogue: 0,1:05:18.04,1:05:19.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,1:05:20.44,1:05:21.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好累呀
Dialogue: 0,1:05:22.25,1:05:23.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦妳了
Dialogue: 0,1:05:24.05,1:05:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熱水放好囉
Dialogue: 0,1:05:25.85,1:05:27.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎 謝謝
Dialogue: 0,1:06:07.89,1:06:09.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼感覺妳很緊張
Dialogue: 0,1:06:10.29,1:06:11.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得出來嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:06:14.80,1:06:17.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道妳有秘密嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:06:20.50,1:06:21.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,1:06:24.41,1:06:28.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實打掃時打破東西了
Dialogue: 0,1:06:29.21,1:06:29.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼呀
Dialogue: 0,1:06:30.72,1:06:32.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會這樣就生氣
Dialogue: 0,1:06:34.62,1:06:35.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,1:06:36.72,1:06:38.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那妳沒受傷吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:40.93,1:06:41.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,1:06:42.43,1:06:44.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好了
Dialogue: 0,1:06:46.63,1:06:47.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,1:12:45.49,1:12:46.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:12:53.60,1:12:54.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,1:12:55.70,1:12:56.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找不到啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:57.50,1:12:59.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,1:13:00.20,1:13:02.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找舊的高爾夫球稈
Dialogue: 0,1:13:02.61,1:13:05.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後輩開始玩了想說送他
Dialogue: 0,1:13:06.21,1:13:06.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子呀
Dialogue: 0,1:13:07.71,1:13:09.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去二樓看看
Dialogue: 0,1:13:32.04,1:13:35.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼不見了
Dialogue: 0,1:13:39.24,1:13:41.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡嗎 沒有
Dialogue: 0,1:13:45.55,1:13:47.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這在這
Dialogue: 0,1:13:49.15,1:13:50.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這個
Dialogue: 0,1:14:11.68,1:14:12.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊
Dialogue: 0,1:14:25.49,1:14:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,1:14:52.22,1:14:53.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我一起走吧
Dialogue: 0,1:15:00.32,1:15:01.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起走吧
Dialogue: 0,1:18:24.23,1:18:25.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脫掉吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:02.37,1:24:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫我舔吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:49.51,1:24:51.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 要含深
Dialogue: 0,1:25:34.86,1:25:36.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴怎麼放開了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:37.26,1:25:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續幫我舔
Dialogue: 0,1:25:39.66,1:25:40.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會溫柔的
Dialogue: 0,1:26:53.84,1:26:55.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來讓我舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:27:34.08,1:27:37.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣 繼續
Dialogue: 0,1:27:44.59,1:27:46.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好幫我舔
Dialogue: 0,1:28:29.93,1:28:32.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫我吹
Dialogue: 0,1:28:42.85,1:28:43.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邊看著我吹
Dialogue: 0,1:29:31.79,1:29:32.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也幫妳舔吧
Dialogue: 0,1:31:11.19,1:31:12.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起啊 太急了
Dialogue: 0,1:32:16.06,1:32:16.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要插了
Dialogue: 0,1:34:34.80,1:34:36.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,1:35:06.33,1:35:07.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:35:09.33,1:35:10.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就再多做幾次
Dialogue: 0,1:36:06.09,1:36:08.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我一樣用力搖
Dialogue: 0,1:36:37.02,1:36:37.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐起來
Dialogue: 0,1:36:45.43,1:36:46.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看
Dialogue: 0,1:37:59.90,1:38:01.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:39:14.68,1:39:16.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想從後面舔
Dialogue: 0,1:39:31.79,1:39:33.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看
Dialogue: 0,1:40:02.42,1:40:05.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴吸得好緊
Dialogue: 0,1:42:26.57,1:42:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:42:29.57,1:42:29.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看看
Dialogue: 0,1:42:29.87,1:42:30.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看看
Dialogue: 0,1:43:51.85,1:43:52.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要?
Dialogue: 0,1:43:53.06,1:43:54.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了 想要更多
Dialogue: 0,1:45:20.14,1:45:21.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了要去了
Dialogue: 0,1:45:52.57,1:45:53.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳真讓人受不了
Dialogue: 0,1:46:11.19,1:46:12.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:46:16.60,1:46:17.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:46:23.51,1:46:24.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好硬
Dialogue: 0,1:47:00.74,1:47:01.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:08.25,1:47:09.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:12.45,1:47:13.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:28.67,1:47:29.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:33.78,1:47:34.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,1:48:45.55,1:48:48.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(富田優衣)
Dialogue: 0,1:48:50.35,1:48:52.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(武田大樹 相原一喜)
Dialogue: 0,1:48:53.66,1:48:56.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆 老婆
Dialogue: 0,1:48:57.26,1:48:59.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會這樣
Dialogue: 0,1:49:02.36,1:49:04.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起對不起
Dialogue: 0,1:49:08.37,1:49:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,1:49:14.68,1:49:15.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,1:49:23.69,1:49:26.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(監督 龍太)

