Neteorra Reef Temple Trip,
It was committed by my boss for two days and one night.
Can I really go on an employee trip?
I've been retired for half a year.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's a temple trip after the year-end payment is over.
Our company's performance was good this year.
So in terms of encouragement,
I'm going to a temple trip to a luxury hot spring inn.
No problem with the couple.
Besides, you were an employee of our company.
It's even better.
I am a little embarrassed though.
I said to leave to get pregnant.
When I met again, I thought it was after I had a baby.
Time already, let's hurry.
2 years of marriage
At first I thought I could not depend on young Ryosuke.
In-company love dating at the same company
There was a lot of trouble in communicating with Ryosuke, who was three years old.
I feel trustworthy after marriage.
After my dad broke his ten million yen debt
My family factory was almost on the way to an auction because of my debt.
I thought my dad was over.
Ryosuke was able to get a loan somehow.
I am grateful enough for lack of thanks to Ryosuke.
So I want to have a baby.
I want to build a happy family with Ryosuke.
13:04 ...
Akane and hot springs, temple bus waiting
-Good morning
Good clothes, good.
Good morning
It's been a long time.
It's been a while
- It's been a while.
-Iknow, right
Aoi, you look better.
Oh, is that it?
-How are you? - Good job.
- Did you miss me?
- It's not possible.
- It's all because of you.
- You stole our best Madonna.
-Sorry
- I'll put things in the car before you come.
-Please
please
- It's been a long time.
- It's been a long time, Mr. Aoi.
What's different, Mr. Aoi, your face is wide open?
- It's really good.
-No
How does it feel to be a real wife?
I wish I could, too.
Yes, I love it when I get married.
- Did you get pregnant?
- No. I have not done it yet.
Yes, you have not done it yet.
I know that? If a man is over 40, he will not do anything.
-is that so?
- Yeah, it's not like when I was young.
Yes, I know.
Because I'm still young, I can have it soon.
I really hope so.
So shall we go in?
So let's get cold.
Sawaki, it's been a while.
All right, you came.
Would it be okay for an outsider like me to go on an employee trip?
Because the staff did their best,
I do not have a problem with the couple.
-Yes, Thank you
- Now, let's go.
Now, look at this, turn this one by one.
Thank you.
Here too
Do you think it's almost done?
- Everybody's holding a beer, right?
-Yeah
Thank you.
We have a great vacation with you.
At this time, year-end settlement is over.
We have a close relationship with the client in the future.
It is this season
It's all thanks to you guys.
So today is the New Year's Day.
Currently S1 accounting firm is showing a surge in earnings.
Next year,
Aimed at an organized accounting firm
He's been making good progress.
- Then the salary will be much higher.
- Oh ~
- And goodwill.
- Wow, that's good.
Next year's temple trip ...
- Let's go abroad.
- and ~ overseas travel
- Let's all work together.
-Okay
Hit the can.
- Now, toast
- Cheers ~
-Thank you
I was swayed, Tissue
The car will shake.
Does anyone have nausea?
I think I'll puke.
No one.
- I'm a good nuisance.
- Not really.
I was in the front row when I was in elementary school.
Hooch
This is really inconvenient.
It's hard to sit, will I go inside?
- She wants to get pregnant.
-Yeah
- Are you pregnant?
-yet
- You have not done it yet.
-Yeah
This hand.
It's not different from the past.
The chest is big also
Still, the guy next to you is awkward.
Eyes that see me
The gaze pretending to be the best parent
If there is no other person, it reveals a canine.
When I'm in the company,
I was harassed.
(Arrive at 15:13 Akanezawa SA)
It's okay.
- Is Aoi okay?
- Aoi?
The manager was keeping an eye on him.
The manager likes her.
So you better be careful.
The general manager seems to be gentlemanly
It's totally different for a woman.
But ... Aoi is the wife of the employee.
- Should we do that?
-Do you really think so?
- I mean, really.
-right?
- Aoi's toilet?
-Yeah
Oh yeah, sell limited items here
Let's go quickly.
Let's go, let's go
Aoi, we'll go first.
Look at it a little.
It's about your company's closing.
you..
I wrote reverse accounting.
That's why I've lost 300 million yen.
That's Mr. Kuramoto of the Accounting Department.
I got a payment from the manager.
The former manager
If you made a payment,
You're deceived, I do not know that.
I do not think so.
Besides, you ...
I got bribes to Yamagura.
that's..
And at Aoi Papa Factory
I even loaned ten million won.
Bribery on suspicion of helping tax evasion
If this happens,
You know what happens?
First you'll be deprived of your tax agent status.
You will also live in prison.
Then you're ruined.
Our company
It's a big blow.
please forgive me
Manager, what should I do?
What should I do?
If you do not want to go into a cell,
It's all for me.
Because you did not know anything
I'll treat you as ignorant of them.
When you go back, you change the accountant's account book.
I'm in the food court, I'll talk to the rest later.
Ryosuke's tax evasion?
bit?
for me
He committed a crime to help his father.
Did you hear that?
It's all your husband did.
Really?
Ryosuke ... he got tax evasion at the company.
Hate
stop it
Let go, do not.
Doing
Would you like to go again?
16:22 ...
Aranzawa Onsen arrival, south accommodation
I finally arrived, it's hard
Wow ~ Nice room.
It's really cool.
we are here
Here's a hot spot, pretty famous.
-Oh yeah?
-Huh
I just wanted to see you once.
Well, good.
Onsen
- I'll be there first.
- Good.
Boss
This is a girl.
I know
I saw the sign before I came in.
I want to be with you.
It's beautiful, too.
I like the naked look.
Get out
Show me more.
I can see my breasts.
I do not think I forgot, did I?
What to do
Show me
-your
-It's not possible
My mind will change.
Do not you want to save your husband?
There's no way I can save her.
If you can change your books
Not all the sins are gone.
Who can do it?
You want to put him in jail?
Well, then you should give it to me.
Show me more.
I can not.
I can not help you with anything.
It'll be a while.
To respond to my heart
I do not like it
It's really smooth.
Stop it, I'll scream.
Then I
I can not cooperate with anything.
He's really good.
Please let me go.
I can not stand it.
I'm really tired.
Please stop it
It's getting harder.
You're keen.
It just happened to look like this.
No, stop it.
Please stop.
Please let me go.
Stop it.
If you want to scream, you scream.
Stop it, let go.
It's wet.
Please stop.
It's a killing ass.
Do not
Boss
It's for you guys.
I do not like it
Please let me go.
With that in mind,
This is different.
You're killing me.
Could you suck it with that cute mouth?
- I can.
-I do not like it
Why I hate
It's okay.
Instead of sucking
Please let me go.
Even if you just look at it like this
I've been servering this many times, but what if I did something else?
Under a woman, it's your pussy too
I have an erection like this.
I need you to help me.
Can you do it?
Please suck it.
You can put it in.
Put it all right.
I really kill you.
Do it.
Give me a little more.
Good mood
Please feel good.
Put it a little deeper.
It's awesome.
I can not.
Please stop.
- You're wet.
- It is not.
Stop it.
It does not open.
Who's there?
So is he Aoi? Aoi-san? Aoi-san?
- Just go into the water.
- Aoi? Aoi -
- Anything?
-is not it?
- Aoi? Aoi-san? Is it missing?
- There must be ... Aoi.
- Are you with someone else?
- I do not think so.
- What are you guys doing?
- Oh.
- I'm afraid it's locked in.
- Oh, it's locked in here.
- So what about Aoi?
- Where is he?
I do not know? I went to the hot springs first.
- Where'd he go?
- Is not it an open-air bath?
- Oh, do you have an open-air bath?
- I like that.
- You want to go?
- Yeah, fine. Come on.
Okay, let's go to the open-air bath.
- Are you enjoying it?
- Yes.
Thank you very much.
This year has been a smooth year.
(18:05 ... temple trip, start of the field)
So I was able to come to this temple trip.
Let's enjoy the festivities now that we have plenty to prepare.
You can enjoy yourself.
Then finally, Sawaki's manager
I'll listen to your drink.
Thank you, Sawaki.
Next year, we will further increase the company's performance.
Pleasing clients
I wish you all to be an accounting firm.
Yes
Should not we do something like tax evasion?
I do not think so.
Accountants must be fair and fair
You can not touch a dishonest thing.
However,
We have to work together for taxation.
Let's make a toast for future development.
-Cheers
- Cheers ~
I will enjoy this food
Enjoy all the meals.
It looks really good.
- Aoi-san, do you drink well?
- No. I do not drink much.
-Oh, I see
The hot spring is open all day.
Yes? Do you open 24 hours?
But is there another drink? Get me some whiskey.
- Whiskey please.
- Me too.
You need a lot?
It's delicious.
I have a drink.
I brought the liquor.
- Bring it here.
- It's a set.
Here's a bottle.
Uh, turn that way too.
Reading 45 degrees
Hmm, come on.
I like drinking.
- Do you mind?
- Yes.
It's hot here, but it'll be okay.
It's a good drink.
OK?
You do not drink well.
You drank too much.
Ryosuke go and have more alcohol
-Ah yes
- Water, ice water
Ice water? Yeah
- Let's go pick it up with me.
-Thank you
Sorry
- Do you want a king game?
- The king game?
Gentlemen, here we are.
Red is king. Pick one by one.
I can command you, here one by one
The king can command any order.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Oh please
Who is the king? Who is the king? Who is the king? character!
-Boss
- Dean, too.
- Be strong.
- Now.
-how will we do it
- It's fun.
Anybody kiss me?
OMG! It's terrible.
character! I've decided.
- This time Aoi is here.
- So?
Aoi, why do not we get one shot?
It's okay.
-on? - One-shot one shot
- I'll take it.
- It's the king's order.
- The king's orders are absolute.
- This is smooth.
- Well, Sawaki has a very good manners.
- Is not it too much?
- It's okay.
It's barking.
-drink
-Yeah
Thank you.
-at a whack..
- I'll have a drink.
No, no, it's still there.
It's a long time ago.
It's so poisonous, it's really hard.
Drink this much here.
I will drink
It'll be fine this time.
Let's take a look at what's left.
Drink, drink, drink, drink
- That's all right.
- Let's look at it that way.
-please
- Let's have a quick look at this.
- It was dangerous.
- It's poisonous, too reading.
- Do you want to do it again?
-Yeah
Pick
Who is the king, who is the king, who is the king?
It's me
- I'm here again.
-What's up
It's strong.
- Drink more, drink.
- It's a bunch.
I really can not.
- Are you going to be an alcoholic?
-Iknow, right
- I'm going to be an alcoholic.
- Everything, all of it?
You have to drink everything.
It's not easy.
It's okay, it's okay.
I just want you to do it.
- Let's try it again.
- It's okay. It's okay.
This time, let's leave the manager.
Pick it up.
- Please. - This time.
- You pull everything out? -just a second
I can not get my body shut.
Well, I'm looking forward to it
- Who is the king?
- It's me.
- Aoi, lie here like this.
And drink ...
At a glance, at a glance, at a drink, at a glance, at a drink ...
Who is the king?
- It's me again.
-What?
Strong
What would be better? What do you do?
What should be fun?
Do something different, other.
Yes, there was a hot spring.
- It's okay.
- Let's go. Let's go. - Why do not you take off your clothes?
What're you doing? Do not run away.
If you do, you can save your husband.
Actually
Your husband broke the law for you and your father.
Originally, it's all right.
You need to help.
- Look at this.
- What?
really?
Really? really?
-you can do it?
-I could
Mr. Aoi supports you.
-OK?
- It's okay. Really?
OK? I think I'm drunk.
- I do not think the complexion is too good.
-OK? OK?
-No problem
- Okay, I'm fine.
Sethet!
If you play baseball ~
This happens.
Out, Safe, Scissors Rock!
- I do not think so.
- I really need to get naked.
- I'll take it off.
-really?
- Is she really okay?
- Well then!
I'll take it.
- Our Madonna.
- Can you pull it off?
Can I do it? I'll solve it here.
- Turn around.
-Good
- Look at this. - What color?
- Show me once.
Scissors rock again.
Do it again? Yes, we should do it again.
- How many more times do we have to take off?
- How many are you wearing?
I have to win at least three more times.
Can I really take it all away?
- Shall we go next?
- Let's go.
Music start
When I play baseball
This happens.
Out, Safe, Scissors Rock!
- Hooray!
- I did it.
It's gone.
Take off
He's a really good friend.
It's okay. Are you okay? The manager succeeded.
Well done
The second is winning for the manager.
Then you'll be exaggerated.
Thank you very much
Should we take off now? I'm going.
Please, take off.
- This is killing me.
- Aoi, the milk is big.
- Turn around, turn around.
- I have to turn around.
- Tee panties, tee pants.
- I want to look closer.
- Wait a minute.
- Can I touch it?
- No, what are you talking about?
- Kill me. - Kill me.
-Very cute
What are you doing
- Show me more of this. - It's rare.
- Let me see more.
- I'll just look.
- Wait, wait, wait.
What is it, what are you doing?
- Aoi, are you okay?
- That's what you wanted.
- I can do it. - Let go.
- It's just a game.
I'm too drunk, I'm pregnant, I'm going to do it.
Wait, get out of the way. I have to go to the room.
- I'm playing in the middle of it.
- Go back to our room.
- What are you really doing?
- It really hurts.
-Boss
-Quiet
If you do not be quiet, people will break.
I do not like it
Do not you want to save your husband?
I can get it.
So be quiet.
Hate
Be quiet.
If you let me enjoy it,
That way,
You can not go to jail.
Yes, very good.
I took a picture.
Stop it.
Okay, I got wet.
If you make a sound, I'll spread the picture.
I'll do it now.
But if you make a noise
People will know.
no no
Do not do that
I'm soaked.
Please stop.
I'll catch you.
look
Do not shout
Sorry
I'm touching my pussy.
Good?
Now suck this.
Suck it up like before.
Pictures are scattered.
My husband is going to jail too.
You just have to suck it up a little.
Do not cough, I'll catch you.
finally
Do not
I see you kill me.
I feel really good
Stop it.
Do not
Hate
There's a sound.
Give me your tongue.
Give me a long time.
I do not resist.
I feel really good
I will kill you.
It feels good.
If you do this
It'd be better.
stop it
I'll cover here.
I do not like it.
- You should stick your tongue properly.
-Hate
I do not like it.
Come out.
Has Ryosuke ever done this before?
He's really weak.
Since college
Sail on the wind
I grew up easily.
We have to be weak.
That guy
If you go to jail
How are you gonna stay?
I'm sorry.
Maybe not come back alive.
How can i
Do you want to help? Then one thing
Do not make suggestions.
Your body
Let me write what I want.
I'll help you with Ryosuke.
I'll do anything I can.
Boss
Save him.
Accept the proposal
You can use my body at will.
All right, I promised.
It was committed to the director.
You can not do it if you are committed.
Did he betray Ryosuke?
No. This is to help Ryosuke.
I can not make Ryosuke a criminal.
It's okay if you put up with me.
That way
Hello
Hello, Tsukasa?
Where did you go?
Why do not you answer the phone?
I thought I was a little drunk and I was taking a bath.
Ryosuke, where are you now?
I
It's in the lounge inside the lobby.
It's like a simple snack bar.
Uh, yes.
That's why.
I was having a drink with my ladies.
Come on, Aoi.
Will you come to Tsukasa?
Aoi, come on.
I've been asking you from time to time.
I'm drinking with women.
I'm simply drinking
I said marriage was happy and I followed the liquor
To have a baby soon
Aoi is pregnant soon
Give it to me, give me a break.
Give it back, give it back.
Aoi: Is your body okay? She said she was taking a bath and resting.
- Aoi, Ryosuke was a lot drunk.
-Sorry
What do we do?
- Give me back.
-No no
- Tsukasa. I'm so sorry. I'm too drunk to take it.
-Okay
- Give me back quickly.
-okay okay
Aoi, help Ryosuke wobble.
- Have a drink together. I'll wait here.
-come fast
I can not be Ryosuke.
(23:09 ... Gwangwol Lounge)
- I do not think I can do anything.
- I do not think so.
-Excuse me
- Oh, did you come?
- Mr. Ryosuke is here.
- I'm Aoi.
It's been like this before.
I did not really take it.
- Keep going.
-i See
I do not really ...
I do not know what you're saying.
My job is accounting.
I dream of work.
I did not have a problem with what I did.
- I'm so confident.
- It's not a problem at all.
I've already stretched it like this.
- We did not get it.
-Yes, got it
- We have to bring men in. Can you do it?
- Yeah. It's okay.
- Then we'll go. I'm sorry.
-Thank you very much
It's no big deal.
Honey, get up.
The manager came down.
Look, look, look,
- Because we can not move, we call our male colleagues.
- Come on, honey.
- I'll help you.
- Oh, would you?
- Are you going to the hot springs?
- Oh, I'm thinking about it.
- Well, then this is me.
- Excuse me for bothering you.
-Thanks for your work
- You should get an early rest.
Come on, get up.
- I'm screaming.
-try
Please do yourself a favor.
I'm really screaming.
Then your wife
I'll see you get hit like this.
you
-stop it
- There's no way I can help you.
By the way, why are you wearing these clothes?
You can change your schedule
Did you even think about going back?
Is not that right? If it did
The prison is waiting.
Listen to me properly.
What are you doing?
I do not care.
more
Make me feel good.
You also want it.
You have a strong sexual desire.
No
Go closer.
I'm really excited about this.
The nipple is sensitive.
I can not stand it.
Next door
What is this pantie
Wearing for me?
Yes?
I do not like this.
It was already wet.
In front of her husband
It's soaked.
Do you want me to put it in quickly?
In your hole
I'll rub it like this.
Also
It's already wet.
I'll lick you now.
You like it?
Not excited
I'm rubbing it with your panties.
Feeling good?
It feels good.
it's not like that?
You are obscene.
I'm sorry.
What is this
stop it
Lick my nipples.
Lick me with your hands moving.
Yes, there it is.
Good mood
I'll do it by hand.
Ok a little more
more
Now lick the balls
Lick properly with your tongue
Good good..
How do you feel?
My husband is next to me
I feel like licking my balls
It feels good.
Make me feel better.
Use your hands this time.
Use it yourself.
Do not you want to lose your life now?
So be good.
Let me be a baby.
It's so soft here, here.
Take a look.
Do it well.
Have you ever done this?
It's a good teapot.
Now lick again
By hand
More violently
want?
It's sickening.
I got stuck.
It's getting wet.
Come a little closer.
No, stop it.
Holding a face
Really good
driving me crazy
Come this way
Good mood
It's tight, it's tight.
I like it.
Good mood
So good
I like it.
Did you feel good?
Your husband does not break.
Take your husband back to the room.
What are you doing?
Ryosuke, the manager is going to break.
- Please stop.
-Quiet
Ryosuke is there.
No
Sir, wait.
No, let me go.
Let me go.
I do not like it
- What is it?
-Do not do that
Boss? what
- What ... What?
- Stay still.
Why are you tied up?
Do not do it.
Towards her
Because my feelings have exploded.
- What are you talking about?
- A guy like you.
She does not fit at all.
what?
- I'll show you.
- No, no.
- This is the real look of your wife.
-What?
No, no.
What is this?
No
What the hell is this?
Boss
I can never send you to prison.
So I asked him for help.
- I told you.
- What are you talking about?
Your body
I want you to be able to write for me.
How can you say that?
It's a good wife.
By the way
Rather than you
I am more happy with her happiness
- Wait, what are you doing?
-Boss
No ... No.
Stop it.
Stick out your tongue
- Listen to me.
-No
Then both of you will be ruined.
Tsukasa ..
- Hold your tongue.
-I do not like it
I can never believe that.
I can not believe it.
It's cute.
Go ahead and stick it out like you used to.
Stick out your tongue
Honey, do not look.
Do not look
Tsu ... Tsukasa
Not yet.
What is your status now?
You're already wet, are not you?
Please stop
I'll make you much more cute.
You really like it.
Boss
No..
stop
Please stop
What are you doing
What are you really doing .. Please stop.
Can you hear me?
What is this
Stop it really!
It's really loud.
awhile
You are too noisy
I'm stuck.
No, no.
No!
Let me go.
It was so good that you could not stand it?
no
You got so wet.
Not just touching
Show me the drenched pussy.
It's so wet.
It's a big deal.
No, stop it.
-no
- The milk's hard.
It's getting wet.
It's a really good flesh.
I've been wasting too much.
I brought good gifts.
Do not, do not.
- It feels good.
-Do not do that
So good? How much do you feel?
In your head
My head is dark.
In the head .. in the head ..
Both of you are on their way to destruction.
They are fools.
No, stop it.
Just to be honest, I'm crazy about it.
You have to be honest.
Are you going now?
Hold on.
stop
-stop
- Do you think?
Show me how you never showed your husband.
Are you watching now? Moving back on its own
I'm going?
No ... stop it.
No
You're on your way.
It's gone.
Stop it ... I can not ... Please stop.
I'll give you another one.
- How about this one?
-no no
This ...
Are you really killing me?
Feeling good?
No
No no
- Go ... go.
- You're going.
Put it down.
Goes..
Go, go
Go away ..
Thanks
I found this woman.
It's Danney.
Stop it.
stop..
You know how to pick up your nigga?
I see your bride getting so horny.
What a nonsense.
Yes?
Lick me
You better be good.
For the hip
Enjoy together
Please continue.
You can not move.
stop
I'll get the inside out.
There's no other way than going on.
Okay, from now on
Suck my cock
I can suck my stuff.
You can wash anything.
It's what you like.
Suck it up with your mouth
You do not have the right to deny it.
-right
-nevertheless
Look good
We have to do it until rice.
Use your hands.
As usual
Oh, you did it.
Oh, I've had enough erection.
Use your hands to lick me wildly
It looks like it is now.
It looks like rice.
Show me the wrap.
In this situation,
Is your hair strange?
Suck
Oh, good.
It's especially good today.
I'm so happy.
Keep going, lick the balls.
Lick the pussy.
Faster and faster
With your hands
Okay, very good.
Now get down.
Let's put it
I got sick.
Is this much bigger and cheerful?
Do not
It's huge.
Looks like it's a waste for you.
Go upstairs.
show me
You are so violently stuck
Would you wrap it up?
No
I feel great right now
All right, move it, move it.
Grace ~ kills
stop
in action
All right, all right.
driving me crazy
My cock acknowledges a much better one.
you too
Deeper
A little more
Let's enjoy sex
Put it deep.
Go ahead a little bit more.
bite
If you do not cheat quickly, you will continue.
Good.
More aggressively
Faster
Now show me, you're wrapped up
Move a bit more violently.
More violently
Is it like rice?
Wrap, wrap
Come out, come out.
Wrap
Please clean it.
Stop it.
Feeling good?
- It's coming out.
-No
I go.
Ah, I'm going.
Go ~~~
No
Good mood
Good mood?
Good
In front of your husband
I'll wrap it up.
In the mouth of four years
I'll be great.
I feel good.
Honey
What is going on
then
Please go back well
There is no other choice.
Sorry
you
sorry but
It's all for you.
Sorry
you are..
no..
Wait a minute
No
Do you understand?
-no
-Yeah?
- This is not it.
-awhile
Wait a minute, honey.
Please forgive me.
I did it to save you.
Please forgive
It was for you.