Production
-S1 -
- Instructions -
(Information)
Hello,
It is the president of Kool who greets with the 11th subtitle ^^ *
The left actor starred in this SSNI-444
Aoi is Aoi!
Aoi is 93 years old / 26 years old / 160cm
It's the fifth year actor who debuted in 2014 ^^ *
The hardware that came up as the water rises
Stable acting power is emerging as a sign of S1
Especially if you strip it off.
I have a lot of ...
And another point of this work !!!
If you watch this volume,
You can really feel like it's awesome ^^ ;;;
The smooth texture of the ...
A fantastic collage of that stupid ass that lacks 100 points ...
This SSNI-444 is the hardware of AOI
It's really filled in the video and it is expressed in the high quality
The actor next to Aoi ...
I do well ;;;;
Oh, excuse me
Good morning ~ / Come on ~
Well ... with Eino Arena and ...
I have an appointment to meet.
Would you like to confirm?
Did you make an order? / Yes ...
I'll check to see if it's on the list of reservations / Yes -
You've seen a lot of cameo ;;
Is not there ?? / Just a moment ...
Nowadays ... there are many people who have reservations ...
Oh !! It's okay!
Let me check by phone
Dr. Ikeda came to you
Yes ~
Then we'll show you on the third floor
Yes, sir.
Now you can go up to the third floor!
Okay ~ Thank you ..
You can feel the beauty of Aoi's water right
Authentic Mystery Stand Spencer Thriller Massage ...
Aoi's latest April SSNI-444
Please enjoy with the 11th Korean subtitles of Mr. Jokul ^^ *
I'm talking ;;
Collapse; Thighs ;;;
Anyway ;;; Lol
Start now !!! ^^ *
MADE BY COOL President
11th Story
Is it okay?
Well ... it hurts because of what it is ...
Well ...
<font color="
Conspiracy?
Yes!
I just got a new one before the station
The guests there are very nice
Ah ...
Is there a good reputation?
Yes!
Before you get any worse ... why do not you go?
Well ...
But ... I was so lazy ;;;;
Hey ...
Quickly ...
Because I'm afraid I'll get worse.
Okay ~
Thanks
A receptionist who is weak in coercion and can not express her disgust
And the erotic identity that seeks her
The title of the title
Chiropractor, Massage, etc ...
In a word ...
<font face="HY바다M" color="
Sorry ... Please wait a moment ~
Yes ..
Ai Goya ... I'm sorry. You waited a lot?
It's OK ~
Then ..
Your name is ... Aoi right?
Yes ~
Hi ~ ~ Thank you very much for your reservation ~
Then ...
Are you visiting for the first time today?
Yes ~ / Yes ~~
Thank you
I'll do my best, too, first of all ...
Go to the treatment room and manage from your knees.
Focus on the uncomfortable while looking at the whole
Yes ..
I think I'll look at it and manage it.
So let's go ahead. So quickly
Let's take you to the other room
Yes ~ / Yes ...
I'll be there
here ... come this way ~ / yes ~
You can sit here during your preparation
Ok ..
Well ... here's a simple questionnaire here
I want you to fill out the information ~
Yes ~ / Yes ~
Do you want to keep your bags there? / Thank you ~
Well ... just write it down ~
Oh ~ I see!
I'll leave my bag here
Today ... where are you particularly uncomfortable?
Well ... that's ...
Overall a little uncomfortable ...
Yes ~
Especially ... on the shoulder side ...
Should it be your shoulder? / Yes ~
How about the bottom of your waist?
Your foot? / Yes ~
I have a lot of legs ..... it hurts ~
Simply write it down!
Yes ~ Thank you ~
You are in trouble ~
Then, once you get up on a white towel ...
Oh ... just sit down ...
The shoulder is the worst part, so I'll take a look at it from there
Thank you ~
Is your shoulder a lot uncomfortable?
Yes ~
Is it bad for you?
Yes ... Yes ~~
Well ... the balance of the body is a little bit distorted.
Yes ...
Ah ... definitely ...
Well ... I have a lot of time using my computer ...
Do you have a lot of office work?
Yes ~
If your eyes are tired ...
Later to another part
It can have a bad effect ~
Yes ...
That part is too sick ...
This area is all bent
Ha ... is it really ... ??
Yes ...
I'll press it a little ~
Yes ~
Are you sick?
It hurts ;;;
How about this?
More on the left ...
Is this your word? / Yes ...
Well, excuse me, should I touch my leg?
There must be a problem for you too.
Excuse me ~
Ah ...
This area is very heavy ...
That's right ;;;
I keep heeling and working ...
Oh, that's right.
It's worse because I just left work now ~
Oh ... yes ...
More and more body inflammation
Because waste can not escape ...
Ah ...
Because it is the reception guide ...
I have to keep standing.
Oh ... you're right ~
So I have a rat on my leg.
Oh, so now it is ...
Did you wear uniforms?
Yes ... yes
Right ... I'll excuse you for the other leg for a moment ~
Pouring legs is really all women ..
Everyone's worried ...
That's really it ;;;
Now ... the swelling on the right and left is a little different ...
Well ~ I see!
Focus on these areas
Let's manage it in earnest
Could you take off your shoes? / Yes ~
Are you okay? / It's OK ~
Are you sure?
Oh ~ it's ok ~~
Do you often like these massages?
Still ... in a week ..
I think I got it once ~
Mainly shoulder or something like this?
Right ~ towards the shoulder or waist ..
Now ... towards this
Lie comfortably in the back ~
Yes ~
Are you okay with chiropractor?
Yes ... it's OK ~
Yes ~
Let's lay down ~ ~
Let's start shiatsu in this state ~
Excuse me for a moment ~
If this is the case ... it would have been really hard for me ...
Yes ... / Yes ~
Ah ... cool ... nice ...
Perhaps ..
Recently ...
As my eyes continue to fall into fatigue
I can not get my body to waste
Your body is blocked all over
I feel it is getting harder ~~
So ... your body is cold ...
Well ... I'm sure the temperature is a little low ...
Yes ..
Most women ...
You suffer a lot from hypothermia or chills.
Yes ...
It's always cold.
Well ...
It's really cool ~
That's it!
Yes ~
Also ... if you look back,
The swelling on the left and right is a little different.
Yes ... Yes ...
So this is something I'm worried about ...
Yes ...
Perhaps ... Inside the groin ...
Twisted globally
It may not work well for waste in the body ...
Yes ..
I'll just press down ...
Please tell me if you are sick
You may have some pain.
It's a little ... sick.
How do you feel ...?
Yes ~
You can barely tolerate it
Do not you feel good?
That's right ~ I'm feeling better ~
Could not circulate globally
There's definitely a place for this pain
Yes ..
Waist side too
Press ...
I feel like I'm getting worse ....
Let's go into some more detail?
Yes ~
Now .. here
Yes ..
Turn your left arm over here and turn yourself.
Yes, that's right
Take your legs to this side
Good ~!
I feel relaxed ...
May be a little painful!
Yes ..
It's hurting because I turn it like this ...
You have to have a little patience ~
That's what's good for you
For sure ...
He is a person who is working hard at his job ...
I think my body is sick and I'm passing though.
I do not like it ...
So now, let's do the other side too?
Yes ~ Good ~
Now ... spread your leg straight down this way ~
You can open it ~ Good ~
Ah ... is not it inconvenient?
Yes ~ It's OK ~
Yes ~ I will press down slowly ~
Yes ..
Are not you sick?
A little ... I feel sick ...
Is that so?
So lightly ... I'll keep stretching and continue ~
Except your strength on your body ~
Glance over at the other side of the light and
Slowly breathe and take off your strength
Good ... good ~~
Spit out your breathing power ~
I am doing very well ~ Yes ~
Now ~
Okay ~ Okay ~
Let's continue like a little while ago
Yes ~
A little slow?
Ah ...
Yes ..
Are you ok?
Yes ... / Yes ~~
A ... just stay still as it is ~
I need to manage the groin area ~
Ah .. well ...
Well ... until then ..
I'm a bit embarrassed ...
Is that so? It's okay ~~
At first, everyone is a little embarrassed ~
It's okay because it's for therapeutic purposes
Yes ...
How then ...?
Your legs are fully folded up ...
You need to do this in detail, but ...
It is very helpful for the waste of body waste ~
Most women under the waist
Waste is easy to accumulate ...
If you are in control of this place, you will surely get better
Yes ~
Well ... I'm sorry ... / Oh ~ are you ok?
Too much going on ;; / Oh ... Is that so?
You should do it ...
The treatment is a little easier
So ... I'll stretch my knees up here and do some stretching
Now I'll lift my knees to the waist ~
Yes ..
Now ~
Because I have to release a little bit of hips ...
Turn it lightly this way ~
It's OK ~
I can not see it on my side ~
Let's keep it rolling ~
Your knees may be a little stiff
I'm sorry ... this is ...
It's okay - I can not see it at all
So ~
Do not worry about those parts,
Keep your body in mind ...
Now ~ Good!
This helps to relieve hips
A little inconvenient, but
Please be patient for good health
Now ~ now
I will let my legs stand alone while I keep my body.
Yes, it is!
Good ~~
Yes ~ In this state, straighten the knee joint ~
Near the calf in the soles ...
And ~
To the thigh ... I will try to discharge the body waste ~
Yes ~ Hold on ~ It's over now ~
The groin area was a little harder.
Maybe it's because of the poor circulation of waste ...
Tap and cycle ~
Ah ...
흨 ... ah .......
읔 ....
Vibrate in this way and press ...
The trembling of the body is discharged through the trembling ~
Yes ~
I'll put more pressure on you
Yes ~ Take your strength off your body ~
Now ... it will be over soon ~
Ahhhhh ...
Over there ;;;;
Extend your legs a little longer
Wow ...
Oh ..
Yes ....
Now ~ As the body temperature gets higher and higher ...
Everything is getting better ~
AH ;;;
Ahh ...
Ah .....
Well ......
How are you doing?
Do you think it's a little slow?
OK ...
Okay ...
Yes ...
Almost finished ~
Huh huh ... huh ... huh ...
Hmm ...
Hash ;;;;
It looks like your body is getting a little tired.
Ha ha ha .....
Let's go to the management of the bridge and the toe of the bridge ~
Well ...
Good ...
Let's stretch it out ~
Hahaha ...
Yes - I am now much better than my first state ~
Yes ... Now that you have figured out your body condition
I think you should be more careful about your care.
Yes ... / Yes ~~
Eat ~~ !! Today is over ~
Still
This alone is not enough ...
Forward to
Regularly ...
I think it would be nice to keep it under control ...
Now ~~ / Yes ...
Now ...
You can wake up ~
Young Cars ~~
Okay ~
Call me whenever you have questions
Now ~
It's really getting better ~
Then ...
I look forward to you again.
Yes ...
How did it go?
Yes!
Much more comfortable ~~
Ah ~~
Great!
Regularly managed ...
Would not it be better?
So ...
It's like being a good student at a junior high school
Oh ~ really ?? / Yeah ~~
Yes?
Then ...
Does he like you?
~~ ??
What are you doing?
Ah .. the image is a little ..
Why am I worried about it?
No, it's a normal place
Oh ~ yeah ??
Yes, that's right
Yes!
Then I will also
Let's go?
Yes ~~
I think it's okay ~
Really ?? / Yeah ~~
Excuse me ~
Yes ~
Thank you for visiting us again
Do you see it being done the last time
Somewhat ... Do you feel better?
Yes ~
Is that so? / Yes ~
That's very fortunate ~
So today is the day
Very special for Aoi.
I prepared the oil ~
Oil
Yes!
Improving waste emissions at once
A very special oil
So ...
I have a special underwear ~
Yes ..
Change it with this one ... / Yes ...
You'll have trouble getting oil on your clothes.
Ah ..
Yes ...
But ...
Well ... this is a little ...
Ah ..
To help maximize the efficacy of oil ...
Specially designed to minimize area ~
That's just as effective.
Ah ... but .. / ego ~ !!! Please change this to
I'll be out for a while
If you change everything, please call me again
Yes ...
Excuse me ...
I've changed everything.
Ah ~
So ~
I'll go over there and get ready
Now ~
Lie comfortably and wait
Ah ... but ... there ...
Yes ~ / Should I do this?
What do you mean?
Well ...
really ... this way ...
Should I be managed?
That's right ... but ... what's wrong with you?
Oh .. that's it ;;;
The area is too narrow ;;;
Okay
That's all to increase the efficacy of the oil.
Yes ... Is it ...
Now, do not worry ...
Lie down comfortably ...
You are in control!
Leaning ...?
Yes, head to head here
Lay down comfortably ~
First, the last time I did
Focusing on the lower half
Let's take a look at the overall improvement ~
Let's check it out ~
I'll go ahead a little bit in time!
I see some improvement in blood flow ...
Still ..
I can feel the cool aura ...
Ah ...
Yes ...
So now ... Let's try the oil once?
What kind of fragrance?
Yes ~
It is the incense of a particular plant from the South American Amazon
You can think of it as a very special oil -
Let's play!
First ... Apply on the surface of the body ...
Impressing the skin inside ...
Relieves inflammation ... increases blood flow ~
Well ... um ....
There ...
It's a bit cold. I feel strange ...
It's OK ~
Just by spreading and spreading
It works because ~
You have to apply it properly
Habits .....
Well ......
Uh huh ....
Let me change my posture a bit
Now ~ Turn it to the side like the first number ~
Lie down ~
Yes ~~
Ah ... Wait ... Hey ...
It's OK ~
Many people receive this procedure ~
Now ~
Ah ... but ... it's too shabby ... shy ;;;
That's what I did last time.
Do not worry ~
Well ...
Yes ....
Wait ...
No ...
Do not worry ...
Wait ... still ...
Many people do this procedure
There ... stop it ;;;
What's the problem?
You had the same procedure last time ...
But ... this is ...
It's not just a massage ...
I mean it, but ...
The fact is ... I came expecting it quietly ...
I know! ~
So I do this ...
You touch me here ...
Ah ..
Wait ... Ha ...
Sleep ... Hang on ...
Strengthen your strength ~
AH ;;;
I know ... well ...
I've been doing this job for a long time ...
Tell me what you want ....
Stop ...
Now ... take your strength off ~~
Hash ;;;;;
Ah ... 읔 ... 핰 .... no ;;;
Stop ...
Wow ;;;
huh !!!! ;;; Huh ;;;;
Madam ...
Please ... stop ;;;
Ah ... no ;;;
Madam ...
Do not do this ...
Do not give up.
That's all for the health of your body.
Still ...
Now ~
Cause Your Body
Then I'll take it off.
Wait ... Stop !;
Hmm ~~
Stop it ... there you go ;;;
That's the nipple. / Yeah ~ ??
I need to apply oil properly ...
No ...
That's a nipple ;;;
Ah ~~
I know
Are you happy?
Here too
Give it to me ...
Now ... open your legs on both sides ...
...
Wait ... What are you doing ;;;
How are you? Kill?
Ohhorat ~~ lick lick 쫩쫩 쫩쫩
Sounds good ~ Do not take it if you like it
Licking
Can I just suck it with my tongue?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Wait ... Stop ... I ...
Do you really want to quit?
No ... There's no way to manage it ;;;
Now ...
That's ...
How do the recipients
It's just a matter of feeling ...
Oh .. wait .... ;;;
Eat ~~
I'll make you feel better
Licking
Listen to your ass!
Well ~ wow ~~
Your ass is really killing me.
Now ~ So
I'll keep you feeling better
Wait ... go ;;;;
Are you feeling already?
We will continue to do so ~
More ...
I'm waiting for a better step ...
No ...
Stop ..
Please ...
This time, you can use this ~
Let's go cheerfully ~
Yes .. ?? Wait ;;
That's just ...
It's okay ... ma'am ~~
Oh, this is not it ;; Really ...
흨 .... white .....
Would that be okay?
Do not stop here ... ??
Madam ...
Disclaimer ~
Do not worry at all
You want to be nice ~ ??
For health ...
Let's work together ....
otherwise ~~~
Hmm .... 핰 ...
No ,;;
Not this ...
Should I still do it?
Now, let's get it right here.
I'll use it ~ / Yes ???
Wait ;;;
Sleep ...
Stay still ~
Is it okay to stop really?
Ah ... 앜앜 .....
What are you going to do .... ??
Madam ~~~~
Wait ...
What are you going to do? Wait! Stop it !!!
Is it okay to stop really ... ??
...
Now ..
Strength ...
Hmm ...
I know everything. ~~ / Wait .;
Wait ... No ;;;
Yum ????
Very nice ~~
Wait ... 읔 .... 핰 ..... no ... !!
Uhh 핰 ;;; Awfully 뗴 .... ;; Fuck ㄸ ;;;;
I am putting in
읏 ... again ....
Yes ... ;;
Deprecate ;;;
Wait ;;;
I still do not have enough senses ...
Well ... then. I'll put it deeper ~
Wow; No ;;;;
읏 ... again ...
I have been in a mess ....
Wow ... no way ;;
Swarms ;;;
How about you ???
I know everything
It's cheaper ...
I'll keep putting it back
What? Oh ~~
Because there is no more rebellion ...
You feel so much better ...
Oh! No...!!!
Ah ... when you are at work ;;;
Wow;
Ahh ...
Let's put it a little deeper ~ ~
Wait ;; No;;; What are you going to do ?;
Oh ... no ;;;
Aha 앜 ;;;;
Ah !!! Oh, no;; No!
Uh-huh ;; 읔 !!!!
It keeps flowing down. ~~
Do you know?
Aw ,; No ;;;
Wow; Dame Yame !!!!
Do you really want to stop it?
Is it okay to stop now?
If you really want to stop ...
You can leave it off ~~
Madam ...
But honestly ...
What do you want to say?
I thought you would be very happy ...
Come on !?
Do you feel it's getting tighter now?
Look here ...
Take a look at this ....
Please stop now .... ;;;
So ~
I ...
Now I need to take a break ...
It's really nice ..
Ah !!!
Now ~
Cause Your Body
Wait a minute ... ah ... 앜 ...
Now ...
This time ...
Load your weight
no ;; No;;;
I can not go now ...
Now ~~
Move yourself by yourself
Now ~~~
no more ;;; No ;;;
If so ...
If you stop here ...
I regret it ...
Now ~
Because I set it up correctly.
Turn your back on yourself ~
Otherwise ~~
Now ... open your leg ~
Awesome !!!
Ah !!!
Just .......
Click
<font color="
Then ...
Click
You ...
At TechCom's Information Desk
I was told to see the receptionist ...
Yes? How does it ...?
First ...
You used it when you wrote the questionnaire. ~~
Ah ...
Well ....
Wait ... photos now ... ??
Also in our store ...
Techcom's customers are also visiting a lot ...
At your company's information desk ...
If you are told you are doing this ...
I ...
What do you think?
Customer ~~
From now on ...
Please be my wife ...
Otherwise ...
Previous photo ...
For those customers ...
Do you know?
Then ..
Please come again ... I will be waiting ~~
Um ...
I'm dying ~~
What's up?
Why?
You do not look well ...
Ah ..
The ...
I ...
It was a tough day ...
Ah ~
So ...
Even if I went to my house ...
Then ...
Tomorrow I'll go to the station?
Yes ...
Well ....
I recently had a little bit of trouble with it ....
Would you like to go to the congestion company?
The house seems to have a good reputation around it too ...
and .......
Write ...
I wish I had a massage too ...
Your mind will be comforted ...
There ..
Please erase it ... !!
Yes ...
Of course, we should erase it.
Your body is properly ..
Well done ...
You know?
This time ..
What to manage ...
I was stuck because of the tension at the reception ...
Here in the upper body and lower body ...
It's hard, really ...
h .... hehe ... h ...
Let's get it right.
Now ..
Let's get started happily ~
Exercise your body ...
Feel Relaxed ...
Okora ... too ...
This also causes shoulder stiffness
Because it's so big and amazing ...
Now ..
You have to lose your strength ...
You know it?
Wife ...
Ohora ~~~
This is server-side ...
If you really did not want to do it.
Not so far ...
Also ... I have come to expect a lot.
Usually my boyfriend does not feel this way.
Have you ever felt so happy ... ??
Guys ...
Do you really love it?
Yes ..
Oho ~~
Now ~~
I'm betraying ...
This nipple is ...
fact ..
I can not help it ...
Your body is ... honest.
Feeling good?
Yes ... if you feel better ...
Say you're happy.
I do not feel ....
Is that so?
Got it ~
Then ..
I think it would be nice to have a stronger stimulus ...
Is it here ...
Please feel free to tell me when you feel better
Too wet ...
Compared to saying that it does not feel ... considerably ...
This is ...
Then what? ??
Suddenly ... did your body's sensitivity go up? ???
Ah ...
Here ...
It's empty ...
More and more ...
Sounds good ...
Shy and embarrassed ...
Oh ... no .;;;;
How about feeling here?
I do not feel it. Did not I ... ??
Wow ~
Now ... Lie down ...
Do not tolerate ...
Great for your body ...
Wife ...
Lie down -
Yes?
Well, this time ...
I will go into the procedure using the machine.
No ...
Now ... please wait ~~
Will you let me have a bunch of them?
Ah ... no ;; No;; No;; No ;;;
Can you still tolerate it?
Now ~
Well ... it still seems to be lacking ~~
Let's put it on!
what?
옼 !!!
It's been a long time since I started! Dash!
Wow !!!!
That's right ...
...
Hmmm ... ~
It's coming up now ...
Ohhara ~~
I still have my heart ...
Now, the last is ~~
Fountain Top
No ;;;
Ah ~~
The pit hole is completely wetted until this ..
I was in a good mood ~ ~ ??
Do not see ...
Even if you have a boyfriend ...
Too bad ... lewd.
Do not you think I'm sorry?
You can not feel this feeling with your boyfriend?
Are you okay? Even if you feel like this ...
You had a lot of trouble ~~
I did a great job ~
Master ...
Somewhat ..
I do not seem to be feeling all day today ...
What's up?
Not ...
I ... I feel so cold ...
Yes ... ??
Are you okay? / Yes!
Thanks
I also have ~ ~
I thought there was a man problem ...
How are you? ~ Ho Ho ~
I was worried about what to do ...
TechComm ..
There are many guests coming here ...
Receptionist ..
If you know you're doing this ...
Would you be surprised?
I feel really good ... ??
I feel so nervous ...
So ... did you yell that the hole is good?
Goodbye ~~
Hello ~
Today ... I have some time ~
I'm going to the congestion company ~
Today ... I will not go ..
?
But ...
You recently wanted to go on
It's annoying to visit ....
Oh ...
Oh ....
Well ... that's ...
That's not true ~~
Then ...
I'll prepare breakfast
Ah ~~
Yes!
Donkey ~~~
Yes ~
Hello ~
Excuse me for a moment ~~
Why are you here .... ??
please !!!
Go back ...
Ah ~ !!
Are you coming?
Oh ... I'm sorry ~~
Yes ...
Your boyfriend ...
Ask for a travel massage ..
Well ...
Here's a look at the store homepage ..
It's definitely a travel massage plus posting
You are ~!
You told me that it was too annoying to go there before
Ah ~
Now, come in here ~ ~
Do you mind? / Yeah ~ !! It's okay ~~ !!
I'll excuse you for a moment ~ / Yeah ~~ !!
How about?
Feeling good?
Yes!
There ..
If you do not mind ~
I also recently had a neck and a shoulder
It's pretty stiff and uncomfortable ...
Oh ... Is that it?
Later ...
Can I take a look at my body?
Yes ~ Sure!
Oh, really? / Sure ~
Ah ~
So ~
I ...
I'll be over there ~
Yes ~
Thank you
Yes.
Resting ~
There ..
Now ... you can stop.
That's a really good boyfriend ...
Horror ...
Recently ... Since you did not visit ...
It's pretty much here and there ...
That was hard for me .. ??
What?
I'll release it slowly.
Yes ...
and ..
I'll give you a special service.
In many ways ...
If you hear a sound ...
I'm going to go crazy ..
To my boyfriend ...
Do you know?
More precise ...
I should release it slowly.
Does not it hurt? Here it is ??
It's a lot harder ...
Let me relax slowly.
Let's get started.
If you do not mind it, you can also make a sound ~
It's going to be bad ...
If you do not manage your waistline ...
Power out your body ~
(Aoi ~ !!)
How about?
Huck ..
Yes!
Are you in a massage?
Yes ...
Very good ..
Ah ~ Really ??
Ah ... but ...
My girlfriend is at the reception desk ...
Yes ~~
My feet are often swollen and sore ...
That's right ~
Not only the bridge but also the dorsal ..
The waist is also very bad ...
Oh ... surely that's it .. ??
Yes ~~
Oh ... I'm sorry, but as smooth as possible ..
It hurts me ~
Please take care of yourself
Of course!
I'll try to solve the bad area properly
Definitely ~~
So ~~
Thank you very much ~~
Yes ~~
No ;;;;
I got so wet ...
What are you going to do?
I want to make you feel good
Now ~
Do not do this ;;
Look at this ...
Well, whatever you say ...
You're finally enjoying it ...
Ohorat !! ~
I'm afraid ;;;
Stop it ...
Just ... just enjoy
Would you mind? Do you even sound like that ... ??
You should also lick your breasts ...
Now ~
Extend this way ...
Is everything okay? There's a boyfriend over there ...
Here ... Is it all right?
So ...
How about?
OK?
So ... Soaked up ...
Give me ..
AO or more ...
Really .. to my boyfriend ..
Let me show you ~ ~
Stop ..
Wait ;;;
I'll kill you from your ass ...
I'll get you some more ...
Come on ~~
Here ... I want to put it on my ass ... ??
I know everything!
So ...
No ...
No ;; / I want to put it on my ass?
This ..
Are you ok?
I would like this ...
Horror ...
No ...
No, cosplay does not stop ...
Now ... / Awesome .. ;;
no ;;; / So ...
Ah ... went in ...
Even though my boyfriend is there,
Let's do it right ..
Now ..
Extend your ass ...
No ...
Want more?
Yes ...
I will push you more ...
In front of her boyfriend ..
I feel great ...
It's very ... nigger ~~
Want to go a little further ???
Inhal ;;;
Oh fuck ...
AO or better ..
Grab yourself and suck it ~
Quickly ...
You know it!
Ah ... Joe ..
Over and over
Stick out your ass! ~
Would that be okay?
Ahaha 핰 ....
Also ... will you kill me?
AO or better ..
Please raise your body ~~
No ;;
Have not you ... yet?
Oh ... no ... please ;;;
If you do not mind ... I'll go with you ??
Okay ~~
OK ;;
Go ...
Go !;;;
I think it's rice !!!
Ah ~~ fuck! !!!
AO or better ..
Like good? ??
Oh!
Hight .. Atelier .. Iki 죶
Underwear!
Wow !!!
AO or better ..
Please suck it clean.
You were happy?
Next ...
See you again.
AO or more
Be careful not to question your boyfriend ~
Would that be so? ???
I want to put it on my ass ... ??
Shout ...
Wow!
Uh ..
Where does it hurt?
Ah ...
Sorry ..
Nothing.
Ah ..
Yes ...
Please come to the next guest ~!
Yes ..
I'm sorry.
You've waited a long time ...
Welcome ...
AO or better ..
What are you doing today?
Now ...
Let's have a look at ~
Then ...
Shall I start a massage?
Let's lay down ...
Why?
I think it's pretty nervous.
To be so scared ...
There ...
Please ...
Lower body ..
Please manage your lower body.
What do you mean?
Otherwise ...
So ...
If you have a choice ...
Tell me right away.
If you do not tell ...
I do not know ...
There ...
Put your hand and touch it ...
Direct ...
So ...
Yes ...
That's it!
Aha ~ ~ really kill you ~ ~
What is the procedure?
Want to receive?
Now ~
Let me know right away
Come here ...
You do not have to be ashamed .... ??
Here ...
Would you like me to touch it?
There ...
Massage it there ...
I know!
Is this also true?
How many .. Note I'm here ...
You already have underwear ...
You're sticky wet.
Do this?
Yes ...
I feel good ...
Now ..
What you want ...
Tell me more ...
What do you want to be?
Yes ...
I do not speak ...
Well, I see!
If so, ~
Just like this ... Massage ...
Let's get started ~
Talk to yourself.
What do you want to be ....
...
Suck .. suck ..
Yes, sir.
Puppies
It's really a big hit .;
So delicious ...
Pooh Saw !!!
Now ... turn it to the side ~
Lift your buttocks and show them
Write and ~~
Uh-oh!
Ok ...
I can suck it well ...
Squeeze into your face ...
Ohhh ... go ...
Go ... !!
it .. koo ;;;
For a boyfriend ...
Could not be satisfied?
Stolen ... It's too bad ...
This ...
Do you want to use it?
I feel like I'm having a bitchy year ...
Ah ~~
Why stop?
This oil ...
Did not I miss you?
AO or more ... I put this in my mouth ~
Alaska .....
Too violent ;;;
Okay ... stick out your tongue ...
You are doing well ..
Want to put it?
Well,
AO or better ..
If you want to put it in, please try a little more aggressively.
Want it?
Yes ...
Now ..
Open your legs.
Hey ... it's very annoying ...
Oh ... just like you want more ..
Try to open up more.
If you do not tell us correctly ...
I might not know it well ~
Watch it ...
Well ... guess ~~
Yes ...
I can not stand it ;;;
If you do not tell me right ...
It'll be like this forever
Well ... 얔얔 ;;;
Please put it .... ;;
I do not like ...
Black ... a little cock ...
Where to go ~~
Go to my page ...
What do you mean?
Eat ~~
Oh ... the real ones have put them in themselves ~ ~
I should get drunk ~~
I have a pussy like this ~~
Would you like to put it deeper?
Now ~
Ahh ah ah ah ahh Ikku!
Bigger ~~~
Did you miss that?
Yes!
How about it?
What about my cock?
Now I can shake myself a little bit.
Ah ;; No ;;
Ah ;; Gimochi ...
Ah ;;; Good ;;;;
Now turn your hips to this side
Turn it back ...
Ah !!! No!
I do not think it will fade out ;;;
Ah ;;
Ah ;; I ... k ;;;
Yes, it is ...
Aaikku ..
Lie next to your side.
...
May I put it?
Yes!
Oh! Good
Ahhh ;; Really ... crazy ;;
I love to suck it ~ ~
Akuikuikutsu
Ahh Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah
really ;; Good ...
Ome ...
Mom ...
Are you satisfied with it?
Yes?
Now, what should I do now?
Talk to me ...
How you feel now ...
god ;;
Now ;;;
More ..
Stronger?
I do not think I will ...
Ah ;;; I am mad ;;;
I have to hurry a little bit ~~
Other guests may come to you ~
Hiring .....
Are you feeling a little?
Ah !!!
Can I pick it up straight?
Yes ....
Come closer to here
Please insert ...
What is it?
Totally ... I'm crazy ;;;
Where will it go?
Where you like ....
I'll take it ...
On a pretty face that I only saw on my cell phone ...
Okay?
Namet ~ It's a joke !!!!
Ahhhhhhhh !!!!
Awesome !!!!!
Aye ;;;;;
Over and over
And still practice
If you want to ... whenever ~ ~
Please come to ~
Visiting your store ...
I'll be waiting ...
Starring
Aoi
Hangul subtitles production
- Cool President -