Subtitles by EroJapanese.com
Copyright 2018
Somewhere in Tokyo
We're here.
We're here? Where are we?
This is a parking area in Tokyo.
What? Is it close to the studio?
- The studio isn't around here.
- What do you mean?!
- We're not going to the studio today?
- Actually, today....
We've been running a campaign for fans who wish you could visit their homes.
- Fans' homes?
- That was the advertisement.
As a result, there were so many people who applied.
In this occassion we asked Rion's fans to take part in the shooting of a video. We received a huge reply. Thank you very much!!
They all want you to visit their homes.
Are you serious? We're going to a fan's home right now?
- Yes.
So now we're at a parking area near the first fan.
This is all true.
- I've never been to a fan's home before.
- It would be weird if you did!
It would be pointless just to go to their homes.
So you're going to be leased to the fan for 30 minutes today.
You can lease Rion for 30 minutes!!
- It's just a lease so you'll have to be returned to us.
- Of course, but it's scary. Is it safe?
That's something I'm worried about too. They can do whatever they want for 30 minutes.
- Anything's ok?
- Yes, anything except marrying you.
- I'm getting worried.
- But your fans are all nice people, right?
- Well yes, but...
- By the way, what kind of people are your fans?
I think people who likes big boobs?
- Boob fetishists?
- Yeah.
- That's nice.
- Am I going in these clothes? - Yes.
Isn't this too much?
- Do you think it's too provocative? - Yeah.
But these fans are all novices.
So we have to get them going.
- Get them going?
- They aren't going to make a move.
I will assist you.
Are you serious?
Would that be fine?
- Yes.
- Then you will...
be on lease with the fan for 30 minutes.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
I'm going to go out a bit so wait here.
- What? Are you serious?
- Of course.
- For real?
- Of course it's for real.
- I didn't know about this at all.
- This is that first time I told you.
- It's up to you if this can be released of not.
- No pressure at all then.
This is for real. It's going to start soon. I'm counting on you.
First fan
- Rion-chan.
- Yes.
- This is the first fan's home.
To be honest...
we don't know what kind of person he is and what he wants to do.
- I have no idea myself.
- I'm so nervous.- Somehow...
I've managed to get something this person wants...
- so I will give it to you. - Ok.
- What does it say?
"I want to be sent to heaven with Rion-chan's boobs. Thanks."
- What does that mean?
- No idea.
Like I said, we're here already so...
you're going to go inside...
Actually, today...
- he doesn't know you're coming.
- You haven't told him?!
We already told this fan we would check his room!!
The staff is going to check his room first.
- That's what we told him and he's standing by.
- Are you sure this is ok? - I don't know.
I'll be filming from a few feet away.
Could you ring the bell and explain him the situation?
- Tell him you'll be leased for 30 minutes.
- Sure.
- I'll do it.
- Good luck.
I'll be over here. Ring the bell.
- It says that the bell is out of order.
- Are you serious?
It says please knock.
Oh yeah. I can't believe it.
Please knock. I'll be hiding over here.
- If he's fine with everything, let me know. Good luck.
- Thanks.
Hello, I'm Rion. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- So today...
I'm being leased to you for 30 minutes, is that fine?
- Leased?
- Yes.
- Is this a bad time?
- No, I don't mean that...
- I wasn't expecting you.
- Sorry about this.
- Is this ok? - I guess.
- Please hold on.
- He's ok with it.
- Ok?
You sent an application, right?
- Yes.
- The assistant director told you we need to check your room first.
- Yes, I got that message.
- So to save time, I brought Rion with me.
Can we come in? It's cold out here.
Sorry for this interruption. Excuse me
Are you ok?
Excuse me.
I don't have much in here.
Please come here.
- Can I sit down?
- If you want.
That's a nice chair.
I've had it for 5 years.
- It looks old.
- Are you ok? - Yeah.
- Could you sit next to her?
- What do you think? She's the real girl.
- I can see a little bit from over here.
- I'm sorry.
- I knew it, you love tits!
- Oh yes.
- Show him a bit more.
- What do you think of this?
- I've seen them on DVD.
What do you like about Rion?
Definitely her boobs. They're the best.
Fine... You wrote in your application that...
- What did he write?
- You want to go to heaven.
- What did you mean by that?
- I don't really know.
I was aroused when I was writing it.
I didn't expect I'd see you for real.
Rion told you already but she's all yours for 30 minutes today.
You can do whatever you want.
- It's all good.
- Anything goes.
Leasing Rion for 30 minutes!!
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- I can do anything?
- Anything except marry her.
I want to see your tits more.
- G cup, aren't they?
- Yes.
That's amazing.
- You're cute and pretty.
- I'm embarrassed.
- She's so nice.
- She really is.
- I can do anything?
- Basically, yes.
- Can I go ahead?
- Sure.
- They're heavy.
- Yeah.
Can I squeeze them?
I love them.
- Do you love tits?
- Yes, I think about tits a lot.
- When I jerk off on this chair, I think about them.
- Oh really?
Rion-chan? He's touching you in that chair that he sits in when he jerks off watching your DVDs.
- It's amazing.
- Yeah.
- Can I get closer?
- Yes.
- You have nice tits.
- Thanks.
Do you want to take her clothes off... so you can see her better?
You can if you want.
- Can I do that?
- Yeah, it's already been 10 minutes. - Yeah.
The bed is over there. Come here.
Could you lie down?
- On here?
- What do you want me to do?
- Can I have more fun?
Is this fine?
It smells nice.
- Your glasses are wonky.
- I want to see them.
My tits? I'll take this off.
- So that he can go to heaven.
- Of course.
- They're so pretty.
- Thanks.
- What do you think?
- White underwear...
- Could you take off your bra?
- You want me to take off my bra?
He's in heaven.
This is like heaven.
- Can I come closer?
- Sure.
- Can I lick it?
Your nipples are hard.
This feels good.
I love them.
- Can I do this too?
- Sure.
This is like heaven.
Your tits are amazing.
- Do you like tits?
- I love them.
- I want to do this forever.
- Forever?
- Are your glasses ok?
- I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
I love your tits so much.
You have 15 minutes left.
I'm getting hard. I'm horny.
Can I put my cock between your tits?
Can I take my cock out?
Do you want me to be lying on the bed?
Rion, why don't you show him the saint-like boobjob?
You're really big! Wow!
Look how big he is!
- What position is good?
- You should lie down.
Excuse me.
Could you lift your hips?
- How's this?
- This is the real thing.
- They're so soft.
- Oh really?
- Do you think you can go to heaven?
- I'm already there.
It feels so good. You're good at it.
I want you to jerk me off so much.
- That's so good.
- Like this?
If you cum, that will be the end of it.
- Oh no.
- Did you nearly cum?
- You're in heaven.
- I don't want to cum yet.
Could you use your mouth?
I'll use my mouth.
That's too much.
- That's too much.
- Oh really?
- Could you check what he wants to do?
- What would you like to do?
I want to fuck you and go to heaven.
- Sure.
- Really?
I'm going to put a condom on.
- You're so big so it's difficult.
- Could you do it yourself?
- You really have a huge cock.
- Yes.
Such a big penis.
Is this good?
This is so good.
Can I touch you?
- Can I keep touching you?
- Sure.
I'm going to ride you.
It's so good.
- How's that?
- I love it.
Your tits are jiggling so much.
Please look at me more.
Oh my god, this is amazing.
It's so good.
You really love tits, don't' you?
- He's using both hands to squeeze your boob.
- Her tits are too big for one hand.
- Two hands are just right.
- Oh really?
- Can I do more?
- He wants it in his mouth.
- It feels so good.
- Me too.
Oh my god.
You really like tits, don't you?
- Can we change positions?
- From behind?
Rion-chan, could you face this way?
- How's his cock?
- It's so big.
And hard, so makes me feel good.
It feels amazing.
- Are you ok?
- Yeah.
It feels so good.
I love it.
- So you want to try the missionary position?
- I do.
I'll put some more lube on.
It's getting hot.
Please, pull out when you feel like cumming.
Rion will take the condom off.
Tell us when you're about to cum.
It feels so good.
- Do you like it?
- I do.
It's so good.
I love it.
Could you touch my nipples?
- It feels so good.
- You like that?
Your nipples are hard.
I'm getting close.
Are you close?
Oh my god.
It's all over your hands.
- Wow, that's a lot of cum.
- I know!
That looks so thick.
- I'm sorry, are you ok?
Yes. - Thank you very much.
- Do you have some tissue?
- Oh, it's right there.
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry, Rion will clean you up.
You don't have to wipe your cock.
- How was that?
- It felt heavenly.
- Sorry, I'm all out of energy.
- Did you go to heaven? - Yeah.
I'm glad you did.
- I really did. - How did you like her tits?
- It was the best.
- Can I touch them one last time?
- Sure - Thanks so much!
- Thank you.
Can she use your shower?
Let's go over here.
Rion-chan... Come over here.
- That was amazing.
- I was surprised.
He's all frozen.
Your tits were amazing.
He couldn't help himself.
I'm glad he went to heaven.
Let's just use his shower and move on to the next fan.
Could you take us to the shower?
- His cock was huge.
- Yeah, I was surprised.
Noobies are scary.
- But he was nice. Nice face and personality.
- Yeah.
Let's go to the shower.
Second fan
Rion-chan.
This is the second fan. We're in front of his house.
It's amazing here.
Yeah, it feels old.
Like before, could you ring the bell and explain him everything?
- Sure.
- If the first thing he sees is a camera, it's going to be too much for him.
It's better to explain it first, so I'll be out of your way.
I'll be over here so that he doesn't notice.
Go ahead.
Oh hello. I'm Rion.
I'm on a lease to you for 30 minutes. Do you have time?
30 minutes... No?
- Are you alone? Is the crew around?
- Yeah, he's over there.
- I'm sorry.
- Hello.
You applied, right?
- It's been a while.
- Today...
the assistant director contacted you to check your room first.
- Oh yes, but I thought it was a joke.
- So we brought Rion with us.
Can we go in? We may be disturbing your neighbors.
Excuse me.
Could she sit there?
Can Rion sit there?
Could she sit in the back?
Sorry for coming like this.
Rion is yours for 30 minutes.
You can do whatever you want.
Are you confused?
Yes, 30 minutes.
We decided to film today.
Sorry for not telling your earlier.
I thought that phone call was a joke or something.
Rion is here now.
I'm yours for 30 minutes. Is there something you want to do?
Let me think.
I have some clothes I'd like you to wear.
I'm not sure if you'd like it.
What do you mean?
Could you come here?
Is it ok to go over this room? Thanks.
I've had this for a long time.
I sometimes wash it.
Uniform? You want me to wear a uniform?
- You never wear uniforms in your videos.
- You're right.
Could you wear it for me?
I washed it yesterday.
I didn't want to be rude and make you wear dirty clothes.
You want her to wear the uniform?
Like you're a student.
Could she change here?
- Could you let us know when you're finished changing?
- Got it.
- We'll be waiting here. We didn't expect this.
This is a first.
Let us know when you're ready.
She changed into the sailor uniform.
- That's amazing.
- I'm so nervous.
- Do you like tits?
- I really love them.
Do you want her to wear a bra under the uniform?
Later... Hm... I don't know.
- It's nice to go bra-less actually.
- Rion...
- could you remove your bra?
- Sure.
- Is that acceptable?
- Yeah, of course.
I'm getting excited.
I'll check.
- Is she a J cup?
- Yes, she is.
I've washed it many times so it might be too small.
10 minutes later...
- I think she's still changing.
- Were you surprised that we came without notice?
- I was.
- What do you think of her?
- We're going to open the door.
- Are you ready?
Why are you hiding?
- It's showing. I'm embarrassed.
- Show us!
I'm so embarrassed.
That's amazing.
I didn't think it was so small.
- I can do anything, right?
- Yeah, within 30 minutes.
- I like groping in the train.
- I see.
I love this... Could you pretend you're on the train?
- Like this. Hold on to the handle?
- Ok.
Oh my god.
They're so soft.
This is really detailed.
- Were your tits this big when you were a student?
- Yeah, they were.
Oh my god.
- You never wear uniforms at all.
- No, I don't.
- This is rare.
- It really is rare.
- Are you embarrassed?
- I am.
- Can I lick?
- Yeah.
- I can lick, right?
- Yes.
Could you put your tits on my head?
Could you rub it?
They're real.
One by one.
Like this?
Put them on me.
Yes...
- I'm so hard.
- You really are hard.
You need to hold on to the handle.
- I can't resist anymore. Can I....
- Yes, within 30 minutes.
- Can I grind myself against you?
- Yes.
Wow. It's so detailed. I love it.
I love your tits more than your ass.
- I don't know. - You can do whatever.
- I think your tits are better.
Could you rub your tits?
You don't have to rush.
- We're in the train.
- Yeah.
We're fucking in the train.
The train is completely empty.
- Could you spit on my cock?
- Sure.
Could you rub your tits on my cock?
It's so good.
How is it? What do you think of her tits?
I'm so glad I applied.
It's been 20 minutes. What do you want to do for the next 10 minutes?
- What shall I do? I can do anything?
- Sure.
- Your cunt. I want to visit your cunt.
- Visit?!
- Here you are.
- Ok.
I'm going to put a condom on your cock.
Oh my god.
Is it ok if I put lube on your cock?
My cock is hard.
Can I fuck you from behind?
Standing and from the back? That's impressive.
Here? Are you ready?
- Could you bend over? Is it in?
- Yes, it is.
Oh my god.
Could you bend over a bit more?
You don't have to strain too much.
Could you face this way?
Do you want to hold on to here?
You can go on the floor if you want?
I'm sorry... Are you fine?
- I'm so turned on.
- That's impressive.
Rion-chan, this is amazing.
He's so energetic.
- You're fucking her so good.
- Look this way.
Can you go on top? I'm getting tired.
I'm going to put more lube on.
I want to see your tits while we fuck.
- Can I see my cock inside you?
- Do you want to see?
Can you see it?
Let's fuck like this.
- Let's not pull out.
- Let's not.
That's amazing. I'm impressed.
You have so much energy.
You've got so much energy.
Rion-chan... do you like it?
Did you cum?
Oh yes.
He came.
You came.
You came so much.
- It surprised me.
- I'm sorry.
You didn't warn me.
That's too bad.
Do you have some tissue?
Can we borrow some tissue?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Rion-chan, could you clean him up?
- What?
- I'll clean you up.
How was it?
The real one is amazing.
- I'm glad.
- I want to see you again on the train.
Rion-chan... say thank you and let's go.
- Thank you. - Me too.
- Let's shake hands.
- Please support me for a long time.
- Of course.
Let's go.
Could she use your shower?
Come here.
- It was amazing.
- He had a whole scenario planned.
Let's get out of here.
Third fan
This is the third fan's home.
Your fans are really interesting.
Yes, they are all very unique.
- They all love big tits.
- Yeah, I'm surprised.
- The guy just now, he had a uniform ready.
- I was so surprised,
That was unexpected.
The next guy doesn't know you're coming either.
He thinks staff is coming to see the room.
So ring the bell and tell him that you're here on a lease
- and surprise him. I'll be hiding over here.
- Yes.
Press the bell. Good luck.
- Hello.
- Oh Rion-chan!
We arrive unannounced
I'm here for 30 minutes on a lease. Do you have time?
I'm sorry, I heard the assistant director was coming...
Can I come in?
Can we come in?
Are you filming?
We will explain inside. Is that ok?
- Let's go in.
- Yes, thank you.
- Excuse me.
- I cleaned up because I was told the assistant director would come.
Do you want to sit on that sofa?
Please sit next to her.
- What do you think? She's the real Rion.
- Why is this happening?
Rion-chan, could you read this to him?
"I'm your biggest fan. If possible, I'd like to watch your DVD and...
receive a boobjob.
Please, make my dream come true. Let's watch your DVD together."
- Do you remember submitting that application?
- That was ages ago.
We came to make your dream come true.
- Are you serious?
- But as Rion said before...
we only have 30 minutes. So Rion is yours for 30 minutes.
Are you sure? I'm so surprised.
- Do you have her DVDs?
- Yeah, of course.
- I have most of them.
- Which one if your favorite?
I think it's in the DVD player.
- Yeah, it's in the player.
- Show us.
- How many times have you jerked off watching it?
- I've lost count.
- Do you want to watch this DVD with her?
- Yes, I think so.
- Could you play it?
- Rion-chan...
- Yes?
- Your DVDs... do you watch them?
- No.
Please watch it with him.
It's so embarrassing.
Oh my god, this is so embarrassing. Watch together?
- Do you jerk off watching this?
- Yeah, this is my favorite.
- I play the DVD from this scene.
- This scene?
- Do you want to see her tits?
- Yeah.
He says he wants to see.
Sure.
You can see but only for 30 minutes.
You've got 25 minutes left.
Why don't you take it off?
- Do you like boobjobs?
- I love them.
- You love them?
- I love them so much.
Out of all the porn actresses, you have the best.
The shape and size are perfect and you're cute.
"My tits are the best," you're thinking that, aren't you?
Rion-chan.
- This is the ultimate double-team so can you stand next to the TV?
- Are you serious?
What do you think?
What do you think of this?
- This is amazing.
- I'm so embarrassed.
Are you happy now?
What do you want to do?
- Can I touch them? - Sure.
- Could you sit over there
on that sofa?
- Could you turn off the DVD because it's distracting?
- Can I keep it on?
Do you want to keep it on?
Do whatever you want.
- Can I touch?
- Sure.
Can I look from the bottom?
- How do you like them?
- They're the best.
- Can I?
- Sure.
It turns me on so much.
- This is amazing. The DVD is on in the background.
- It's so embarrassing.
It's not the same feeling the weight of your tits. It's not like watching the DVD.
- Do you think so? Which do you like more?
- I like the real one.
Can you slap me with your tits?
Like this?
- You like that?
- I love it.
It turns me on. My dream is coming true.
What? Boobjob?
I applied so that I could get a boobjob.
Do you want to? Sure, go ahead.
He's cumming on the DVD.
I want to watch it and get a boobjob.
I've jerked off watching this so many times.
Boobjob?
- You've only got 15 minutes left.
- Oh really?
Can I turn the volume down?
She's really go in for it in the DVD.
It's amazing.
- What shall I do?
- Could you take off your clothes?
Please take them off.
- Are you already hard?
- Yeah, I'm really turned on.
Oh yes, you are. I can see your bulge.
Could you strip naked?
Sorry, I'm a bit chubby.
Please, take off your underwear.
It's so big!
It looks really thick.
What shall we do? Could you lie down there?
Your head on this side.
You can lie back. Rion will take care of the rest.
Could you place your hips on my lap?
Can you come closer?
- What do you think?
- It feels amazing.
- It's so good.
- Oh really? Do you like it?
It's so good.
Do you want use some lube?
- Do you have it?
- Yeah.
I'm going to put some on.
- Rion-chan is touching my cock.
- Are you surprised?
- What are you thinking?
- It's like a dream.
It's the real Rion.
She's so cute.
That's amazing.
That's what I watch all the time. Press it on your nipples.
- Do you like this?
- I love it. That's what makes me cum.
You've got 10 minutes left.
- What do you want to do? I've got a condom.
- Are you sure?
- Do you want to put it on?
- No, I don't want to soil you. I prefer just a boobjob.
I love your tits so much.
If that's his wish, let's keep going.
Are you doing ok?
Tell us when you're about to cum.
You can tell her how you want it if you want it stronger.
I don't know. Can I ask anything?
Could you spit on my cock?
It feels so nice.
Do you want the devil's handjob?
- Are you sure? - Yeah, could you do that?
Is this the devil's handjob?
It's the devil's handjob after the boobjob.
It's good.
This is a dream, isn't it?
- You have 5 minutes left.
- Not much time left.
- Can I cum? - You can cum whenever you want.
- What if I can't cum?
If you can't, we're going home.
- This is perverted.
- Do you want more lotion?
You can get whatever you want.
I love your tits but...
If you could spit on my face.
I want her spit.
- He wants your spit.
- On your hand? - On my face.
Oh your face?
If you put it on your hand and then on my face...
More?
- Thank you.
- Do you like that?
- Can I cum?
- Of course.
Oh my god. The devil's handjob...
That's amazing.
Oh my god.
I'm cumming.
That was amazing. It's on the sofa!
That was amazing.
- That was really strong.
- It surprised me.
It's all over you.
- Is it always like this?
- Yeah, when I jerk off watching her.
It's everywhere?
It's on the sofa.
It's because she's real.
Rion-chan, let's clean it up and go home.
I want to keep you forever.
You've gone over the time limit.
Thank you. Please continue supporting her.
She's going to use your bathroom.
It's that way.
Thank you.
It went everywhere.
You can jerk off watching that.
Thank you so much.
Fourth fan
This is the fourth guy.
On top of these stairs is his house.
It's amazing.
Let's go up the stairs.
- Oh my god. I'm going to fall off.
- It's that room.
Your clothes are cute.
You got really wet with lube from earlier.
It doesn't have a door bell.
- That's not a door bell.
- You can just knock the door.
- Are you...? - I'm Rion.
- You're real?
- Did you come all the way here?
- I'm yours for 30 minutes.
- Are you sure? - Do you have the time?
- I've been waiting for you.
- You can stay for however long you want.
- It's just for 30 minutes.
- Can we come in?
- Of course.
Please don't fall down.
In this occasion we are visiting...
This is amazing.
Please come in.
You're so cute.
- Thank you.
- Sorry, I'm in my underwear.
I think you got a phone call from our assistant director.
Saying he was going to check your room.
But we brought Rion instead.
Thank you. I can't believe it.
Your room is really messy.
- There's so much stuff here.
- Please make yourself at home.
You're so pretty and you smell nice.
Can we have a minute?
- Could you close that?
- Yes.
Please hold on a minute?
We haven't done anything.
- Are you doing fine?
- I couldn't breathe.
- The smell... It stinks in there.
- I don't think he's aware.
You can't tell from the video, but there was a peculiar smell in there.
I hate it too.
- I couldn't say it.
- I'm going to talk to him.
Could you go to the car?
This is not suitable for filming.
Could you wait in the car?
I'm going to talk to him. I'm so sorry.
It stinks really bad.
The director TAKE-D asked Rion to leave the room while he discussed the shooting with the fan.
Hello.
- What's the matter?
- I'm really sorry...
Would it be fine if we come some other time?
- I'll clean up, yes.
- But there's so much. - True.
I'm so sorry for showing up without notice.
So I'm sure you weren't expecting us.
We didn't tell you that she was coming.
When we come next time...
- could you maybe clean up a little bit?
- Of course.
- I'll try.
- I'm really sorry. You were waiting for us all day.
I did clean up as much as I could.
If you need, we will sent the assistant director to help you clean up.
So we're going to go for now.
- I see. What a waste of time.
- I'm so sorry.
We will definitely come back.
- I should have worn something better.
- I'm sorry for coming without notice.
I'm so sorry.
You came all the way here.
- I'm so sad.
- We'll get back to you.
I will clean up for next time.
I'm so sorry.
- Is Rion still there?
- No, she went to the car.
- I'm so sad.
- Sorry about that. Bye.
You could have enjoyed her company for a short while!!
But in this occasion we are sorry.
Fifth fan
This is the fifth fan's house.
The one before was unexpected.
Yes, it made me feel nauseous.
I explained it to him.
- I told him we would come back.
- Thanks.
- We never know what may come up.
- Yeah, unless you go to the house.
This is the last one. It's quite late.
Let's go quietly.
This last guy said in the application that...
he wanted to try sex-service play.
- Could you take this with you?
- What is this?
- That's a pervert stool.
- Pervert stool?
I'll tell you how to use it. Let's ring the bell first.
I'll hide here. Good luck.
Go ahead.
Hello, I'm Rion.
Hello. I'm here on a lease for 30 minutes.
But I was told it was going to be the crew staff only.
- I didn't know about this!
- You're allowed to do whatever you want.
I didn't know you were coming.
I think the assistant director said he would be coming to check your room out.
But Rion was with us so she came along.
We arrive unannounced.
I'm not emotionally ready for this.
Can we come in? We don't want to disturb your neighbors.
Let's go in.
- Can I put this down?
- Sure.
I will carry this for you.
Is there somewhere she can sit down?
You can come in here.
Wow.
- There're so many posters.
- It's all my posters.
I didn't expect the real one to come here.
- Please come here.
- You can sit on the bed.
- Rion-chan, it's really clean in here.
-Yes, it's very clean.
It's just the walls are white.
We had an uncomfortable situation earlier.
- It's really good, isn't it?
- Yes, very tidy.
- It's pretty messy.
- Not at all.
- There's place to walk around.
- Well, yeah.
- You submitted an application, didn't you?
- Yeah, I did.
You wrote you wanted to try sex-service play.
Yes, I want her to do things on a mat.
- That was my request.
- We couldn't bring a big mat all the way here.
- But instead, we brought this stool.
- That's what this is for?
I think Rion explained it already, but she's yours for 30 minutes.
This is only for 30 minutes?
Yes, you can do whatever you want.
- You've only got 25 minutes left.
- That's so fast!
- What do you want to do?
- I can do anything?
- Can I touch her tits?
- Sure.
Excuse me.
- I really love them.
- You're really going for it.
It's so soft. I didn't expect it to be this soft.
It's soft but bouncy.
I love it.
It's like I could fall asleep.
- Will you do this for me?
- Yes.
Could you hold on?
Suddenly, he started looking for something.
- Can you wear this for me?
- Of course.
Could you wear this and put lube on your tits?
- Is that ok?
- Sure.
Let's change.
Oh my god.
Can you see?
I didn't expect to see this for real. It's like a dream come true.
How's the real Rion?
She's cute. And pretty.
She's curvy.
Can I touch them?
I love it.
- You're sensitive.
- Yes, I like having my boobs fondled.
Sorry, I can't help myself.
This is amazing. Sorry, could you wear this?
- Have you ever worn this?
- Yes. Can you help me?
- You wore it in that DVD.
- Yes, I sometimes do.
Could you tie it in the back?
I bought it but I've never had someone wear it.
- Do I tie it in the back?
- Yes.
- Is that fine?
- I think so.
I want my girlfriend to wear this but I don't have one.
- Were you prepared, just in case?
- Yeah.
- But there's no one to wear it.
- I'm glad I'm here.
- How is it? - Is that good?
- I love it. Could you put the bottom on?
You don't have many pubes?
Not many, no.
- I like it. It's very pretty.
- Really? I'm glad.
- I love it. What shall we do now?
- Let's bring this over here. I don't want to get your carpet wet.
Rion-chan, could you bring the pervert stool here?
Let's put it here.
You can get naked.
Do you want to use this?
Where shall I sit?
Please go ahead.
It's so soft.
Could you press on me more?
Isn't the bikini in the way?
I want to enjoy the bounciness.
You can rub against me more.
You can hug me if you want.
- Can I face you?
- Face to face?
I love it.
I won't be able to sleep tonight.
- How is it?
- I love it. It's the best.
You have 20 minutes left.
Could you put them on me directly?
Can I suck it?
You love her tits.
Can you stimulate my cock too?
There's no point in having the pervert stool.
Could you do it like this then?
- Like that?
- That's an interesting way to use it.
- Like this?
- Could you touch my balls too?
- Like this? And my tits?
- Yes, please.
- How's this?
- I love it.
You're so hard.
Could you press your nipples on my cock?
You have 15 minutes left.
- Can I do anything?
- You can use this. - Oh really?
Can I fuck you on the bed?
- Can you go on top first?
- Sure.
Can I put some lube?
- You can't cum yet.
- I don't want to waste my chance.
Oh my god. I'm fucking Rion-chan.
- Do you have sensitive nipples?
- Yes, it feels amazing.
- Could it this be real? I can see everything.
- It's the real Rion-chan.
- Oh my god, it feels amazing.
- Do you like it?
You can fuck her all you want.
- Can I fuck you from behind?
- Yes, of course.
Can I use more lube?
Rion-chan, how does it feel to get fucked from behind as you see your DVDs?
It's amazing.
- Is it like this all the time?
- Do you make use of them often in bed?
Yes, I do.
- You have everything.
- Wow.
I'm looking at myself.
- I'm everywhere.
- It's crazy.
Your tits are jiggling so much.
Oh my god.
You can grab her tits all you want.
- You love tits.
- I really do.
I'm filming her tits so please jiggle them.
Please tell us when you're going to cum. Can you remove your condom when you cum?
- As much as you can.
- I don't do it usually. I'm not used to it.
I want you to cum on her.
- Cum as much as possible.
- Ok.
I'm going to cum.
- Please, try to take it off.
- I'm going to try.
It's all over his cock.
Could you touch his cum?
It's so thick. That's so thick.
- It's not dripping.
- I didn't jerk off last night.
- Do you have some tissue?
- Yes.
It's so thick. Look.
Wow, that's amazing.
- Here you are.
- Thanks.
Do you want to use this?
Rion-chan is going to clean you up so could you give her your cock?
Thank you so much. This is a dream come true. I loved it.
This is the best thing that's happened to me this year.
- I'll keep supporting you.
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much. We just need to film the last comments.
Please stand back.
Thank you so much for this video
Could you go over there?
Rion-chan... could you give us some last comments.
- This is the end. - Yes.
- How was today's experience?
It was... I realized there are all sorts of people in the world.
They are all your fans.
They are all very unique.
But it's amazing how much they love you.
They all love boobs a lot.
They all made use of their only chance.
- But it's nice to get to meet your fans, right?
- Yes.
That's the end. Let's go home.
There were some things that went wrong today.
But it's all done.
- Could she just use your shower?
- Yes.
Please buy her DVDs.
- Where's the shower?
- It's over here.
Can I ask what these handcuffs are for?
- This right here.
- I'd rather not say.
- I like to do that sometimes.
- You're such a pervert.
Take a shower and let's go home.
- Please use this towel.
- Oh thank you.
- Please take a shower.
- See you later.
Subtitles by EroJapanese.com
Copyright 2018
Visiting homes without notice. It was so exciting. We had a great time.
Big fans of Rion!!
Thanks for your support.