It is worthy of the former champion
Don't say this, seniors.
What are the seniors?
Just call it in peacetime.
No, the campus is a relationship between the front and the back.
Line
This racket for you
- The event time is pending - is it?
Let's play with this
it is good
- You want this right. - Thank you.
Right, take a few photos of club activities.
of course can
- Then I have to shoot. - Ok.
- Take a photo together. - Take a photo.
Photo
Novice female teacher consultant
Ghost student abuses the tennis department
I am Ji Gaoning.
Start class for everyone today.
Please advise
- So cute. - So cute.
Does the teacher have a boyfriend?
Quiet and quiet
Teacher Ji Gao started as a consultant today.
Responsible for sports, teaching tennis
Squad leader, please advise
it is good
- I didn’t ask this. - Sorry.
Our venue has to be taken away
Yes, sorry.
Said it all
If you dare to have two hearts
The consequences you understand
Got it
- That group of students - you are too loud
I am sorry
I don't know specifically.
But they made a lot of things
However, the chairman of the board has insufficient funds.
It’s best to be smooth.
They used to play baseball there before.
The tennis department is now working with them.
is that OK
Let me play with her
Yes, Muto, although you don’t play tennis.
But very good at sports.
But the other party is professional
Give this to me
Split the venue?
After naked teacher
You can use our venue.
Then I will be naked
I am going to ask her how to ask for conditions.
- Let her be your woman
- She is not stupid.
Not as good as this
If I win
Take the teacher's racket
Continue that educational game
That's it, no problem.
The teacher wants to win, get the venue.
- I want to be biased towards the teacher.
- No, be fair.
Also
Ji Gao serve
-Out of bounds -Ming Ming Online
Teacher, how do you teach students?
- Out of bounds - The bridge
I am very sorry to continue the game.
Teacher, I forgot to wear glasses.
I will go and take it down.
time out
The teacher is not professional.
Really played very well
Yes, forget it.
Directors prefer baseball
If there is no baseball field, it’s very troublesome.
For the venue unscrupulous
When is the educator appropriate?
Stop the game.
Too late
Stop now, there will be no change.
how come
How about this
I just want to win
The teacher only wants the venue right.
Consensus
But don’t win, no
I will give you a chance.
opportunity
Do not wear underwear to play
Do not wear underwear for intense exercise
It should be seen by everyone.
Then continue the game
Before this change referee
Trouble
Then continue the game.
Start
15 to 0
Can't be seen by them
No panties
Seems like not wearing
be quiet
15 to 30
Ji Gao serve
Online?
I don’t see it too much.
Online, I lost.
End of the game Ji Gao wins
I lost.
Why are you saying this?
Don't you want to win?
The real battle is now starting
Man woman hormonal fight
what are you doing
The teacher is excited too.
Getting hot
let me go
Let me see how
Still telling your boyfriend
How did you know
Can see that it is in communication
well
Do not
If you know that you are
Listening to me, I don’t wear underwear.
He must be shocked.
Teacher, this is a transaction.
No matter what I say
I have to listen to it.
Then first
- Start here first - Don't
Do not
- don't
- Why do you want me to go to the chairperson?
Do not
- Tell your boyfriend.
- don't ask you.
- Let me see it. - Don't.
- Can I touch it? - I don't ask you.
The teacher said not to
Still want to be touched
Here
- Seriously.
- Don't want me not to like this
The chest is very cute.
Look
The teacher is also an adult.
I was serious
Hard nipples show me
- Please, please.
- It really reacted.
- Good hard. - No.
- The teacher is serious too. - No.
Hard
It’s hard here.
Do not
Please do not
Please, please.
Harder and harder
carry on
Directly, it’s more comfortable.
- The chest is hot. - Don't.
- Please don't continue. - Legs apart.
Do not
Is it just wet?
no
Not very good?
Turn around
Very good teacher
- Let me see it. - Don't.
Just at the time of the game
Your ass is up
Here
- Is the underwear worn? - Don't
Like it, like this.
Can't stop it?
Twist like this
- Do you like this? - Don't touch
why
Don't listen to the teacher?
Let's talk to the chairman.
- What to do. Continue or let me go.
-Do not want any
Do not want any
Then I won't stop.
Here
Let me see more ass
Very good, come over
I want to be touched here.
- don't - the taste of sensuality
- don't
Lust
What is the taste here?
- Please, please. - Don't you want to be taken off?
like this
Is this?
Then
Use this
- don't ask you.
- Why don't you want me to use your hand?
The racket is not used to do this kind of thing.
How do you feel?
- Tell me how to use it. - Don't.
Do you know this?
- I only use it like this - don't
What seems to be making a sound?
Do not
What happened?
Why do you have to do this kind of prank?
Because the teacher does not teach me how to use the racket
Turn around and relax
Separate feet, do you know what it means?
- use like this - don't
Is this?
Do not
Is this comfortable?
no
Will it be like this to a boyfriend?
- It’s so color. - No.
- Variable speed?
You said this, I will feel like this.
What did you say? Just
- How is it here? - No.
Have a good time to confirm
Do not
- It seems to be wet here. - No.
Sweat
So have to confirm it.
Do not
I just didn't go in.
Going in now
Here
Take your hand and open it. I can see it here.
- Wet - Don't look
- here - don't
Teacher, it’s hot here.
what happened
- don't
- You just didn't teach me how to use a racket.
- What is going on here? - No.
Do not
- Don't - How is the little hole?
- don't
- Continue to let me touch here.
It’s hot
Do not
It’s very tight here.
Good
I beg you
What is this teacher?
Tell me here, don't tell me?
- don't - continue - don't
- The underwear is so wet. - Don't.
- We are still wet than
Is it comfortable here? Is it really ok?
Then out
Game change
Next, the teacher makes me comfortable.
- Come - don't
Said, then the teacher.
- this - what?
Here
Obedient
Do not
What happened? So
Teacher
-what
- I said the teacher.
- Come - don't
- Don't want to be like this.
What happened? Teacher
Comfortable?
no, do not want
Come to the real showdown
Continue just now
The teacher came out a lot.
- Don't touch words - don't want to be like this
Would you like me to tell others?
Do not
The teacher is not good, can't you?
Does the teacher like it?
So how is this?
More intense
Deeper
Look here, see here, teacher.
- Seriously - don't
Deeper
Like it
time up
I said time is up, come over.
- Don't why. - Come over.
-do not come
- Why - come over to the teacher
no, do not want
-Here
- I don’t ask you, you are dry.
Isn't it a serious fight?
Don't say no, don't
To start
Do not
- What happened? - No.
- Is it comfortable? Teacher
- No, don’t ask for you.
-Comfortable
- Enjoy it. - No.
- wet - don't
- Don't - Comfortable?
- Why did it sound out? - Don't
What is this sound?
Do not
No, no.
Amazing
- Don't - the sound is quite big.
- don't - what?
No, no.
Very comfortable, teacher.
Do not
What happened? I can't understand.
- Keep going. - Don't.
Do not
- Come over, teacher - don't
- don't - what?
- Please, please. - No.
Do you like it?
-what
- Don't you say that you can't do it?
- What do you do last? - Don't
- Teacher, butt is facing me. - Don't.
Hurry up, turn around
Good posture
Very good teacher
- Very good teacher. - No.
So hot
Do not
- What? - No.
No, I have to go.
Asking you, why is it climax?
- Why is it climax? - Don't
Do you like to like to enter?
no
No, no.
carry on
Here
Do not
No, no.
Comfortable
No, I have to go. No.
The teacher likes to go in.
- No. - That's right.
Next
Go here
Do not
well
- Stand up. - Don't stop.
Don't like it very much, why do you say this?
- Are you shy? Don't
- here - don't
Do not
No, I have to go. No.
Got a few times, ask you
- Please, stop. - Why?
- Can't you do it? - Don't.
Do not
- Is it climax?
- No, I have to go.
No, no.
The teacher is lascivious.
I want to see all the teachers.
Here the hat is worn
Do not
- Can you shoot it? - Don't
- Don't - continue? I have to shoot.
- don't
I have to shoot
how come
I saw you making love with him.
No, I am forced
force
That teacher is going to class soon.
I will ask you again after school.
Forced?
How is it comfortable?
The teacher did not wear panties.
Everyone feels very strange
- I don’t wear it now. - No.
The teacher is so stiff.
- Show me - don't
- Teacher - What do you do?
- Wear it like this.
Lustful ass
so cute
Teacher, your body is lascivious.
Don't want this bridge
Here
- It's amazing. - Don't.
- Excited, show me - don't
- Teacher - Don't
- What are you doing? - A little bit of color
Do not
Amazing
- don't
- What happened? Does the teacher feel it?
No, what are you doing?
Teacher, let me see it.
- Don't touch me - because it is very comfortable
- No. - No?
It’s very comfortable here, teacher, lascivious.
- And it’s beautiful. - What are you talking about?
no, do not want
- See you. - Don't.
Teacher, feel good, show me
- don't - here
- like here - don't touch me.
Where do you want to be touched? Teacher
Don't say no
- Where? - Say don't touch.
Don't touch where
Right here.
Amazing
Very rough, teacher.
- Enough is not enough - Teacher
- Teacher - Don't
- How are you comfortable?
-Do not touch me
- Is it comfortable? - No.
Then why is he?
Teacher, let me touch it.
Amazing
Do not
I want to see more
- Lust teacher - don't
- Ok, the teacher showed me.
-what
Otherwise it is very dangerous
no, do not want
- Great, teacher. - Don't.
- Ass is beautiful. - Don't.
- Great. - Why do this?
- Is it comfortable? It seems to be wet. - No.
- Teacher's ass - don't look
- What's wrong, I want to be seen.
-no
Here
Lust, teacher
It’s very comfortable here.
I wanted to touch the teacher's ass before.
- Teacher - Don't
- How? - No.
Look, let’s go in.
- It’s a comfortable place.
-no
Clitoris
Look like this
- What's wrong? Is it a asshole?
-do not look
Le went in, teacher.
Teacher, sure enough.
- Look - don't you, why?
- It’s wet, teacher, why?
-no
- Is it true that when I was in class?
Is that true? Teacher
- Wet here - Don't
- Good wet - don't
- Still say asshole - no
- Teacher, right? - No.
Teacher, my ass tilted up and showed it to me.
No, I don't want this
- Why is the teacher beautiful? Show me
- don't
- So beautiful ass. - No.
- Are you shy? Teacher.
- No, don't.
- Quiet, I am going to marry.
- don't
Do not
- Don't - wet, teacher.
Please
Do not
What happened? Teacher
Not letting you be quiet?
Although very comfortable
But what if I hear too loudly?
Don't mess
- here - don't - come on
- here - don't
Do not
Very good teacher
- Are you excited? - Don't
- Don't continue. - What is the relationship?
Do not
- Let me see - don't
- How about the teacher - don't
so cute
Teacher, so beautiful.
It’s beautiful.
- Come to the teacher - don't
Teacher, what is going on?
What is the situation?
The teacher is really a lecherous female teacher.
- No. - What is not?
-do not do that
Is this the case?
Lust, teacher
- wet - don't
- Please, please.
- Is it comfortable here?
- here - don't
Good wet
Do not
- No. - What does the teacher endure?
- I want to climax.
- No, stop.
It’s so wet
- I want to climax.
- No, please.
- Come - don't
Do not
Very good teacher, shaking very well
Waist is moving
It’s amazing, keep going, teacher.
- Can you continue? - Don't
- Do you like this? Two fingers
- don't
Sure enough, still two fingers.
- It’s so deep. - Don’t.
Can you see it?
Nice slutty teacher
Do not
No, I have to go.
Teacher is very good
The teacher is very good, so wet.
Very tight
Teacher is very good
My fingers are wet
Very good, teacher.
no
The club activities are going well.
Previous game
If you win, you can use it.
I heard about it from Muto.
This state is too good
Now it’s a tennis court.
This bridge, what do you do?
- Teacher - You are dry.
- Give it to me - don't
- No, don't you. - Anything?
Be careful, I will tell you your secrets.
- Come - don't
- Make me comfortable
Do not
I will tell everyone that line.
That makes me comfortable.
Come
Faster
Including
So comfortable, teacher
- Don't - Why stop?
- don't
keep going
If you don’t hurry, be careful.
The teacher is really lascivious.
Actually all contain
Teacher, skilled
teacher
- It’s also here. - No.
- reverse side
There is also a testicle, the tongue sticks out.
well
I will listen to what I say, teacher.
look here
Right, okay?
So comfortable
well
awesome
Delicious? Teacher
Contain
Look here
So comfortable
teacher
- I want to see your ass. - No.
- No, I want to see it. Teacher.
- Show me - don't
Let’s take it off.
- Teacher, I’m gonna call me.
- don't
well
Nice ass
Harder
Amazing
Do not
The teacher showed me the underwear.
- don't
- Not excited enough, don't want to end soon?
OKOK
- Come over - don't
What's wrong? Don't let go, teacher.
Including
So comfortable
Very good, then fierce, ah, good 舔
Very good teacher
Watching me continue
So comfortable, very good
So comfortable
- Very good. Teacher - let me go.
Not enough, I didn’t shoot
teacher
So comfortable
well
Let me shoot it quickly
It’s over today.
Teacher, look at me舔
well
Very comfortable, very good
Very good, very comfortable
The teacher is going to shoot
teacher
well
The teacher is going to shoot very well.
teacher
Teacher, mouth
I have to shoot
So comfortable
Teacher, open your mouth and show it to me.
- Shoot a lot, delicious? Teacher.
- don't
The teacher is really a good teacher.
awesome
no
What should the teacher do?
Are you leaving with us? Teacher
Still going to report it?
- Come here, teacher. - What?
Here here
No, what?
- Continue. - Don't want it.
I want to go where I don't like it?
- Don't mess up - don't
no, do not want
- Everyone wants this - don't
- Yes, right. - Come.
no, do not want
- What do you want? - Do you like this?
- No. - Like this.
Why do this kind of thing?
- The teacher clearly likes it - not
I saw it all right.
Hard here
- Don't - make it harder here.
The teacher is comfortable, making this sound.
- I want to see it. - Teacher comes.
Come see us
no, do not want
- I saw it. - Really good. Teacher.
- Don't look. - Very beautiful. Teacher.
- Come over - what?
- I want to touch it. - How do you touch it?
- Do you like this?
Do you like this?
- Don't let me go. - Like it.
- like this - don't
Very good teacher
Watched by everyone
Please, don't look.
The teacher is so cute
What is the relationship?
- here - don't
- Here? - Don't let me go.
Is it comfortable here?
- Still touch directly - also
- Don’t ask you.
Want to be touched?
Very hard, hard
- don't - haven't touched yet - here
Do not
- Breathing is rushing. - Is it comfortable?
- don't - hard
- The teacher is very sensitive. - Teacher.
- Where do you like to be touched? - Don't
The teacher is great.
Here
- I want to be touched here too.
- Don't do it.
- Very sensitive. Teacher.
- Is it ok here?
- don't
-Students ask for you.
Please let me go
- What is the relationship?
- Don’t ask you.
- Ask for you - scissors
- Don't - like it.
- If so, don't.
Do you like being shackled at the same time?
Do not
- Why - Of course not
- obviously made this sound
- Lust, teacher.
- here - don't - good hard
What happened under the underwear?
Good intention
- So curious, I want to see.
- Don’t ask you anymore.
No, everyone.
like this
Don't shoot
- It’s wet. - No.
- Do you feel it? - Don't
Look, teacher.
-Here - it’s amazing.
Don't look away
- It's amazing. - Don't.
- Don't do this. - Like it.
I am very interested in the female body.
Learn here, teacher
- Yes.
- This is not learning.
Isn't it?
Don't shoot
- Learning to learn - yes.
Teacher, how comfortable, tell us
no, do not want
- Look, teacher. - Don't.
- Look at it clearly - don't
Like to be touched, teacher
- Come - OK.
- Show it to everyone - don't
Look
- Come - don't
- Please do not. - Can you see it?
- It’s just clear - the asshole is visible
Do not
- Learned - is not learning
is it
- If it’s not learning, just do it.
-What are you doing
Do not
I just want to be like this
- It’s amazing.
- Please, don't.
Amazing
Why are you so wet, teacher told me
What are you forbearing?
Do not
- Trembling is great - don't
No here
Do not
Amazing
Teacher, look at the ass.
- Give me a good look.
- I want to show us the minimum guarantee.
Really good, very good
- Come - very good
- You guys. - Very good.
- I saw the teacher, asshole.
- don't
- What are you not? - Please, please.
What happened, let me see
Teacher, where is it comfortable?
- Where - What?
- Have a comfortable place.
Is it here?
Look, wet, have you seen it?
look
- here - don't
It’s also very wet here.
Do not
- Please, please.
-how about it
Is this the teacher?
- How? - No.
Teacher, it’s so wet here.
- It's amazing. - Don't ask.
- here - don't
- here - no - here
- Are you going? Teacher, show me.
- I want to see the teacher's face.
- don't
- Trembling is great. Teacher.
What kind of fingers do you like?
- Don't - like what
Do not
Don't do this kind of thing
No, here can't, please.
Teacher, so comfortable
Also makes me comfortable
Come over, what should the teacher do?
Don't want to continue, don't
Is that okay? That photo
Understand, teacher
Look here teacher
I want to hold it.
Contain and then 撸
Teacher, skilled
Teacher, look here
Very good, the teacher is lascivious.
- No. - What happened? Teacher.
Here
- Come hold it - like this
I like it very much.
Teacher, can't you have a boyfriend?
I can’t satisfy you completely.
- Play with us later. - Don't.
My also come
- It’s so comfortable. It’s amazing.
So comfortable, the teacher is coming.
There is still no stop here.
Everyone is watching, what are you looking like?
Very good, delicious?
-Like it. -Two at the same time.
very good
- Very good. - I like the teacher.
So comfortable
Unlucky
- It’s so comfortable. - The teacher wants to be jealous.
- How? - Think about it.
- Please, let me go.
- Let’s go together.
Don't ask you anymore
- Come over - don't
So clear
- Come over, oh, don't.
- Great. - Don't.
- So comfortable, teacher.
-continue
Comfortable
Very good, sit up
Come
Everyone is watching it.
Very comfortable
- Don't - the teacher's waist is frozen.
- Do you like it? - No.
- How is this? - Don't ask for you.
Tongue is moving
Do not
Don't be too good
- Please, please.
- Do you want me to stop?
- Then continue. How? - Teacher.
I like it.
Let me touch my chest
Very good, a little deeper
well
Very good, very comfortable
I’m gonna go, no.
- Lust. - Is it climax?
- Trembling is great. Is it climax?
Do you like being jealous?
Shouldn't you want this?
look
Kneeling
Teacher is going to insert
Very good teacher, very tight
how is it going
- this - don't be so deep
Don't you like it?
So comfortable
Let's get deeper
Here
Very good, very comfortable
No, no.
- Can't you?
- No, don't be so intense.
I am moving myself.
Very good very good
So comfortable, is the teacher comfortable?
- It's amazing. - The teacher is so lascivious.
You have been waiting for a long time - don't
- Look, I have it.
- Moving?
- The teacher is very good. - Good meeting.
So comfortable
- It’s amazing. - Think about me?
I want to ask you to insert you.
- Don't - let everyone hear
Move up
- What? - Move it up.
No way, teacher.
Look at me like this
No, no.
Very tight
Teacher, very comfortable
The teacher also wants it.
Ok, why is he so comfortable?
Can you make me comfortable?
Insert deep
Amazing
Great
No, I can’t help but twist.
What happened? Teacher
The teacher is a little faster than just
Can't stop
well
One start
- No, is it comfortable?
- No, no.
No, it’s so comfortable.
No, no.
Teacher
Come to contain
Right
The teacher moved up and down again.
Amazing
I like this, teacher.
Very good, is the teacher comfortable?
No, this is not working.
Going to go
Teacher is very good
- Wet - Teacher, stand up
Stand up, feel comfortable, hold hands
Amazing
So comfortable
So comfortable, you are comfortable too.
- How? - No.
No, it won't work.
No, no.
The teacher is climaxing right away.
- No. - This is not okay. Teacher.
Not enough, look at me.
I like it very much, teacher.
Comfortable
- Teacher, great. - No.
- No, it’s amazing.
Don't stop
It’s amazing. - Please, don’t say it.
- Let us be comfortable.
- No, no.
No, I have to go.
- Very good. - No.
The teacher is climaxing?
No, no.
Strange
Very good, good wet
Is it climax?
Very good teacher, look here
Don't look at it - shrinking small holes
- Orgasm, it’s amazing.
- I want to see the teacher.
Come
Here
So comfortable
-do not do that
- You are very happy.
- No, it’s here.
Don't be gone
- It's so comfortable. - No.
No, I have to go.
Come to the teacher
Holding hands
So comfortable
well
Don't be gone
- How are you comfortable?
- don't don't
Everyone can see it, plug it so deep.
- Can you see it? - Don't be like this.
Can you see it?
Give cute students a look
Come
lie down
teacher
Comfortable
- Excited. - Don't look.
- Can you see it? - What are you doing?
Excited, just like the teacher.
Do not
Amazing
really not bad
Have a climax many times?
We can also shoot it.
- What? Everyone is watching.
- Don't - not just watching it.
Do not
No, no.
No, it’s strange.
I also want to insert it.
Yes, teacher.
The teacher’s here is so wet.
- Teacher - Don't
Plugged in
Very good teacher, very comfortable
Do not
- Comfortable. - No.
No, no.
- No, is it? - Is this?
- No, no.
- No, I have to go. - Climax.
Everyone is stunned.
- They all want to shoot.
-no, do not want
- What's up, like it. - No.
- No. - What is not?
Like this
Just want to be like this
- Say you want to shoot. - Don't.
Can you shoot?
Teacher, watch everyone climax.
Come to be shot by everyone
No, no.
- No, here. - Comfortable.
Going to go
I said, don't you shoot?
What's wrong? Don't you?
- I want to shoot. Can you? - Don't.
The teacher is so good that I have to shoot.
teacher
Really fornication
Here
- Still oh - don't
- Stop now. - Why?
- Don't - the teacher has climaxed several times.
- don't
- Everyone wants to shoot too. - Don't
Don't you think? Teacher
- Everyone wants to shoot. - Don't.
what
Don't have to endure to the teacher
Direct shot is fine
Do not
Shot a lot
Amazing
I have to shoot
So comfortable
- It’s amazing. It’s not a teacher.
I can’t help myself, the teacher is going to shoot.
Teacher, laughing one
-Photos of club activities - don't
Sent to the homepage
There will be a lot of new members next year.
Do not
Actor: Ji Gaoning々
Production: S1 NO.1 STYLE
Ji Gaoning, decoration, tennis consultant
Takeda Daishu (TKD) decoration Muto
Hashimoto Shogo
Tsuyoshi Gohda Decoration Senior Teacher
END